[
    {
        "question": "57 - 43",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 14
    },
    {
        "question": "311 - 59",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 252
    },
    {
        "question": "197 - 25",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 172
    },
    {
        "question": "18 - 69",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -51
    },
    {
        "question": "301 + 57",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 358
    },
    {
        "question": "256 x 27",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 6912
    },
    {
        "question": "154 + 1",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 155
    },
    {
        "question": "309 - 5",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 304
    },
    {
        "question": "187 x 97",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 18139
    },
    {
        "question": "71 + 59",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 130
    },
    {
        "question": "242 - 23",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 219
    },
    {
        "question": "9 - 95",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -86
    },
    {
        "question": "338 - 79",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 259
    },
    {
        "question": "55 x 83",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 4565
    },
    {
        "question": "145 - 85",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 60
    },
    {
        "question": "44 x 79",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 3476
    },
    {
        "question": "4 - 19",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -15
    },
    {
        "question": "75 - 63",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 12
    },
    {
        "question": "375 - 21",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 354
    },
    {
        "question": "6 + 27",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 33
    },
    {
        "question": "126 - 37",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 89
    },
    {
        "question": "294 - 65",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 229
    },
    {
        "question": "113 x 87",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 9831
    },
    {
        "question": "56 + 97",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 153
    },
    {
        "question": "338 - 21",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 317
    },
    {
        "question": "49 + 65",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 114
    },
    {
        "question": "98 x 17",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1666
    },
    {
        "question": "340 + 49",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 389
    },
    {
        "question": "159 - 35",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 124
    },
    {
        "question": "219 x 59",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 12921
    },
    {
        "question": "157 - 67",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 90
    },
    {
        "question": "266 - 65",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 201
    },
    {
        "question": "381 + 1",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 382
    },
    {
        "question": "41 x 21",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 861
    },
    {
        "question": "150 x 73",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 10950
    },
    {
        "question": "360 x 45",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 16200
    },
    {
        "question": "137 - 51",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 86
    },
    {
        "question": "374 + 69",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 443
    },
    {
        "question": "63 x 97",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 6111
    },
    {
        "question": "45 - 85",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -40
    },
    {
        "question": "304 + 31",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 335
    },
    {
        "question": "219 + 13",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 232
    },
    {
        "question": "107 x 11",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1177
    },
    {
        "question": "212 + 63",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 275
    },
    {
        "question": "130 x 89",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 11570
    },
    {
        "question": "3 - 47",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -44
    },
    {
        "question": "315 - 63",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 252
    },
    {
        "question": "180 - 1",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 179
    },
    {
        "question": "31 x 39",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1209
    },
    {
        "question": "261 - 31",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 230
    },
    {
        "question": "31 - 49",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -18
    },
    {
        "question": "216 x 11",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 2376
    },
    {
        "question": "323 - 1",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 322
    },
    {
        "question": "64 - 93",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -29
    },
    {
        "question": "270 x 3",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 810
    },
    {
        "question": "148 - 81",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 67
    },
    {
        "question": "277 + 91",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 368
    },
    {
        "question": "148 x 7",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1036
    },
    {
        "question": "92 x 83",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 7636
    },
    {
        "question": "366 - 61",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 305
    },
    {
        "question": "257 x 95",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 24415
    },
    {
        "question": "32 x 25",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 800
    },
    {
        "question": "28 + 19",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 47
    },
    {
        "question": "223 + 99",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 322
    },
    {
        "question": "317 + 31",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 348
    },
    {
        "question": "235 + 73",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 308
    },
    {
        "question": "140 + 87",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 227
    },
    {
        "question": "182 - 41",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 141
    },
    {
        "question": "344 x 7",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 2408
    },
    {
        "question": "352 + 73",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 425
    },
    {
        "question": "324 - 73",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 251
    },
    {
        "question": "131 + 31",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 162
    },
    {
        "question": "396 x 87",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 34452
    },
    {
        "question": "353 x 91",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 32123
    },
    {
        "question": "370 - 63",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 307
    },
    {
        "question": "124 - 27",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 97
    },
    {
        "question": "389 + 93",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 482
    },
    {
        "question": "95 - 81",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 14
    },
    {
        "question": "107 - 55",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 52
    },
    {
        "question": "262 - 59",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 203
    },
    {
        "question": "138 - 95",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 43
    },
    {
        "question": "176 + 7",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 183
    },
    {
        "question": "130 x 41",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 5330
    },
    {
        "question": "294 + 51",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 345
    },
    {
        "question": "326 x 67",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 21842
    },
    {
        "question": "374 x 77",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 28798
    },
    {
        "question": "145 x 33",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 4785
    },
    {
        "question": "305 - 77",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 228
    },
    {
        "question": "231 + 83",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 314
    },
    {
        "question": "64 + 73",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 137
    },
    {
        "question": "143 + 89",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 232
    },
    {
        "question": "119 + 55",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 174
    },
    {
        "question": "91 + 71",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 162
    },
    {
        "question": "374 - 5",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 369
    },
    {
        "question": "271 + 35",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 306
    },
    {
        "question": "146 + 77",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 223
    },
    {
        "question": "104 + 63",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 167
    },
    {
        "question": "234 - 11",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 223
    },
    {
        "question": "375 + 53",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 428
    },
    {
        "question": "159 + 37",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 196
    },
    {
        "question": "273 x 75",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 20475
    },
    {
        "question": "100 x 87",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 8700
    },
    {
        "question": "394 x 13",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 5122
    },
    {
        "question": "168 - 59",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 109
    },
    {
        "question": "90 + 79",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 169
    },
    {
        "question": "29 x 97",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 2813
    },
    {
        "question": "43 x 9",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 387
    },
    {
        "question": "113 + 25",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 138
    },
    {
        "question": "336 - 55",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 281
    },
    {
        "question": "6 + 73",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 79
    },
    {
        "question": "198 + 89",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 287
    },
    {
        "question": "62 + 97",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 159
    },
    {
        "question": "183 + 65",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 248
    },
    {
        "question": "384 + 93",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 477
    },
    {
        "question": "80 x 5",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 400
    },
    {
        "question": "21 - 21",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "253 - 47",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 206
    },
    {
        "question": "383 - 3",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 380
    },
    {
        "question": "217 x 7",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1519
    },
    {
        "question": "132 - 95",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 37
    },
    {
        "question": "71 x 99",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 7029
    },
    {
        "question": "159 x 53",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 8427
    },
    {
        "question": "282 + 47",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 329
    },
    {
        "question": "127 - 49",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 78
    },
    {
        "question": "288 x 55",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 15840
    },
    {
        "question": "1 + 79",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 80
    },
    {
        "question": "355 - 91",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 264
    },
    {
        "question": "58 + 71",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 129
    },
    {
        "question": "121 x 51",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 6171
    },
    {
        "question": "132 + 1",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 133
    },
    {
        "question": "97 + 65",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 162
    },
    {
        "question": "79 + 63",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 142
    },
    {
        "question": "164 x 89",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 14596
    },
    {
        "question": "90 + 85",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 175
    },
    {
        "question": "15 - 13",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "138 - 41",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 97
    },
    {
        "question": "55 + 47",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 102
    },
    {
        "question": "326 + 79",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 405
    },
    {
        "question": "217 x 97",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 21049
    },
    {
        "question": "225 - 11",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 214
    },
    {
        "question": "158 x 9",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1422
    },
    {
        "question": "297 - 25",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 272
    },
    {
        "question": "139 - 97",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 42
    },
    {
        "question": "343 - 63",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 280
    },
    {
        "question": "302 x 85",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 25670
    },
    {
        "question": "272 - 13",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 259
    },
    {
        "question": "328 x 53",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 17384
    },
    {
        "question": "297 + 43",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 340
    },
    {
        "question": "292 x 39",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 11388
    },
    {
        "question": "236 + 69",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 305
    },
    {
        "question": "80 x 79",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 6320
    },
    {
        "question": "137 - 59",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 78
    },
    {
        "question": "66 + 85",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 151
    },
    {
        "question": "196 + 81",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 277
    },
    {
        "question": "255 x 53",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 13515
    },
    {
        "question": "358 + 3",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 361
    },
    {
        "question": "148 x 5",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 740
    },
    {
        "question": "359 + 63",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 422
    },
    {
        "question": "325 - 23",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 302
    },
    {
        "question": "301 + 27",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 328
    },
    {
        "question": "260 + 97",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 357
    },
    {
        "question": "130 x 15",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1950
    },
    {
        "question": "304 - 21",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 283
    },
    {
        "question": "338 x 41",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 13858
    },
    {
        "question": "265 - 85",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 180
    },
    {
        "question": "70 x 99",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 6930
    },
    {
        "question": "208 + 45",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 253
    },
    {
        "question": "33 + 9",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 42
    },
    {
        "question": "391 + 41",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 432
    },
    {
        "question": "228 x 13",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 2964
    },
    {
        "question": "176 x 39",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 6864
    },
    {
        "question": "64 + 81",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 145
    },
    {
        "question": "94 - 19",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 75
    },
    {
        "question": "35 x 13",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 455
    },
    {
        "question": "277 - 25",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 252
    },
    {
        "question": "275 - 1",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 274
    },
    {
        "question": "111 - 7",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 104
    },
    {
        "question": "155 x 55",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 8525
    },
    {
        "question": "358 + 23",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 381
    },
    {
        "question": "154 + 25",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 179
    },
    {
        "question": "327 + 3",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 330
    },
    {
        "question": "341 + 15",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 356
    },
    {
        "question": "299 + 7",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 306
    },
    {
        "question": "137 + 57",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 194
    },
    {
        "question": "123 - 49",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 74
    },
    {
        "question": "248 - 67",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 181
    },
    {
        "question": "25 x 97",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 2425
    },
    {
        "question": "189 - 53",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 136
    },
    {
        "question": "280 + 17",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 297
    },
    {
        "question": "97 - 77",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 20
    },
    {
        "question": "168 + 17",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 185
    },
    {
        "question": "376 x 87",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 32712
    },
    {
        "question": "150 + 99",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 249
    },
    {
        "question": "183 + 61",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 244
    },
    {
        "question": "347 + 47",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 394
    },
    {
        "question": "182 - 5",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 177
    },
    {
        "question": "208 - 47",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 161
    },
    {
        "question": "374 x 25",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 9350
    },
    {
        "question": "118 - 57",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 61
    },
    {
        "question": "146 x 59",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 8614
    },
    {
        "question": "144 x 75",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 10800
    },
    {
        "question": "233 x 91",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 21203
    },
    {
        "question": "159 - 37",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 122
    },
    {
        "question": "180 + 69",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 249
    },
    {
        "question": "349 - 69",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 280
    },
    {
        "question": "371 x 25",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 9275
    },
    {
        "question": "214 + 31",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 245
    },
    {
        "question": "92 - 11",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 81
    },
    {
        "question": "89 + 59",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 148
    },
    {
        "question": "279 x 83",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 23157
    },
    {
        "question": "155 - 33",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 122
    },
    {
        "question": "4 x 71",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 284
    },
    {
        "question": "333 + 67",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 400
    },
    {
        "question": "242 x 17",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 4114
    },
    {
        "question": "347 + 23",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 370
    },
    {
        "question": "186 - 7",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 179
    },
    {
        "question": "303 + 63",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 366
    },
    {
        "question": "289 x 47",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 13583
    },
    {
        "question": "102 + 45",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 147
    },
    {
        "question": "353 + 53",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 406
    },
    {
        "question": "30 + 45",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 75
    },
    {
        "question": "269 + 19",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 288
    },
    {
        "question": "217 - 13",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 204
    },
    {
        "question": "301 x 93",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 27993
    },
    {
        "question": "294 + 93",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 387
    },
    {
        "question": "33 - 37",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -4
    },
    {
        "question": "242 - 99",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 143
    },
    {
        "question": "142 x 67",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 9514
    },
    {
        "question": "352 - 63",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 289
    },
    {
        "question": "336 x 7",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 2352
    },
    {
        "question": "36 - 65",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -29
    },
    {
        "question": "59 + 13",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 72
    },
    {
        "question": "1 + 95",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 96
    },
    {
        "question": "127 - 81",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 46
    },
    {
        "question": "113 x 35",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 3955
    },
    {
        "question": "214 + 71",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 285
    },
    {
        "question": "326 x 93",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 30318
    },
    {
        "question": "261 + 81",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 342
    },
    {
        "question": "230 x 59",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 13570
    },
    {
        "question": "383 x 67",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 25661
    },
    {
        "question": "239 - 7",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 232
    },
    {
        "question": "158 - 39",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 119
    },
    {
        "question": "283 - 91",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 192
    },
    {
        "question": "24 x 25",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 600
    },
    {
        "question": "103 - 53",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 50
    },
    {
        "question": "3 - 35",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -32
    },
    {
        "question": "319 + 83",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 402
    },
    {
        "question": "370 x 37",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 13690
    },
    {
        "question": "31 - 13",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 18
    },
    {
        "question": "127 x 25",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 3175
    },
    {
        "question": "191 - 13",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 178
    },
    {
        "question": "241 + 77",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 318
    },
    {
        "question": "345 + 29",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 374
    },
    {
        "question": "286 + 61",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 347
    },
    {
        "question": "337 x 1",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 337
    },
    {
        "question": "339 x 75",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 25425
    },
    {
        "question": "188 x 51",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 9588
    },
    {
        "question": "202 x 73",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 14746
    },
    {
        "question": "329 x 21",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 6909
    },
    {
        "question": "301 x 85",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 25585
    },
    {
        "question": "395 - 79",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 316
    },
    {
        "question": "281 x 15",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 4215
    },
    {
        "question": "37 - 11",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 26
    },
    {
        "question": "243 x 25",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 6075
    },
    {
        "question": "145 x 97",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 14065
    },
    {
        "question": "197 + 67",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 264
    },
    {
        "question": "30 - 5",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 25
    },
    {
        "question": "144 x 27",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 3888
    },
    {
        "question": "18 x 5",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 90
    },
    {
        "question": "127 - 95",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 32
    },
    {
        "question": "256 x 11",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 2816
    },
    {
        "question": "396 - 63",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 333
    },
    {
        "question": "225 + 45",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 270
    },
    {
        "question": "282 x 47",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 13254
    },
    {
        "question": "12 + 67",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 79
    },
    {
        "question": "298 - 83",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 215
    },
    {
        "question": "114 x 43",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 4902
    },
    {
        "question": "38 + 87",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 125
    },
    {
        "question": "79 + 85",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 164
    },
    {
        "question": "192 - 63",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 129
    },
    {
        "question": "29 x 79",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 2291
    },
    {
        "question": "27 x 81",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 2187
    },
    {
        "question": "85 + 39",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 124
    },
    {
        "question": "66 - 99",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -33
    },
    {
        "question": "265 - 15",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 250
    },
    {
        "question": "35 + 29",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 64
    },
    {
        "question": "322 + 61",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 383
    },
    {
        "question": "172 + 61",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 233
    },
    {
        "question": "170 x 91",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 15470
    },
    {
        "question": "320 - 25",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 295
    },
    {
        "question": "25 + 35",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 60
    },
    {
        "question": "33 - 43",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -10
    },
    {
        "question": "115 + 51",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 166
    },
    {
        "question": "270 x 33",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 8910
    },
    {
        "question": "99 - 27",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 72
    },
    {
        "question": "358 - 17",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 341
    },
    {
        "question": "4 x 43",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 172
    },
    {
        "question": "161 - 57",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 104
    },
    {
        "question": "231 - 33",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 198
    },
    {
        "question": "263 x 17",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 4471
    },
    {
        "question": "367 + 29",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 396
    },
    {
        "question": "7 + 7",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 14
    },
    {
        "question": "323 - 15",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 308
    },
    {
        "question": "40 - 87",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -47
    },
    {
        "question": "298 + 85",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 383
    },
    {
        "question": "229 x 71",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 16259
    },
    {
        "question": "323 x 21",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 6783
    },
    {
        "question": "295 x 45",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 13275
    },
    {
        "question": "361 x 89",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 32129
    },
    {
        "question": "154 x 27",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 4158
    },
    {
        "question": "261 - 71",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 190
    },
    {
        "question": "36 x 91",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 3276
    },
    {
        "question": "386 - 51",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 335
    },
    {
        "question": "328 + 35",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 363
    },
    {
        "question": "97 - 91",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 6
    },
    {
        "question": "188 + 5",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 193
    },
    {
        "question": "137 + 43",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 180
    },
    {
        "question": "29 x 25",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 725
    },
    {
        "question": "373 - 65",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 308
    },
    {
        "question": "125 x 53",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 6625
    },
    {
        "question": "71 + 93",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 164
    },
    {
        "question": "282 - 37",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 245
    },
    {
        "question": "355 x 23",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 8165
    },
    {
        "question": "196 + 47",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 243
    },
    {
        "question": "294 x 19",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 5586
    },
    {
        "question": "274 + 55",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 329
    },
    {
        "question": "335 - 91",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 244
    },
    {
        "question": "124 + 93",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 217
    },
    {
        "question": "129 - 95",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 34
    },
    {
        "question": "329 - 7",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 322
    },
    {
        "question": "296 - 97",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 199
    },
    {
        "question": "256 - 63",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 193
    },
    {
        "question": "334 + 61",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 395
    },
    {
        "question": "15 + 79",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 94
    },
    {
        "question": "73 - 91",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -18
    },
    {
        "question": "82 - 33",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 49
    },
    {
        "question": "329 + 75",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 404
    },
    {
        "question": "125 x 17",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 2125
    },
    {
        "question": "67 x 37",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 2479
    },
    {
        "question": "105 - 59",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 46
    },
    {
        "question": "14 x 1",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 14
    },
    {
        "question": "363 x 9",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 3267
    },
    {
        "question": "278 - 63",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 215
    },
    {
        "question": "136 - 35",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 101
    },
    {
        "question": "27 - 19",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 8
    },
    {
        "question": "77 - 69",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 8
    },
    {
        "question": "350 x 91",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 31850
    },
    {
        "question": "130 + 45",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 175
    },
    {
        "question": "340 + 53",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 393
    },
    {
        "question": "328 x 45",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 14760
    },
    {
        "question": "391 - 13",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 378
    },
    {
        "question": "373 - 65",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 308
    },
    {
        "question": "221 + 57",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 278
    },
    {
        "question": "112 - 87",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 25
    },
    {
        "question": "90 x 35",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 3150
    },
    {
        "question": "105 x 13",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1365
    },
    {
        "question": "207 x 65",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 13455
    },
    {
        "question": "332 - 45",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 287
    },
    {
        "question": "71 + 17",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 88
    },
    {
        "question": "177 x 53",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 9381
    },
    {
        "question": "290 x 61",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 17690
    },
    {
        "question": "77 + 7",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 84
    },
    {
        "question": "10 x 57",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 570
    },
    {
        "question": "377 + 91",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 468
    },
    {
        "question": "237 x 3",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 711
    },
    {
        "question": "292 - 39",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 253
    },
    {
        "question": "128 x 23",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 2944
    },
    {
        "question": "102 - 11",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 91
    },
    {
        "question": "143 - 43",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 100
    },
    {
        "question": "40 x 85",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 3400
    },
    {
        "question": "369 + 89",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 458
    },
    {
        "question": "337 - 73",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 264
    },
    {
        "question": "72 x 77",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 5544
    },
    {
        "question": "226 x 69",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 15594
    },
    {
        "question": "71 - 93",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -22
    },
    {
        "question": "301 - 9",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 292
    },
    {
        "question": "201 + 91",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 292
    },
    {
        "question": "79 x 87",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 6873
    },
    {
        "question": "256 - 9",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 247
    },
    {
        "question": "162 x 83",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 13446
    },
    {
        "question": "394 x 55",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 21670
    },
    {
        "question": "310 - 43",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 267
    },
    {
        "question": "97 x 51",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 4947
    },
    {
        "question": "87 x 15",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1305
    },
    {
        "question": "315 x 87",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 27405
    },
    {
        "question": "341 + 95",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 436
    },
    {
        "question": "15 + 31",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 46
    },
    {
        "question": "26 x 49",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1274
    },
    {
        "question": "238 + 21",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 259
    },
    {
        "question": "395 - 99",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 296
    },
    {
        "question": "127 + 17",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 144
    },
    {
        "question": "284 - 27",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 257
    },
    {
        "question": "142 + 65",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 207
    },
    {
        "question": "89 + 37",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 126
    },
    {
        "question": "148 + 29",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 177
    },
    {
        "question": "288 x 13",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 3744
    },
    {
        "question": "139 + 21",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 160
    },
    {
        "question": "356 - 25",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 331
    },
    {
        "question": "371 + 69",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 440
    },
    {
        "question": "19 - 29",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -10
    },
    {
        "question": "114 + 81",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 195
    },
    {
        "question": "235 - 45",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 190
    },
    {
        "question": "372 + 11",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 383
    },
    {
        "question": "281 - 59",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 222
    },
    {
        "question": "298 - 15",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 283
    },
    {
        "question": "277 x 91",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 25207
    },
    {
        "question": "203 x 99",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 20097
    },
    {
        "question": "136 + 29",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 165
    },
    {
        "question": "270 x 99",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 26730
    },
    {
        "question": "334 + 1",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 335
    },
    {
        "question": "11 + 7",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 18
    },
    {
        "question": "37 x 55",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 2035
    },
    {
        "question": "264 x 9",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 2376
    },
    {
        "question": "294 + 97",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 391
    },
    {
        "question": "146 + 55",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 201
    },
    {
        "question": "172 + 1",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 173
    },
    {
        "question": "182 - 27",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 155
    },
    {
        "question": "12 + 81",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 93
    },
    {
        "question": "39 x 53",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 2067
    },
    {
        "question": "176 + 29",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 205
    },
    {
        "question": "183 x 19",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 3477
    },
    {
        "question": "343 x 11",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 3773
    },
    {
        "question": "174 x 9",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1566
    },
    {
        "question": "136 - 43",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 93
    },
    {
        "question": "390 - 61",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 329
    },
    {
        "question": "135 - 19",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 116
    },
    {
        "question": "165 x 49",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 8085
    },
    {
        "question": "8 - 79",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -71
    },
    {
        "question": "298 x 93",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 27714
    },
    {
        "question": "54 x 89",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 4806
    },
    {
        "question": "385 x 13",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 5005
    },
    {
        "question": "281 + 67",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 348
    },
    {
        "question": "253 - 63",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 190
    },
    {
        "question": "117 + 11",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 128
    },
    {
        "question": "394 x 65",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 25610
    },
    {
        "question": "280 + 65",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 345
    },
    {
        "question": "332 x 53",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 17596
    },
    {
        "question": "247 + 29",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 276
    },
    {
        "question": "364 x 61",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 22204
    },
    {
        "question": "54 + 1",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 55
    },
    {
        "question": "340 + 87",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 427
    },
    {
        "question": "24 + 75",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 99
    },
    {
        "question": "145 + 37",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 182
    },
    {
        "question": "103 x 67",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 6901
    },
    {
        "question": "117 x 19",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 2223
    },
    {
        "question": "167 + 41",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 208
    },
    {
        "question": "355 + 25",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 380
    },
    {
        "question": "127 - 15",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 112
    },
    {
        "question": "174 - 81",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 93
    },
    {
        "question": "125 - 25",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 100
    },
    {
        "question": "159 x 31",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 4929
    },
    {
        "question": "303 + 61",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 364
    },
    {
        "question": "346 + 25",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 371
    },
    {
        "question": "206 - 37",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 169
    },
    {
        "question": "343 + 93",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 436
    },
    {
        "question": "122 - 27",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 95
    },
    {
        "question": "91 x 1",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 91
    },
    {
        "question": "68 x 17",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1156
    },
    {
        "question": "147 + 27",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 174
    },
    {
        "question": "111 - 59",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 52
    },
    {
        "question": "49 + 49",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 98
    },
    {
        "question": "372 + 21",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 393
    },
    {
        "question": "251 + 63",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 314
    },
    {
        "question": "315 - 39",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 276
    },
    {
        "question": "290 - 19",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 271
    },
    {
        "question": "148 - 35",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 113
    },
    {
        "question": "385 + 55",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 440
    },
    {
        "question": "383 - 89",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 294
    },
    {
        "question": "119 + 85",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 204
    },
    {
        "question": "108 x 75",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 8100
    },
    {
        "question": "374 + 61",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 435
    },
    {
        "question": "392 + 51",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 443
    },
    {
        "question": "222 - 53",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 169
    },
    {
        "question": "239 - 63",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 176
    },
    {
        "question": "68 + 45",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 113
    },
    {
        "question": "52 - 49",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 3
    },
    {
        "question": "254 + 89",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 343
    },
    {
        "question": "338 + 97",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 435
    },
    {
        "question": "222 + 87",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 309
    },
    {
        "question": "231 x 79",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 18249
    },
    {
        "question": "381 - 69",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 312
    },
    {
        "question": "347 x 37",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 12839
    },
    {
        "question": "78 + 31",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 109
    },
    {
        "question": "369 x 55",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 20295
    },
    {
        "question": "337 + 81",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 418
    },
    {
        "question": "67 x 35",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 2345
    },
    {
        "question": "148 x 43",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 6364
    },
    {
        "question": "131 - 67",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 64
    },
    {
        "question": "132 + 1",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 133
    },
    {
        "question": "75 - 79",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -4
    },
    {
        "question": "335 x 11",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 3685
    },
    {
        "question": "206 + 37",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 243
    },
    {
        "question": "296 - 73",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 223
    },
    {
        "question": "19 x 71",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1349
    },
    {
        "question": "277 - 89",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 188
    },
    {
        "question": "287 - 37",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 250
    },
    {
        "question": "136 x 69",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 9384
    },
    {
        "question": "200 + 69",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 269
    },
    {
        "question": "280 - 1",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 279
    },
    {
        "question": "65 - 77",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -12
    },
    {
        "question": "178 x 95",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 16910
    },
    {
        "question": "261 - 29",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 232
    },
    {
        "question": "383 - 57",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 326
    },
    {
        "question": "78 + 73",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 151
    },
    {
        "question": "53 - 5",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 48
    },
    {
        "question": "325 x 93",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 30225
    },
    {
        "question": "266 + 79",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 345
    },
    {
        "question": "175 x 39",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 6825
    },
    {
        "question": "30 + 1",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 31
    },
    {
        "question": "372 x 91",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 33852
    },
    {
        "question": "384 - 99",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 285
    },
    {
        "question": "165 x 41",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 6765
    },
    {
        "question": "192 + 1",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 193
    },
    {
        "question": "310 - 47",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 263
    },
    {
        "question": "295 + 79",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 374
    },
    {
        "question": "325 + 77",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 402
    },
    {
        "question": "293 - 29",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 264
    },
    {
        "question": "127 x 37",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 4699
    },
    {
        "question": "41 x 35",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1435
    },
    {
        "question": "399 - 33",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 366
    },
    {
        "question": "3 x 21",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 63
    },
    {
        "question": "148 x 51",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 7548
    },
    {
        "question": "30 + 17",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 47
    },
    {
        "question": "41 x 33",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1353
    },
    {
        "question": "120 - 13",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 107
    },
    {
        "question": "87 + 11",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 98
    },
    {
        "question": "340 - 9",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 331
    },
    {
        "question": "88 + 3",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 91
    },
    {
        "question": "397 - 47",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 350
    },
    {
        "question": "399 - 85",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 314
    },
    {
        "question": "273 + 87",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 360
    },
    {
        "question": "342 - 87",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 255
    },
    {
        "question": "148 + 99",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 247
    },
    {
        "question": "147 + 69",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 216
    },
    {
        "question": "376 + 47",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 423
    },
    {
        "question": "256 - 53",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 203
    },
    {
        "question": "154 + 79",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 233
    },
    {
        "question": "183 - 79",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 104
    },
    {
        "question": "380 + 49",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 429
    },
    {
        "question": "253 x 55",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 13915
    },
    {
        "question": "371 - 99",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 272
    },
    {
        "question": "341 - 79",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 262
    },
    {
        "question": "193 + 69",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 262
    },
    {
        "question": "283 - 79",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 204
    },
    {
        "question": "121 x 27",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 3267
    },
    {
        "question": "13 x 11",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 143
    },
    {
        "question": "167 - 47",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 120
    },
    {
        "question": "72 - 51",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 21
    },
    {
        "question": "214 - 99",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 115
    },
    {
        "question": "373 x 49",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 18277
    },
    {
        "question": "77 x 51",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 3927
    },
    {
        "question": "5 - 69",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -64
    },
    {
        "question": "175 x 95",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 16625
    },
    {
        "question": "18 + 57",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 75
    },
    {
        "question": "326 - 35",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 291
    },
    {
        "question": "101 x 73",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 7373
    },
    {
        "question": "324 + 99",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 423
    },
    {
        "question": "357 x 7",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 2499
    },
    {
        "question": "207 + 29",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 236
    },
    {
        "question": "321 - 43",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 278
    },
    {
        "question": "48 x 83",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 3984
    },
    {
        "question": "319 - 67",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 252
    },
    {
        "question": "344 + 39",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 383
    },
    {
        "question": "330 + 65",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 395
    },
    {
        "question": "328 - 97",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 231
    },
    {
        "question": "172 x 81",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 13932
    },
    {
        "question": "185 + 53",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 238
    },
    {
        "question": "344 x 25",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 8600
    },
    {
        "question": "229 - 15",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 214
    },
    {
        "question": "125 - 79",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 46
    },
    {
        "question": "95 + 21",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 116
    },
    {
        "question": "282 + 31",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 313
    },
    {
        "question": "103 x 15",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1545
    },
    {
        "question": "332 + 51",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 383
    },
    {
        "question": "225 + 47",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 272
    },
    {
        "question": "322 x 35",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 11270
    },
    {
        "question": "15 - 5",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 10
    },
    {
        "question": "382 - 87",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 295
    },
    {
        "question": "229 - 55",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 174
    },
    {
        "question": "234 - 97",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 137
    },
    {
        "question": "45 + 1",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 46
    },
    {
        "question": "136 x 21",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 2856
    },
    {
        "question": "243 x 9",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 2187
    },
    {
        "question": "356 - 39",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 317
    },
    {
        "question": "139 x 89",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 12371
    },
    {
        "question": "91 - 65",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 26
    },
    {
        "question": "227 + 15",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 242
    },
    {
        "question": "205 + 73",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 278
    },
    {
        "question": "134 + 5",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 139
    },
    {
        "question": "2 + 35",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 37
    },
    {
        "question": "293 - 65",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 228
    },
    {
        "question": "105 x 29",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 3045
    },
    {
        "question": "12 x 31",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 372
    },
    {
        "question": "178 - 43",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 135
    },
    {
        "question": "335 x 35",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 11725
    },
    {
        "question": "287 x 79",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 22673
    },
    {
        "question": "27 x 27",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 729
    },
    {
        "question": "307 x 65",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 19955
    },
    {
        "question": "343 x 89",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 30527
    },
    {
        "question": "129 + 59",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 188
    },
    {
        "question": "270 - 41",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 229
    },
    {
        "question": "174 - 13",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 161
    },
    {
        "question": "155 x 39",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 6045
    },
    {
        "question": "68 x 29",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1972
    },
    {
        "question": "300 - 91",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 209
    },
    {
        "question": "121 x 11",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1331
    },
    {
        "question": "365 + 33",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 398
    },
    {
        "question": "291 - 21",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 270
    },
    {
        "question": "150 + 55",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 205
    },
    {
        "question": "376 - 59",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 317
    },
    {
        "question": "270 x 67",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 18090
    },
    {
        "question": "23 - 93",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -70
    },
    {
        "question": "280 + 73",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 353
    },
    {
        "question": "39 x 67",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 2613
    },
    {
        "question": "92 + 97",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 189
    },
    {
        "question": "238 - 67",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 171
    },
    {
        "question": "391 + 59",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 450
    },
    {
        "question": "369 x 35",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 12915
    },
    {
        "question": "244 x 81",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 19764
    },
    {
        "question": "223 - 67",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 156
    },
    {
        "question": "107 x 45",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 4815
    },
    {
        "question": "125 x 7",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 875
    },
    {
        "question": "13 x 69",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 897
    },
    {
        "question": "62 x 35",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 2170
    },
    {
        "question": "306 - 25",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 281
    },
    {
        "question": "277 x 11",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 3047
    },
    {
        "question": "43 x 17",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 731
    },
    {
        "question": "246 x 29",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 7134
    },
    {
        "question": "255 - 11",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 244
    },
    {
        "question": "104 x 31",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 3224
    },
    {
        "question": "381 - 9",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 372
    },
    {
        "question": "223 + 57",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 280
    },
    {
        "question": "227 - 95",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 132
    },
    {
        "question": "338 x 39",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 13182
    },
    {
        "question": "165 + 45",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 210
    },
    {
        "question": "359 x 49",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 17591
    },
    {
        "question": "282 - 35",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 247
    },
    {
        "question": "298 + 15",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 313
    },
    {
        "question": "91 - 33",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 58
    },
    {
        "question": "57 + 51",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 108
    },
    {
        "question": "237 - 55",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 182
    },
    {
        "question": "175 - 69",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 106
    },
    {
        "question": "158 x 41",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 6478
    },
    {
        "question": "179 x 65",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 11635
    },
    {
        "question": "159 + 85",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 244
    },
    {
        "question": "335 - 21",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 314
    },
    {
        "question": "181 x 5",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 905
    },
    {
        "question": "39 + 63",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 102
    },
    {
        "question": "363 x 65",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 23595
    },
    {
        "question": "360 + 79",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 439
    },
    {
        "question": "96 - 35",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 61
    },
    {
        "question": "111 x 99",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 10989
    },
    {
        "question": "90 x 11",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 990
    },
    {
        "question": "95 x 55",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 5225
    },
    {
        "question": "277 - 81",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 196
    },
    {
        "question": "311 + 75",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 386
    },
    {
        "question": "124 + 21",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 145
    },
    {
        "question": "361 + 9",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 370
    },
    {
        "question": "92 x 85",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 7820
    },
    {
        "question": "304 x 91",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 27664
    },
    {
        "question": "325 x 67",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 21775
    },
    {
        "question": "301 + 19",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 320
    },
    {
        "question": "322 - 63",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 259
    },
    {
        "question": "311 x 13",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 4043
    },
    {
        "question": "304 + 59",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 363
    },
    {
        "question": "124 - 35",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 89
    },
    {
        "question": "304 x 15",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 4560
    },
    {
        "question": "199 x 69",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 13731
    },
    {
        "question": "132 x 63",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 8316
    },
    {
        "question": "239 + 23",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 262
    },
    {
        "question": "253 + 21",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 274
    },
    {
        "question": "327 + 85",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 412
    },
    {
        "question": "302 x 1",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 302
    },
    {
        "question": "61 x 35",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 2135
    },
    {
        "question": "117 + 33",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 150
    },
    {
        "question": "201 + 97",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 298
    },
    {
        "question": "45 x 77",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 3465
    },
    {
        "question": "384 x 93",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 35712
    },
    {
        "question": "199 x 81",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 16119
    },
    {
        "question": "204 - 59",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 145
    },
    {
        "question": "174 x 81",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 14094
    },
    {
        "question": "110 - 9",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 101
    },
    {
        "question": "151 x 73",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 11023
    },
    {
        "question": "66 + 91",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 157
    },
    {
        "question": "295 - 55",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 240
    },
    {
        "question": "366 - 91",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 275
    },
    {
        "question": "331 + 99",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 430
    },
    {
        "question": "94 x 67",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 6298
    },
    {
        "question": "340 + 81",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 421
    },
    {
        "question": "39 x 37",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1443
    },
    {
        "question": "384 + 1",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 385
    },
    {
        "question": "6 + 45",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 51
    },
    {
        "question": "279 - 35",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 244
    },
    {
        "question": "398 - 3",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 395
    },
    {
        "question": "347 x 13",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 4511
    },
    {
        "question": "12 - 73",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -61
    },
    {
        "question": "277 + 83",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 360
    },
    {
        "question": "276 + 23",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 299
    },
    {
        "question": "246 + 81",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 327
    },
    {
        "question": "130 x 51",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 6630
    },
    {
        "question": "206 - 29",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 177
    },
    {
        "question": "62 x 85",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 5270
    },
    {
        "question": "68 - 73",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -5
    },
    {
        "question": "314 - 69",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 245
    },
    {
        "question": "293 + 31",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 324
    },
    {
        "question": "211 x 5",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1055
    },
    {
        "question": "284 + 13",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 297
    },
    {
        "question": "274 + 53",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 327
    },
    {
        "question": "130 - 23",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 107
    },
    {
        "question": "41 + 39",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 80
    },
    {
        "question": "209 x 3",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 627
    },
    {
        "question": "254 + 11",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 265
    },
    {
        "question": "150 + 85",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 235
    },
    {
        "question": "158 - 65",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 93
    },
    {
        "question": "12 x 99",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1188
    },
    {
        "question": "173 - 89",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 84
    },
    {
        "question": "228 + 27",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 255
    },
    {
        "question": "195 + 45",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 240
    },
    {
        "question": "260 - 45",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 215
    },
    {
        "question": "365 x 69",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 25185
    },
    {
        "question": "9 - 61",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -52
    },
    {
        "question": "205 x 65",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 13325
    },
    {
        "question": "111 + 51",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 162
    },
    {
        "question": "374 + 67",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 441
    },
    {
        "question": "2 - 53",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -51
    },
    {
        "question": "47 + 55",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 102
    },
    {
        "question": "186 + 59",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 245
    },
    {
        "question": "379 - 13",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 366
    },
    {
        "question": "200 + 45",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 245
    },
    {
        "question": "188 + 5",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 193
    },
    {
        "question": "327 + 51",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 378
    },
    {
        "question": "101 x 97",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 9797
    },
    {
        "question": "80 + 39",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 119
    },
    {
        "question": "231 - 25",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 206
    },
    {
        "question": "165 x 49",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 8085
    },
    {
        "question": "315 x 79",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 24885
    },
    {
        "question": "116 + 99",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 215
    },
    {
        "question": "316 - 75",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 241
    },
    {
        "question": "348 x 65",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 22620
    },
    {
        "question": "201 x 99",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 19899
    },
    {
        "question": "131 x 55",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 7205
    },
    {
        "question": "351 - 61",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 290
    },
    {
        "question": "80 x 33",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 2640
    },
    {
        "question": "80 x 67",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 5360
    },
    {
        "question": "58 + 69",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 127
    },
    {
        "question": "389 - 7",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 382
    },
    {
        "question": "283 - 69",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 214
    },
    {
        "question": "263 x 59",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 15517
    },
    {
        "question": "316 + 11",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 327
    },
    {
        "question": "232 + 77",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 309
    },
    {
        "question": "14 + 67",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 81
    },
    {
        "question": "59 - 67",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -8
    },
    {
        "question": "104 + 21",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 125
    },
    {
        "question": "56 - 91",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -35
    },
    {
        "question": "22 - 17",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 5
    },
    {
        "question": "241 x 49",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 11809
    },
    {
        "question": "5 + 1",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 6
    },
    {
        "question": "395 - 45",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 350
    },
    {
        "question": "160 - 69",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 91
    },
    {
        "question": "336 x 63",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 21168
    },
    {
        "question": "264 + 25",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 289
    },
    {
        "question": "89 x 49",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 4361
    },
    {
        "question": "92 + 59",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 151
    },
    {
        "question": "44 x 77",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 3388
    },
    {
        "question": "325 - 95",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 230
    },
    {
        "question": "103 + 97",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 200
    },
    {
        "question": "83 + 63",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 146
    },
    {
        "question": "262 - 83",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 179
    },
    {
        "question": "181 - 47",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 134
    },
    {
        "question": "21 x 3",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 63
    },
    {
        "question": "211 x 67",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 14137
    },
    {
        "question": "72 - 17",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 55
    },
    {
        "question": "23 - 9",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 14
    },
    {
        "question": "2 x 17",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 34
    },
    {
        "question": "329 - 27",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 302
    },
    {
        "question": "346 - 89",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 257
    },
    {
        "question": "304 + 61",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 365
    },
    {
        "question": "276 - 39",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 237
    },
    {
        "question": "93 - 83",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 10
    },
    {
        "question": "352 x 21",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 7392
    },
    {
        "question": "318 + 99",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 417
    },
    {
        "question": "214 + 25",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 239
    },
    {
        "question": "60 x 69",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 4140
    },
    {
        "question": "158 x 53",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 8374
    },
    {
        "question": "226 - 63",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 163
    },
    {
        "question": "392 + 25",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 417
    },
    {
        "question": "71 x 65",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 4615
    },
    {
        "question": "200 x 47",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 9400
    },
    {
        "question": "145 + 51",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 196
    },
    {
        "question": "353 x 53",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 18709
    },
    {
        "question": "338 - 35",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 303
    },
    {
        "question": "294 + 51",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 345
    },
    {
        "question": "299 x 95",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 28405
    },
    {
        "question": "171 + 49",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 220
    },
    {
        "question": "117 - 9",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 108
    },
    {
        "question": "64 - 81",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -17
    },
    {
        "question": "29 x 91",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 2639
    },
    {
        "question": "27 - 31",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -4
    },
    {
        "question": "83 x 47",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 3901
    },
    {
        "question": "351 x 35",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 12285
    },
    {
        "question": "97 - 79",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 18
    },
    {
        "question": "200 - 69",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 131
    },
    {
        "question": "310 x 41",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 12710
    },
    {
        "question": "57 - 29",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 28
    },
    {
        "question": "126 x 39",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 4914
    },
    {
        "question": "55 - 47",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 8
    },
    {
        "question": "279 + 47",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 326
    },
    {
        "question": "118 - 69",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 49
    },
    {
        "question": "12 - 43",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -31
    },
    {
        "question": "175 + 77",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 252
    },
    {
        "question": "201 + 61",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 262
    },
    {
        "question": "288 - 83",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 205
    },
    {
        "question": "132 + 3",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 135
    },
    {
        "question": "313 - 19",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 294
    },
    {
        "question": "231 x 41",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 9471
    },
    {
        "question": "114 - 75",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 39
    },
    {
        "question": "165 x 33",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 5445
    },
    {
        "question": "181 - 37",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 144
    },
    {
        "question": "300 x 9",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 2700
    },
    {
        "question": "243 x 53",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 12879
    },
    {
        "question": "71 + 1",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 72
    },
    {
        "question": "341 x 51",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 17391
    },
    {
        "question": "60 x 89",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 5340
    },
    {
        "question": "14 + 27",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 41
    },
    {
        "question": "334 x 63",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 21042
    },
    {
        "question": "70 - 89",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -19
    },
    {
        "question": "343 x 71",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 24353
    },
    {
        "question": "102 x 19",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1938
    },
    {
        "question": "359 - 7",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 352
    },
    {
        "question": "378 x 41",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 15498
    },
    {
        "question": "188 + 59",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 247
    },
    {
        "question": "155 x 49",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 7595
    },
    {
        "question": "374 + 55",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 429
    },
    {
        "question": "134 x 23",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 3082
    },
    {
        "question": "244 x 93",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 22692
    },
    {
        "question": "240 x 55",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 13200
    },
    {
        "question": "46 + 47",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 93
    },
    {
        "question": "319 + 69",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 388
    },
    {
        "question": "23 + 77",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 100
    },
    {
        "question": "282 + 15",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 297
    },
    {
        "question": "314 x 25",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 7850
    },
    {
        "question": "251 + 49",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 300
    },
    {
        "question": "281 x 27",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 7587
    },
    {
        "question": "133 x 43",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 5719
    },
    {
        "question": "37 x 15",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 555
    },
    {
        "question": "359 + 73",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 432
    },
    {
        "question": "51 x 33",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1683
    },
    {
        "question": "145 + 31",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 176
    },
    {
        "question": "125 + 47",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 172
    },
    {
        "question": "255 x 83",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 21165
    },
    {
        "question": "184 - 69",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 115
    },
    {
        "question": "197 + 17",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 214
    },
    {
        "question": "347 - 51",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 296
    },
    {
        "question": "26 + 49",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 75
    },
    {
        "question": "380 - 45",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 335
    },
    {
        "question": "140 - 27",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 113
    },
    {
        "question": "217 + 49",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 266
    },
    {
        "question": "33 x 19",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 627
    },
    {
        "question": "328 + 41",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 369
    },
    {
        "question": "50 + 27",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 77
    },
    {
        "question": "86 + 15",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 101
    },
    {
        "question": "263 - 61",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 202
    },
    {
        "question": "211 x 63",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 13293
    },
    {
        "question": "214 x 47",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 10058
    },
    {
        "question": "367 x 57",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 20919
    },
    {
        "question": "221 + 83",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 304
    },
    {
        "question": "344 x 53",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 18232
    },
    {
        "question": "306 - 63",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 243
    },
    {
        "question": "396 + 83",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 479
    },
    {
        "question": "395 x 37",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 14615
    },
    {
        "question": "371 + 67",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 438
    },
    {
        "question": "40 + 9",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 49
    },
    {
        "question": "254 - 73",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 181
    },
    {
        "question": "87 - 19",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 68
    },
    {
        "question": "365 x 91",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 33215
    },
    {
        "question": "45 + 41",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 86
    },
    {
        "question": "67 x 23",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1541
    },
    {
        "question": "73 + 49",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 122
    },
    {
        "question": "94 + 39",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 133
    },
    {
        "question": "335 x 89",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 29815
    },
    {
        "question": "274 x 85",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 23290
    },
    {
        "question": "63 x 93",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 5859
    },
    {
        "question": "300 + 29",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 329
    },
    {
        "question": "38 + 89",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 127
    },
    {
        "question": "69 - 67",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "13 x 37",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 481
    },
    {
        "question": "89 x 13",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1157
    },
    {
        "question": "122 + 47",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 169
    },
    {
        "question": "169 + 69",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 238
    },
    {
        "question": "15 x 39",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 585
    },
    {
        "question": "243 - 33",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 210
    },
    {
        "question": "261 - 89",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 172
    },
    {
        "question": "83 x 81",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 6723
    },
    {
        "question": "50 + 7",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 57
    },
    {
        "question": "71 - 21",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 50
    },
    {
        "question": "4 - 83",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -79
    },
    {
        "question": "278 x 5",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1390
    },
    {
        "question": "294 x 1",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 294
    },
    {
        "question": "357 x 27",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 9639
    },
    {
        "question": "73 x 35",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 2555
    },
    {
        "question": "73 - 43",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 30
    },
    {
        "question": "324 x 63",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 20412
    },
    {
        "question": "354 - 9",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 345
    },
    {
        "question": "141 - 67",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 74
    },
    {
        "question": "44 - 63",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -19
    },
    {
        "question": "167 - 73",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 94
    },
    {
        "question": "242 + 19",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 261
    },
    {
        "question": "395 - 27",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 368
    },
    {
        "question": "91 x 53",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 4823
    },
    {
        "question": "215 - 23",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 192
    },
    {
        "question": "315 - 27",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 288
    },
    {
        "question": "206 + 15",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 221
    },
    {
        "question": "361 x 79",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 28519
    },
    {
        "question": "267 + 29",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 296
    },
    {
        "question": "42 + 1",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 43
    },
    {
        "question": "219 - 57",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 162
    },
    {
        "question": "185 + 73",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 258
    },
    {
        "question": "16 - 5",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 11
    },
    {
        "question": "361 - 61",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 300
    },
    {
        "question": "344 - 59",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 285
    },
    {
        "question": "259 + 79",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 338
    },
    {
        "question": "341 - 3",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 338
    },
    {
        "question": "248 x 55",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 13640
    },
    {
        "question": "241 x 77",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 18557
    },
    {
        "question": "254 - 89",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 165
    },
    {
        "question": "289 x 59",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 17051
    },
    {
        "question": "263 + 7",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 270
    },
    {
        "question": "112 x 89",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 9968
    },
    {
        "question": "118 + 95",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 213
    },
    {
        "question": "153 x 35",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 5355
    },
    {
        "question": "264 + 13",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 277
    },
    {
        "question": "104 + 69",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 173
    },
    {
        "question": "99 x 39",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 3861
    },
    {
        "question": "157 + 79",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 236
    },
    {
        "question": "222 + 75",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 297
    },
    {
        "question": "31 x 15",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 465
    },
    {
        "question": "363 - 87",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 276
    },
    {
        "question": "346 x 51",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 17646
    },
    {
        "question": "18 x 85",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1530
    },
    {
        "question": "118 - 33",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 85
    },
    {
        "question": "155 + 17",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 172
    },
    {
        "question": "114 x 73",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 8322
    },
    {
        "question": "176 + 67",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 243
    },
    {
        "question": "26 + 33",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 59
    },
    {
        "question": "289 + 67",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 356
    },
    {
        "question": "9 x 33",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 297
    },
    {
        "question": "396 - 73",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 323
    },
    {
        "question": "66 - 49",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 17
    },
    {
        "question": "63 + 67",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 130
    },
    {
        "question": "148 x 97",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 14356
    },
    {
        "question": "149 - 33",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 116
    },
    {
        "question": "210 x 37",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 7770
    },
    {
        "question": "393 + 9",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 402
    },
    {
        "question": "12 x 51",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 612
    },
    {
        "question": "269 + 59",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 328
    },
    {
        "question": "113 x 53",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 5989
    },
    {
        "question": "301 x 43",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 12943
    },
    {
        "question": "133 + 41",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 174
    },
    {
        "question": "347 x 77",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 26719
    },
    {
        "question": "216 + 91",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 307
    },
    {
        "question": "151 + 61",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 212
    },
    {
        "question": "40 - 43",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -3
    },
    {
        "question": "78 - 81",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -3
    },
    {
        "question": "134 - 7",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 127
    },
    {
        "question": "182 x 21",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 3822
    },
    {
        "question": "52 x 77",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 4004
    },
    {
        "question": "137 + 43",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 180
    },
    {
        "question": "84 x 39",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 3276
    },
    {
        "question": "176 + 59",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 235
    },
    {
        "question": "29 x 35",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1015
    },
    {
        "question": "38 - 43",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -5
    },
    {
        "question": "119 - 45",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 74
    },
    {
        "question": "295 x 79",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 23305
    },
    {
        "question": "174 - 5",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 169
    },
    {
        "question": "122 + 39",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 161
    },
    {
        "question": "173 - 37",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 136
    },
    {
        "question": "389 + 41",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 430
    },
    {
        "question": "207 x 51",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 10557
    },
    {
        "question": "87 x 89",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 7743
    },
    {
        "question": "172 x 91",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 15652
    },
    {
        "question": "255 - 19",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 236
    },
    {
        "question": "397 + 7",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 404
    },
    {
        "question": "188 + 41",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 229
    },
    {
        "question": "96 + 51",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 147
    },
    {
        "question": "263 + 51",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 314
    },
    {
        "question": "284 - 49",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 235
    },
    {
        "question": "185 + 73",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 258
    },
    {
        "question": "390 + 43",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 433
    },
    {
        "question": "24 + 63",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 87
    },
    {
        "question": "318 - 65",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 253
    },
    {
        "question": "306 + 43",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 349
    },
    {
        "question": "166 x 83",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 13778
    },
    {
        "question": "303 + 57",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 360
    },
    {
        "question": "250 + 59",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 309
    },
    {
        "question": "102 x 9",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 918
    },
    {
        "question": "84 + 45",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 129
    },
    {
        "question": "375 x 93",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 34875
    },
    {
        "question": "204 x 31",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 6324
    },
    {
        "question": "221 - 41",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 180
    },
    {
        "question": "7 - 93",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -86
    },
    {
        "question": "90 + 9",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 99
    },
    {
        "question": "98 + 1",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 99
    },
    {
        "question": "93 x 45",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 4185
    },
    {
        "question": "65 x 43",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 2795
    },
    {
        "question": "75 - 39",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 36
    },
    {
        "question": "2 + 41",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 43
    },
    {
        "question": "21 x 3",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 63
    },
    {
        "question": "24 - 5",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 19
    },
    {
        "question": "20 - 39",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -19
    },
    {
        "question": "28 x 31",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 868
    },
    {
        "question": "58 x 21",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1218
    },
    {
        "question": "78 + 21",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 99
    },
    {
        "question": "76 x 25",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1900
    },
    {
        "question": "76 + 43",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 119
    },
    {
        "question": "60 + 5",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 65
    },
    {
        "question": "37 + 33",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 70
    },
    {
        "question": "65 + 33",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 98
    },
    {
        "question": "67 x 11",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 737
    },
    {
        "question": "25 + 7",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 32
    },
    {
        "question": "85 x 23",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1955
    },
    {
        "question": "63 - 19",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 44
    },
    {
        "question": "35 x 3",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 105
    },
    {
        "question": "53 + 47",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 100
    },
    {
        "question": "87 + 23",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 110
    },
    {
        "question": "78 x 37",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 2886
    },
    {
        "question": "44 x 33",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1452
    },
    {
        "question": "65 - 47",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 18
    },
    {
        "question": "8 x 5",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 40
    },
    {
        "question": "64 + 47",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 111
    },
    {
        "question": "97 x 33",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 3201
    },
    {
        "question": "89 + 7",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 96
    },
    {
        "question": "21 x 13",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 273
    },
    {
        "question": "22 - 21",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "68 + 17",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 85
    },
    {
        "question": "9 + 23",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 32
    },
    {
        "question": "32 - 17",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 15
    },
    {
        "question": "21 x 39",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 819
    },
    {
        "question": "26 x 25",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 650
    },
    {
        "question": "10 - 9",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "89 - 35",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 54
    },
    {
        "question": "85 x 39",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 3315
    },
    {
        "question": "31 x 37",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1147
    },
    {
        "question": "86 + 1",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 87
    },
    {
        "question": "95 - 11",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 84
    },
    {
        "question": "19 x 41",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 779
    },
    {
        "question": "83 + 47",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 130
    },
    {
        "question": "15 x 5",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 75
    },
    {
        "question": "89 - 31",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 58
    },
    {
        "question": "69 - 45",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 24
    },
    {
        "question": "50 x 19",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 950
    },
    {
        "question": "64 + 3",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 67
    },
    {
        "question": "16 x 7",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 112
    },
    {
        "question": "1 + 45",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 46
    },
    {
        "question": "61 + 31",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 92
    },
    {
        "question": "46 x 37",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1702
    },
    {
        "question": "80 + 29",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 109
    },
    {
        "question": "87 + 45",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 132
    },
    {
        "question": "54 - 15",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 39
    },
    {
        "question": "52 x 1",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 52
    },
    {
        "question": "83 - 41",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 42
    },
    {
        "question": "26 + 37",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 63
    },
    {
        "question": "79 x 21",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1659
    },
    {
        "question": "57 - 35",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 22
    },
    {
        "question": "55 - 25",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 30
    },
    {
        "question": "93 x 17",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1581
    },
    {
        "question": "1 - 41",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -40
    },
    {
        "question": "10 x 45",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 450
    },
    {
        "question": "52 - 35",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 17
    },
    {
        "question": "61 - 27",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 34
    },
    {
        "question": "98 + 23",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 121
    },
    {
        "question": "54 - 37",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 17
    },
    {
        "question": "79 x 1",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 79
    },
    {
        "question": "60 - 43",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 17
    },
    {
        "question": "67 x 45",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 3015
    },
    {
        "question": "82 - 25",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 57
    },
    {
        "question": "95 - 7",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 88
    },
    {
        "question": "40 + 33",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 73
    },
    {
        "question": "56 - 47",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 9
    },
    {
        "question": "7 + 17",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 24
    },
    {
        "question": "46 + 29",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 75
    },
    {
        "question": "60 - 47",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 13
    },
    {
        "question": "24 + 3",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 27
    },
    {
        "question": "35 + 39",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 74
    },
    {
        "question": "66 - 23",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 43
    },
    {
        "question": "33 x 9",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 297
    },
    {
        "question": "99 x 11",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1089
    },
    {
        "question": "35 - 27",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 8
    },
    {
        "question": "87 + 7",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 94
    },
    {
        "question": "53 x 25",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1325
    },
    {
        "question": "64 - 15",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 49
    },
    {
        "question": "4 + 21",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 25
    },
    {
        "question": "53 + 31",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 84
    },
    {
        "question": "30 + 17",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 47
    },
    {
        "question": "88 x 15",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1320
    },
    {
        "question": "81 - 31",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 50
    },
    {
        "question": "8 - 37",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -29
    },
    {
        "question": "41 + 19",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 60
    },
    {
        "question": "41 x 43",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1763
    },
    {
        "question": "42 x 3",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 126
    },
    {
        "question": "63 + 29",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 92
    },
    {
        "question": "307 + 7",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 314
    },
    {
        "question": "163 - 21",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 142
    },
    {
        "question": "307 x 91",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 27937
    },
    {
        "question": "387 x 83",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 32121
    },
    {
        "question": "324 + 13",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 337
    },
    {
        "question": "282 + 87",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 369
    },
    {
        "question": "114 x 29",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 3306
    },
    {
        "question": "243 - 47",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 196
    },
    {
        "question": "310 x 99",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 30690
    },
    {
        "question": "173 - 95",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 78
    },
    {
        "question": "45 x 87",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 3915
    },
    {
        "question": "125 + 55",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 180
    },
    {
        "question": "271 - 57",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 214
    },
    {
        "question": "179 + 33",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 212
    },
    {
        "question": "227 - 5",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 222
    },
    {
        "question": "60 - 17",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 43
    },
    {
        "question": "398 x 99",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 39402
    },
    {
        "question": "58 x 1",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 58
    },
    {
        "question": "56 - 93",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -37
    },
    {
        "question": "393 x 3",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1179
    },
    {
        "question": "228 - 47",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 181
    },
    {
        "question": "277 - 95",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 182
    },
    {
        "question": "167 - 33",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 134
    },
    {
        "question": "185 + 47",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 232
    },
    {
        "question": "163 - 9",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 154
    },
    {
        "question": "390 - 67",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 323
    },
    {
        "question": "79 - 23",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 56
    },
    {
        "question": "248 - 23",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 225
    },
    {
        "question": "225 - 41",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 184
    },
    {
        "question": "124 x 77",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 9548
    },
    {
        "question": "372 - 89",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 283
    },
    {
        "question": "300 - 3",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 297
    },
    {
        "question": "240 x 93",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 22320
    },
    {
        "question": "18 x 7",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 126
    },
    {
        "question": "249 + 67",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 316
    },
    {
        "question": "178 - 99",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 79
    },
    {
        "question": "326 + 83",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 409
    },
    {
        "question": "189 + 79",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 268
    },
    {
        "question": "195 + 59",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 254
    },
    {
        "question": "212 - 55",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 157
    },
    {
        "question": "99 + 99",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 198
    },
    {
        "question": "66 + 49",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 115
    },
    {
        "question": "139 + 89",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 228
    },
    {
        "question": "147 - 87",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 60
    },
    {
        "question": "344 + 83",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 427
    },
    {
        "question": "152 - 79",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 73
    },
    {
        "question": "36 + 97",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 133
    },
    {
        "question": "321 - 61",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 260
    },
    {
        "question": "389 - 29",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 360
    },
    {
        "question": "195 - 79",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 116
    },
    {
        "question": "96 + 39",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 135
    },
    {
        "question": "152 x 39",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 5928
    },
    {
        "question": "396 x 19",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 7524
    },
    {
        "question": "377 + 79",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 456
    },
    {
        "question": "141 - 31",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 110
    },
    {
        "question": "70 + 5",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 75
    },
    {
        "question": "391 - 75",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 316
    },
    {
        "question": "365 x 43",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 15695
    },
    {
        "question": "249 x 31",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 7719
    },
    {
        "question": "90 + 37",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 127
    },
    {
        "question": "82 - 63",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 19
    },
    {
        "question": "288 + 63",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 351
    },
    {
        "question": "383 - 31",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 352
    },
    {
        "question": "383 + 43",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 426
    },
    {
        "question": "200 + 85",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 285
    },
    {
        "question": "229 + 73",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 302
    },
    {
        "question": "383 + 19",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 402
    },
    {
        "question": "323 + 57",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 380
    },
    {
        "question": "308 x 85",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 26180
    },
    {
        "question": "102 + 25",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 127
    },
    {
        "question": "214 + 61",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 275
    },
    {
        "question": "331 + 97",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 428
    },
    {
        "question": "137 + 23",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 160
    },
    {
        "question": "30 - 7",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 23
    },
    {
        "question": "71 + 73",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 144
    },
    {
        "question": "96 - 79",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 17
    },
    {
        "question": "105 + 59",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 164
    },
    {
        "question": "139 x 83",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 11537
    },
    {
        "question": "376 - 1",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 375
    },
    {
        "question": "213 + 29",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 242
    },
    {
        "question": "197 - 43",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 154
    },
    {
        "question": "153 - 31",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 122
    },
    {
        "question": "125 + 53",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 178
    },
    {
        "question": "283 - 1",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 282
    },
    {
        "question": "388 x 77",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 29876
    },
    {
        "question": "44 - 25",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 19
    },
    {
        "question": "113 - 89",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 24
    },
    {
        "question": "33 - 93",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -60
    },
    {
        "question": "388 x 83",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 32204
    },
    {
        "question": "56 x 3",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 168
    },
    {
        "question": "171 - 53",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 118
    },
    {
        "question": "169 - 9",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 160
    },
    {
        "question": "93 x 63",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 5859
    },
    {
        "question": "399 x 3",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1197
    },
    {
        "question": "142 x 7",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 994
    },
    {
        "question": "357 x 49",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 17493
    },
    {
        "question": "233 + 45",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 278
    },
    {
        "question": "219 - 7",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 212
    },
    {
        "question": "341 x 81",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 27621
    },
    {
        "question": "2 + 31",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 33
    },
    {
        "question": "335 - 79",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 256
    },
    {
        "question": "353 x 41",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 14473
    },
    {
        "question": "345 + 89",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 434
    },
    {
        "question": "3 + 11",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 14
    },
    {
        "question": "3 - 79",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -76
    },
    {
        "question": "56 - 63",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -7
    },
    {
        "question": "366 + 57",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 423
    },
    {
        "question": "221 - 83",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 138
    },
    {
        "question": "88 + 39",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 127
    },
    {
        "question": "66 + 61",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 127
    },
    {
        "question": "371 - 17",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 354
    },
    {
        "question": "352 x 51",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 17952
    },
    {
        "question": "375 x 39",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 14625
    },
    {
        "question": "204 - 93",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 111
    },
    {
        "question": "360 x 47",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 16920
    },
    {
        "question": "358 - 31",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 327
    },
    {
        "question": "320 + 97",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 417
    },
    {
        "question": "395 x 21",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 8295
    },
    {
        "question": "395 + 15",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 410
    },
    {
        "question": "37 x 41",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1517
    },
    {
        "question": "146 x 35",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 5110
    },
    {
        "question": "2 - 15",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -13
    },
    {
        "question": "4 x 1",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 4
    },
    {
        "question": "139 x 41",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 5699
    },
    {
        "question": "264 + 23",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 287
    },
    {
        "question": "77 x 83",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 6391
    },
    {
        "question": "286 x 43",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 12298
    },
    {
        "question": "104 x 73",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 7592
    },
    {
        "question": "146 - 1",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 145
    },
    {
        "question": "352 x 99",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 34848
    },
    {
        "question": "36 + 73",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 109
    },
    {
        "question": "260 x 67",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 17420
    },
    {
        "question": "283 + 99",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 382
    },
    {
        "question": "171 + 71",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 242
    },
    {
        "question": "52 x 83",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 4316
    },
    {
        "question": "305 x 67",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 20435
    },
    {
        "question": "28 - 37",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -9
    },
    {
        "question": "330 - 93",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 237
    },
    {
        "question": "329 x 85",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 27965
    },
    {
        "question": "47 x 33",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1551
    },
    {
        "question": "101 x 49",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 4949
    },
    {
        "question": "372 - 15",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 357
    },
    {
        "question": "315 - 85",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 230
    },
    {
        "question": "98 + 85",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 183
    },
    {
        "question": "99 + 73",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 172
    },
    {
        "question": "258 x 25",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 6450
    },
    {
        "question": "381 + 77",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 458
    },
    {
        "question": "107 + 55",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 162
    },
    {
        "question": "320 x 9",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 2880
    },
    {
        "question": "135 - 89",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 46
    },
    {
        "question": "190 x 51",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 9690
    },
    {
        "question": "178 + 93",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 271
    },
    {
        "question": "12 x 45",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 540
    },
    {
        "question": "157 + 43",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 200
    },
    {
        "question": "150 + 43",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 193
    },
    {
        "question": "179 - 7",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 172
    },
    {
        "question": "225 + 89",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 314
    },
    {
        "question": "323 - 79",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 244
    },
    {
        "question": "248 - 69",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 179
    },
    {
        "question": "293 - 95",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 198
    },
    {
        "question": "223 + 75",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 298
    },
    {
        "question": "380 x 87",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 33060
    },
    {
        "question": "35 - 75",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -40
    },
    {
        "question": "246 - 17",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 229
    },
    {
        "question": "237 - 79",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 158
    },
    {
        "question": "279 + 77",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 356
    },
    {
        "question": "225 - 71",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 154
    },
    {
        "question": "24 x 43",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1032
    },
    {
        "question": "114 x 67",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 7638
    },
    {
        "question": "219 x 71",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 15549
    },
    {
        "question": "72 x 77",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 5544
    },
    {
        "question": "13 x 47",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 611
    },
    {
        "question": "64 x 91",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 5824
    },
    {
        "question": "206 - 83",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 123
    },
    {
        "question": "118 - 27",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 91
    },
    {
        "question": "41 + 91",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 132
    },
    {
        "question": "397 x 89",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 35333
    },
    {
        "question": "179 x 33",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 5907
    },
    {
        "question": "312 + 19",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 331
    },
    {
        "question": "181 - 93",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 88
    },
    {
        "question": "144 - 29",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 115
    },
    {
        "question": "16 x 31",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 496
    },
    {
        "question": "303 x 33",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 9999
    },
    {
        "question": "211 + 89",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 300
    },
    {
        "question": "322 - 25",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 297
    },
    {
        "question": "59 - 83",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -24
    },
    {
        "question": "82 + 39",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 121
    },
    {
        "question": "197 + 67",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 264
    },
    {
        "question": "179 + 29",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 208
    },
    {
        "question": "342 - 63",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 279
    },
    {
        "question": "95 + 1",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 96
    },
    {
        "question": "73 + 63",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 136
    },
    {
        "question": "245 x 45",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 11025
    },
    {
        "question": "171 - 97",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 74
    },
    {
        "question": "296 - 53",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 243
    },
    {
        "question": "13 + 11",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 24
    },
    {
        "question": "266 + 49",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 315
    },
    {
        "question": "343 + 23",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 366
    },
    {
        "question": "353 + 67",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 420
    },
    {
        "question": "392 - 65",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 327
    },
    {
        "question": "275 x 91",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 25025
    },
    {
        "question": "108 - 65",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 43
    },
    {
        "question": "107 + 61",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 168
    },
    {
        "question": "109 - 11",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 98
    },
    {
        "question": "278 - 7",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 271
    },
    {
        "question": "70 + 27",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 97
    },
    {
        "question": "240 - 69",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 171
    },
    {
        "question": "374 - 53",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 321
    },
    {
        "question": "167 x 53",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 8851
    },
    {
        "question": "249 - 91",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 158
    },
    {
        "question": "195 x 79",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 15405
    },
    {
        "question": "59 x 31",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1829
    },
    {
        "question": "318 x 1",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 318
    },
    {
        "question": "308 - 75",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 233
    },
    {
        "question": "280 x 55",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 15400
    },
    {
        "question": "145 - 5",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 140
    },
    {
        "question": "286 - 65",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 221
    },
    {
        "question": "358 + 31",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 389
    },
    {
        "question": "179 + 25",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 204
    },
    {
        "question": "199 x 1",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 199
    },
    {
        "question": "311 - 45",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 266
    },
    {
        "question": "26 + 99",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 125
    },
    {
        "question": "67 x 89",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 5963
    },
    {
        "question": "46 - 41",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 5
    },
    {
        "question": "375 x 83",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 31125
    },
    {
        "question": "35 + 29",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 64
    },
    {
        "question": "69 - 93",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -24
    },
    {
        "question": "213 + 39",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 252
    },
    {
        "question": "188 x 69",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 12972
    },
    {
        "question": "271 + 55",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 326
    },
    {
        "question": "110 + 29",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 139
    },
    {
        "question": "276 - 33",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 243
    },
    {
        "question": "170 x 69",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 11730
    },
    {
        "question": "85 + 17",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 102
    },
    {
        "question": "25 x 5",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 125
    },
    {
        "question": "135 + 97",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 232
    },
    {
        "question": "270 x 55",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 14850
    },
    {
        "question": "76 x 39",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 2964
    },
    {
        "question": "11 + 59",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 70
    },
    {
        "question": "92 - 63",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 29
    },
    {
        "question": "102 x 9",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 918
    },
    {
        "question": "353 x 33",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 11649
    },
    {
        "question": "187 - 37",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 150
    },
    {
        "question": "162 x 51",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 8262
    },
    {
        "question": "77 x 75",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 5775
    },
    {
        "question": "72 + 61",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 133
    },
    {
        "question": "229 + 19",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 248
    },
    {
        "question": "266 - 63",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 203
    },
    {
        "question": "28 + 89",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 117
    },
    {
        "question": "293 + 17",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 310
    },
    {
        "question": "146 - 13",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 133
    },
    {
        "question": "197 + 1",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 198
    },
    {
        "question": "359 x 21",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 7539
    },
    {
        "question": "249 x 7",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1743
    },
    {
        "question": "299 x 85",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 25415
    },
    {
        "question": "180 + 69",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 249
    },
    {
        "question": "14 + 25",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 39
    },
    {
        "question": "207 - 67",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 140
    },
    {
        "question": "386 + 7",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 393
    },
    {
        "question": "366 x 7",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 2562
    },
    {
        "question": "220 x 31",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 6820
    },
    {
        "question": "345 x 29",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 10005
    },
    {
        "question": "136 x 67",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 9112
    },
    {
        "question": "5 + 11",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 16
    },
    {
        "question": "230 - 29",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 201
    },
    {
        "question": "85 + 89",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 174
    },
    {
        "question": "345 x 85",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 29325
    },
    {
        "question": "141 - 27",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 114
    },
    {
        "question": "148 + 35",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 183
    },
    {
        "question": "185 + 91",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 276
    },
    {
        "question": "100 + 55",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 155
    },
    {
        "question": "253 x 71",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 17963
    },
    {
        "question": "205 + 53",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 258
    },
    {
        "question": "181 - 71",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 110
    },
    {
        "question": "157 x 99",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 15543
    },
    {
        "question": "274 + 87",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 361
    },
    {
        "question": "229 - 55",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 174
    },
    {
        "question": "6 - 95",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -89
    },
    {
        "question": "388 - 95",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 293
    },
    {
        "question": "12 + 59",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 71
    },
    {
        "question": "371 + 33",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 404
    },
    {
        "question": "155 x 87",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 13485
    },
    {
        "question": "9 + 3",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 12
    },
    {
        "question": "14 - 45",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -31
    },
    {
        "question": "175 x 35",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 6125
    },
    {
        "question": "104 x 25",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 2600
    },
    {
        "question": "333 + 7",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 340
    },
    {
        "question": "53 + 71",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 124
    },
    {
        "question": "26 + 59",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 85
    },
    {
        "question": "201 - 21",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 180
    },
    {
        "question": "161 + 93",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 254
    },
    {
        "question": "5 x 87",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 435
    },
    {
        "question": "84 - 51",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 33
    },
    {
        "question": "131 x 51",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 6681
    },
    {
        "question": "162 x 57",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 9234
    },
    {
        "question": "135 + 39",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 174
    },
    {
        "question": "289 + 99",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 388
    },
    {
        "question": "9 + 59",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 68
    },
    {
        "question": "140 - 75",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 65
    },
    {
        "question": "234 + 35",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 269
    },
    {
        "question": "11 x 25",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 275
    },
    {
        "question": "66 - 37",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 29
    },
    {
        "question": "79 + 15",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 94
    },
    {
        "question": "30 x 87",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 2610
    },
    {
        "question": "42 - 1",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 41
    },
    {
        "question": "26 - 59",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -33
    },
    {
        "question": "286 - 15",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 271
    },
    {
        "question": "200 + 37",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 237
    },
    {
        "question": "341 - 43",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 298
    },
    {
        "question": "244 - 87",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 157
    },
    {
        "question": "199 - 85",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 114
    },
    {
        "question": "331 x 59",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 19529
    },
    {
        "question": "238 x 95",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 22610
    },
    {
        "question": "48 + 29",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 77
    },
    {
        "question": "43 + 39",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 82
    },
    {
        "question": "270 - 85",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 185
    },
    {
        "question": "214 x 97",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 20758
    },
    {
        "question": "325 x 97",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 31525
    },
    {
        "question": "255 x 11",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 2805
    },
    {
        "question": "66 x 65",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 4290
    },
    {
        "question": "251 - 95",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 156
    },
    {
        "question": "280 - 31",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 249
    },
    {
        "question": "327 + 79",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 406
    },
    {
        "question": "160 x 83",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 13280
    },
    {
        "question": "291 - 3",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 288
    },
    {
        "question": "388 + 43",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 431
    },
    {
        "question": "88 - 39",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 49
    },
    {
        "question": "385 - 13",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 372
    },
    {
        "question": "288 + 15",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 303
    },
    {
        "question": "144 - 87",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 57
    },
    {
        "question": "383 + 9",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 392
    },
    {
        "question": "273 - 59",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 214
    },
    {
        "question": "46 + 13",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 59
    },
    {
        "question": "29 + 37",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 66
    },
    {
        "question": "107 + 93",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 200
    },
    {
        "question": "81 - 41",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 40
    },
    {
        "question": "119 x 41",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 4879
    },
    {
        "question": "26 - 3",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 23
    },
    {
        "question": "45 x 33",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1485
    },
    {
        "question": "313 x 57",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 17841
    },
    {
        "question": "295 - 11",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 284
    },
    {
        "question": "46 - 89",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -43
    },
    {
        "question": "174 x 35",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 6090
    },
    {
        "question": "26 + 77",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 103
    },
    {
        "question": "166 + 81",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 247
    },
    {
        "question": "144 x 99",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 14256
    },
    {
        "question": "196 - 51",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 145
    },
    {
        "question": "294 + 9",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 303
    },
    {
        "question": "62 + 59",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 121
    },
    {
        "question": "297 x 31",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 9207
    },
    {
        "question": "56 x 55",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 3080
    },
    {
        "question": "231 - 19",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 212
    },
    {
        "question": "123 + 65",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 188
    },
    {
        "question": "140 x 1",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 140
    },
    {
        "question": "288 - 33",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 255
    },
    {
        "question": "371 x 99",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 36729
    },
    {
        "question": "213 + 3",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 216
    },
    {
        "question": "247 x 77",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 19019
    },
    {
        "question": "233 + 61",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 294
    },
    {
        "question": "57 + 61",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 118
    },
    {
        "question": "217 + 97",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 314
    },
    {
        "question": "369 + 81",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 450
    },
    {
        "question": "117 + 87",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 204
    },
    {
        "question": "20 + 51",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 71
    },
    {
        "question": "228 + 9",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 237
    },
    {
        "question": "255 + 81",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 336
    },
    {
        "question": "397 x 73",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 28981
    },
    {
        "question": "207 - 77",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 130
    },
    {
        "question": "51 + 15",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 66
    },
    {
        "question": "98 x 23",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 2254
    },
    {
        "question": "152 - 31",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 121
    },
    {
        "question": "188 + 27",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 215
    },
    {
        "question": "227 x 37",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 8399
    },
    {
        "question": "45 - 19",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 26
    },
    {
        "question": "230 + 47",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 277
    },
    {
        "question": "6 + 69",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 75
    },
    {
        "question": "295 x 47",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 13865
    },
    {
        "question": "276 + 17",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 293
    },
    {
        "question": "107 x 7",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 749
    },
    {
        "question": "44 x 61",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 2684
    },
    {
        "question": "6 - 67",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -61
    },
    {
        "question": "161 - 7",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 154
    },
    {
        "question": "101 - 55",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 46
    },
    {
        "question": "317 - 21",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 296
    },
    {
        "question": "131 + 25",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 156
    },
    {
        "question": "383 x 57",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 21831
    },
    {
        "question": "207 - 5",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 202
    },
    {
        "question": "124 x 97",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 12028
    },
    {
        "question": "171 - 85",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 86
    },
    {
        "question": "308 + 43",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 351
    },
    {
        "question": "49 + 3",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 52
    },
    {
        "question": "132 - 91",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 41
    },
    {
        "question": "144 + 13",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 157
    },
    {
        "question": "90 - 23",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 67
    },
    {
        "question": "388 x 69",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 26772
    },
    {
        "question": "357 x 71",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 25347
    },
    {
        "question": "81 - 99",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -18
    },
    {
        "question": "238 + 63",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 301
    },
    {
        "question": "233 + 51",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 284
    },
    {
        "question": "169 - 47",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 122
    },
    {
        "question": "181 - 83",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 98
    },
    {
        "question": "256 - 51",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 205
    },
    {
        "question": "298 - 21",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 277
    },
    {
        "question": "253 x 43",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 10879
    },
    {
        "question": "172 - 15",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 157
    },
    {
        "question": "388 + 75",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 463
    },
    {
        "question": "212 x 59",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 12508
    },
    {
        "question": "90 - 69",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 21
    },
    {
        "question": "121 - 71",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 50
    },
    {
        "question": "279 - 21",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 258
    },
    {
        "question": "397 + 41",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 438
    },
    {
        "question": "94 - 67",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 27
    },
    {
        "question": "298 - 51",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 247
    },
    {
        "question": "111 x 41",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 4551
    },
    {
        "question": "166 + 69",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 235
    },
    {
        "question": "356 x 81",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 28836
    },
    {
        "question": "361 - 15",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 346
    },
    {
        "question": "72 x 93",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 6696
    },
    {
        "question": "202 + 85",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 287
    },
    {
        "question": "241 + 77",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 318
    },
    {
        "question": "99 x 97",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 9603
    },
    {
        "question": "238 x 47",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 11186
    },
    {
        "question": "79 - 7",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 72
    },
    {
        "question": "141 + 93",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 234
    },
    {
        "question": "202 + 49",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 251
    },
    {
        "question": "102 - 51",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 51
    },
    {
        "question": "287 + 7",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 294
    },
    {
        "question": "294 + 95",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 389
    },
    {
        "question": "230 x 33",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 7590
    },
    {
        "question": "130 x 17",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 2210
    },
    {
        "question": "126 x 85",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 10710
    },
    {
        "question": "264 x 63",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 16632
    },
    {
        "question": "198 x 39",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 7722
    },
    {
        "question": "369 x 71",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 26199
    },
    {
        "question": "42 - 79",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -37
    },
    {
        "question": "77 - 59",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 18
    },
    {
        "question": "78 + 81",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 159
    },
    {
        "question": "138 - 65",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 73
    },
    {
        "question": "327 - 25",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 302
    },
    {
        "question": "154 x 3",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 462
    },
    {
        "question": "253 + 99",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 352
    },
    {
        "question": "48 + 87",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 135
    },
    {
        "question": "209 + 7",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 216
    },
    {
        "question": "382 + 89",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 471
    },
    {
        "question": "254 x 65",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 16510
    },
    {
        "question": "40 - 29",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 11
    },
    {
        "question": "304 x 25",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 7600
    },
    {
        "question": "213 - 9",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 204
    },
    {
        "question": "68 + 53",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 121
    },
    {
        "question": "181 x 29",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 5249
    },
    {
        "question": "162 + 49",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 211
    },
    {
        "question": "34 - 61",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -27
    },
    {
        "question": "117 - 81",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 36
    },
    {
        "question": "396 - 71",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 325
    },
    {
        "question": "398 + 41",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 439
    },
    {
        "question": "257 - 3",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 254
    },
    {
        "question": "306 x 63",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 19278
    },
    {
        "question": "153 - 43",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 110
    },
    {
        "question": "86 x 91",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 7826
    },
    {
        "question": "163 + 77",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 240
    },
    {
        "question": "228 + 95",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 323
    },
    {
        "question": "374 + 29",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 403
    },
    {
        "question": "164 x 45",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 7380
    },
    {
        "question": "392 x 29",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 11368
    },
    {
        "question": "232 x 91",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 21112
    },
    {
        "question": "109 + 51",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 160
    },
    {
        "question": "254 + 67",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 321
    },
    {
        "question": "99 - 33",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 66
    },
    {
        "question": "161 x 51",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 8211
    },
    {
        "question": "146 - 9",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 137
    },
    {
        "question": "143 x 21",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 3003
    },
    {
        "question": "127 x 37",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 4699
    },
    {
        "question": "59 - 25",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 34
    },
    {
        "question": "19 + 21",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 40
    },
    {
        "question": "348 + 15",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 363
    },
    {
        "question": "149 x 33",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 4917
    },
    {
        "question": "148 x 55",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 8140
    },
    {
        "question": "172 x 29",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 4988
    },
    {
        "question": "199 x 85",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 16915
    },
    {
        "question": "152 + 15",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 167
    },
    {
        "question": "262 + 75",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 337
    },
    {
        "question": "327 + 59",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 386
    },
    {
        "question": "23 + 73",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 96
    },
    {
        "question": "168 - 57",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 111
    },
    {
        "question": "184 + 61",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 245
    },
    {
        "question": "329 + 63",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 392
    },
    {
        "question": "296 x 31",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 9176
    },
    {
        "question": "202 + 65",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 267
    },
    {
        "question": "288 + 59",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 347
    },
    {
        "question": "196 + 93",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 289
    },
    {
        "question": "17 - 97",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -80
    },
    {
        "question": "194 - 29",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 165
    },
    {
        "question": "169 - 27",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 142
    },
    {
        "question": "237 - 25",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 212
    },
    {
        "question": "370 x 25",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 9250
    },
    {
        "question": "378 - 3",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 375
    },
    {
        "question": "265 - 11",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 254
    },
    {
        "question": "227 x 15",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 3405
    },
    {
        "question": "314 x 17",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 5338
    },
    {
        "question": "323 + 91",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 414
    },
    {
        "question": "341 x 87",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 29667
    },
    {
        "question": "197 x 95",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 18715
    },
    {
        "question": "315 x 19",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 5985
    },
    {
        "question": "10 + 65",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 75
    },
    {
        "question": "107 - 97",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 10
    },
    {
        "question": "33 - 13",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 20
    },
    {
        "question": "320 - 79",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 241
    },
    {
        "question": "378 - 23",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 355
    },
    {
        "question": "59 x 23",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1357
    },
    {
        "question": "179 + 19",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 198
    },
    {
        "question": "117 + 47",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 164
    },
    {
        "question": "16 - 65",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -49
    },
    {
        "question": "51 - 63",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -12
    },
    {
        "question": "373 x 71",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 26483
    },
    {
        "question": "217 x 89",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 19313
    },
    {
        "question": "162 - 97",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 65
    },
    {
        "question": "207 - 65",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 142
    },
    {
        "question": "12 - 83",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -71
    },
    {
        "question": "194 - 65",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 129
    },
    {
        "question": "214 + 61",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 275
    },
    {
        "question": "222 - 99",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 123
    },
    {
        "question": "375 - 39",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 336
    },
    {
        "question": "160 x 81",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 12960
    },
    {
        "question": "252 x 37",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 9324
    },
    {
        "question": "293 - 67",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 226
    },
    {
        "question": "22 x 97",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 2134
    },
    {
        "question": "122 x 43",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 5246
    },
    {
        "question": "172 + 57",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 229
    },
    {
        "question": "271 + 71",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 342
    },
    {
        "question": "174 x 31",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 5394
    },
    {
        "question": "66 x 43",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 2838
    },
    {
        "question": "397 + 69",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 466
    },
    {
        "question": "389 - 29",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 360
    },
    {
        "question": "249 - 31",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 218
    },
    {
        "question": "72 x 83",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 5976
    },
    {
        "question": "253 x 41",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 10373
    },
    {
        "question": "195 - 47",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 148
    },
    {
        "question": "327 + 87",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 414
    },
    {
        "question": "337 x 53",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 17861
    },
    {
        "question": "303 - 3",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 300
    },
    {
        "question": "312 + 75",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 387
    },
    {
        "question": "134 x 35",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 4690
    },
    {
        "question": "47 x 55",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 2585
    },
    {
        "question": "288 - 65",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 223
    },
    {
        "question": "105 + 25",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 130
    },
    {
        "question": "348 - 83",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 265
    },
    {
        "question": "13 x 13",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 169
    },
    {
        "question": "181 - 39",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 142
    },
    {
        "question": "272 x 73",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 19856
    },
    {
        "question": "3 + 55",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 58
    },
    {
        "question": "293 + 39",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 332
    },
    {
        "question": "330 x 83",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 27390
    },
    {
        "question": "35 + 27",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 62
    },
    {
        "question": "281 - 19",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 262
    },
    {
        "question": "41 + 13",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 54
    },
    {
        "question": "131 x 19",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 2489
    },
    {
        "question": "150 + 27",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 177
    },
    {
        "question": "374 + 97",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 471
    },
    {
        "question": "209 - 55",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 154
    },
    {
        "question": "91 x 47",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 4277
    },
    {
        "question": "178 - 61",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 117
    },
    {
        "question": "14 - 99",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -85
    },
    {
        "question": "90 - 73",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 17
    },
    {
        "question": "38 x 5",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 190
    },
    {
        "question": "315 + 69",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 384
    },
    {
        "question": "391 + 69",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 460
    },
    {
        "question": "25 + 19",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 44
    },
    {
        "question": "108 - 97",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 11
    },
    {
        "question": "335 - 17",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 318
    },
    {
        "question": "152 + 51",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 203
    },
    {
        "question": "210 + 21",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 231
    },
    {
        "question": "245 - 53",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 192
    },
    {
        "question": "285 x 87",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 24795
    },
    {
        "question": "278 + 17",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 295
    },
    {
        "question": "6 - 93",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -87
    },
    {
        "question": "145 x 81",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 11745
    },
    {
        "question": "60 x 9",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 540
    },
    {
        "question": "284 x 65",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 18460
    },
    {
        "question": "148 x 83",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 12284
    },
    {
        "question": "199 - 97",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 102
    },
    {
        "question": "326 x 65",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 21190
    },
    {
        "question": "85 x 85",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 7225
    },
    {
        "question": "142 x 35",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 4970
    },
    {
        "question": "13 + 85",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 98
    },
    {
        "question": "135 + 27",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 162
    },
    {
        "question": "148 + 49",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 197
    },
    {
        "question": "79 x 53",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 4187
    },
    {
        "question": "213 - 45",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 168
    },
    {
        "question": "257 x 67",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 17219
    },
    {
        "question": "60 + 9",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 69
    },
    {
        "question": "131 - 27",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 104
    },
    {
        "question": "157 + 57",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 214
    },
    {
        "question": "313 x 91",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 28483
    },
    {
        "question": "379 - 99",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 280
    },
    {
        "question": "307 - 93",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 214
    },
    {
        "question": "354 - 41",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 313
    },
    {
        "question": "164 + 95",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 259
    },
    {
        "question": "3 - 25",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -22
    },
    {
        "question": "75 + 65",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 140
    },
    {
        "question": "31 x 59",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1829
    },
    {
        "question": "124 x 71",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 8804
    },
    {
        "question": "189 + 9",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 198
    },
    {
        "question": "387 x 33",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 12771
    },
    {
        "question": "165 + 3",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 168
    },
    {
        "question": "336 - 73",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 263
    },
    {
        "question": "186 - 7",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 179
    },
    {
        "question": "66 x 61",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 4026
    },
    {
        "question": "316 x 13",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 4108
    },
    {
        "question": "146 x 57",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 8322
    },
    {
        "question": "94 + 45",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 139
    },
    {
        "question": "165 + 7",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 172
    },
    {
        "question": "83 - 71",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 12
    },
    {
        "question": "374 + 21",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 395
    },
    {
        "question": "144 - 17",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 127
    },
    {
        "question": "176 + 13",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 189
    },
    {
        "question": "366 - 25",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 341
    },
    {
        "question": "323 x 93",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 30039
    },
    {
        "question": "209 + 29",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 238
    },
    {
        "question": "164 + 63",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 227
    },
    {
        "question": "127 + 23",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 150
    },
    {
        "question": "140 x 47",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 6580
    },
    {
        "question": "370 - 55",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 315
    },
    {
        "question": "164 + 69",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 233
    },
    {
        "question": "96 + 57",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 153
    },
    {
        "question": "165 - 59",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 106
    },
    {
        "question": "156 x 71",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 11076
    },
    {
        "question": "327 x 3",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 981
    },
    {
        "question": "284 - 21",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 263
    },
    {
        "question": "146 x 29",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 4234
    },
    {
        "question": "211 - 59",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 152
    },
    {
        "question": "317 + 89",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 406
    },
    {
        "question": "144 x 91",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 13104
    },
    {
        "question": "281 + 3",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 284
    },
    {
        "question": "136 + 71",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 207
    },
    {
        "question": "174 + 33",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 207
    },
    {
        "question": "336 x 77",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 25872
    },
    {
        "question": "133 x 41",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 5453
    },
    {
        "question": "58 - 3",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 55
    },
    {
        "question": "154 - 75",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 79
    },
    {
        "question": "70 + 47",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 117
    },
    {
        "question": "365 - 61",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 304
    },
    {
        "question": "299 - 55",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 244
    },
    {
        "question": "362 + 61",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 423
    },
    {
        "question": "389 + 79",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 468
    },
    {
        "question": "7 + 91",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 98
    },
    {
        "question": "3 x 79",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 237
    },
    {
        "question": "88 + 31",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 119
    },
    {
        "question": "169 + 77",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 246
    },
    {
        "question": "283 + 95",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 378
    },
    {
        "question": "216 + 51",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 267
    },
    {
        "question": "230 + 61",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 291
    },
    {
        "question": "130 x 91",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 11830
    },
    {
        "question": "115 + 29",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 144
    },
    {
        "question": "71 x 91",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 6461
    },
    {
        "question": "154 + 3",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 157
    },
    {
        "question": "315 + 29",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 344
    },
    {
        "question": "36 x 31",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1116
    },
    {
        "question": "18 - 41",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -23
    },
    {
        "question": "77 - 59",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 18
    },
    {
        "question": "82 + 95",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 177
    },
    {
        "question": "195 + 33",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 228
    },
    {
        "question": "10 + 1",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 11
    },
    {
        "question": "56 + 39",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 95
    },
    {
        "question": "293 + 5",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 298
    },
    {
        "question": "254 x 19",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 4826
    },
    {
        "question": "398 - 37",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 361
    },
    {
        "question": "99 + 67",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 166
    },
    {
        "question": "109 x 97",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 10573
    },
    {
        "question": "398 + 11",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 409
    },
    {
        "question": "176 x 17",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 2992
    },
    {
        "question": "325 + 89",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 414
    },
    {
        "question": "215 + 9",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 224
    },
    {
        "question": "154 + 93",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 247
    },
    {
        "question": "221 - 47",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 174
    },
    {
        "question": "264 - 53",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 211
    },
    {
        "question": "309 x 87",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 26883
    },
    {
        "question": "39 x 81",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 3159
    },
    {
        "question": "14 + 95",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 109
    },
    {
        "question": "142 x 13",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1846
    },
    {
        "question": "13 + 37",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 50
    },
    {
        "question": "379 + 17",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 396
    },
    {
        "question": "231 + 43",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 274
    },
    {
        "question": "265 - 43",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 222
    },
    {
        "question": "161 - 93",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 68
    },
    {
        "question": "394 - 25",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 369
    },
    {
        "question": "137 x 93",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 12741
    },
    {
        "question": "45 x 79",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 3555
    },
    {
        "question": "22 + 51",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 73
    },
    {
        "question": "392 + 61",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 453
    },
    {
        "question": "342 + 45",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 387
    },
    {
        "question": "161 + 45",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 206
    },
    {
        "question": "258 + 13",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 271
    },
    {
        "question": "257 - 63",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 194
    },
    {
        "question": "276 x 81",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 22356
    },
    {
        "question": "296 x 43",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 12728
    },
    {
        "question": "147 x 75",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 11025
    },
    {
        "question": "258 + 73",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 331
    },
    {
        "question": "196 + 77",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 273
    },
    {
        "question": "29 + 29",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 58
    },
    {
        "question": "175 - 89",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 86
    },
    {
        "question": "10 - 61",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -51
    },
    {
        "question": "297 + 71",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 368
    },
    {
        "question": "64 - 17",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 47
    },
    {
        "question": "147 x 63",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 9261
    },
    {
        "question": "94 + 15",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 109
    },
    {
        "question": "65 - 83",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -18
    },
    {
        "question": "90 x 81",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 7290
    },
    {
        "question": "335 + 77",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 412
    },
    {
        "question": "51 + 51",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 102
    },
    {
        "question": "90 + 81",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 171
    },
    {
        "question": "233 + 71",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 304
    },
    {
        "question": "341 x 87",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 29667
    },
    {
        "question": "349 x 29",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 10121
    },
    {
        "question": "178 x 51",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 9078
    },
    {
        "question": "37 x 75",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 2775
    },
    {
        "question": "275 - 7",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 268
    },
    {
        "question": "62 - 23",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 39
    },
    {
        "question": "345 x 5",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1725
    },
    {
        "question": "22 x 51",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1122
    },
    {
        "question": "182 x 51",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 9282
    },
    {
        "question": "79 - 71",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 8
    },
    {
        "question": "208 x 35",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 7280
    },
    {
        "question": "95 + 83",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 178
    },
    {
        "question": "161 x 67",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 10787
    },
    {
        "question": "29 x 37",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1073
    },
    {
        "question": "160 x 63",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 10080
    },
    {
        "question": "57 x 79",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 4503
    },
    {
        "question": "305 x 93",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 28365
    },
    {
        "question": "280 x 61",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 17080
    },
    {
        "question": "126 + 33",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 159
    },
    {
        "question": "12 x 97",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1164
    },
    {
        "question": "398 + 23",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 421
    },
    {
        "question": "35 - 23",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 12
    },
    {
        "question": "266 + 39",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 305
    },
    {
        "question": "197 + 7",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 204
    },
    {
        "question": "291 x 89",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 25899
    },
    {
        "question": "136 + 99",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 235
    },
    {
        "question": "212 + 9",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 221
    },
    {
        "question": "52 - 47",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 5
    },
    {
        "question": "46 + 99",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 145
    },
    {
        "question": "12 + 29",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 41
    },
    {
        "question": "101 + 9",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 110
    },
    {
        "question": "270 + 33",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 303
    },
    {
        "question": "70 - 87",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -17
    },
    {
        "question": "265 + 67",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 332
    },
    {
        "question": "28 x 23",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 644
    },
    {
        "question": "101 + 73",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 174
    },
    {
        "question": "353 - 43",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 310
    },
    {
        "question": "103 - 89",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 14
    },
    {
        "question": "333 x 91",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 30303
    },
    {
        "question": "47 + 19",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 66
    },
    {
        "question": "167 x 21",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 3507
    },
    {
        "question": "330 + 63",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 393
    },
    {
        "question": "375 + 83",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 458
    },
    {
        "question": "264 + 17",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 281
    },
    {
        "question": "5 + 57",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 62
    },
    {
        "question": "261 - 53",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 208
    },
    {
        "question": "155 x 53",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 8215
    },
    {
        "question": "350 + 41",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 391
    },
    {
        "question": "175 x 49",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 8575
    },
    {
        "question": "366 - 45",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 321
    },
    {
        "question": "38 + 61",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 99
    },
    {
        "question": "379 x 47",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 17813
    },
    {
        "question": "39 x 21",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 819
    },
    {
        "question": "356 + 19",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 375
    },
    {
        "question": "54 + 35",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 89
    },
    {
        "question": "13 x 3",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 39
    },
    {
        "question": "376 - 61",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 315
    },
    {
        "question": "248 - 95",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 153
    },
    {
        "question": "107 - 11",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 96
    },
    {
        "question": "296 x 11",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 3256
    },
    {
        "question": "264 + 63",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 327
    },
    {
        "question": "371 x 53",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 19663
    },
    {
        "question": "254 - 77",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 177
    },
    {
        "question": "159 + 79",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 238
    },
    {
        "question": "76 - 85",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -9
    },
    {
        "question": "113 - 69",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 44
    },
    {
        "question": "195 + 7",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 202
    },
    {
        "question": "85 - 7",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 78
    },
    {
        "question": "96 - 73",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 23
    },
    {
        "question": "41 + 7",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 48
    },
    {
        "question": "262 x 25",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 6550
    },
    {
        "question": "155 - 55",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 100
    },
    {
        "question": "277 - 9",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 268
    },
    {
        "question": "30 + 11",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 41
    },
    {
        "question": "23 + 99",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 122
    },
    {
        "question": "358 + 51",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 409
    },
    {
        "question": "328 x 43",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 14104
    },
    {
        "question": "318 - 25",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 293
    },
    {
        "question": "294 x 77",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 22638
    },
    {
        "question": "189 + 67",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 256
    },
    {
        "question": "373 - 77",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 296
    },
    {
        "question": "373 - 87",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 286
    },
    {
        "question": "174 + 9",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 183
    },
    {
        "question": "157 - 35",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 122
    },
    {
        "question": "141 + 9",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 150
    },
    {
        "question": "352 x 91",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 32032
    },
    {
        "question": "115 x 33",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 3795
    },
    {
        "question": "40 - 75",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -35
    },
    {
        "question": "357 x 39",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 13923
    },
    {
        "question": "308 + 13",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 321
    },
    {
        "question": "83 - 65",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 18
    },
    {
        "question": "53 - 39",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 14
    },
    {
        "question": "286 x 31",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 8866
    },
    {
        "question": "185 - 97",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 88
    },
    {
        "question": "48 + 37",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 85
    },
    {
        "question": "121 - 1",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 120
    },
    {
        "question": "158 + 57",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 215
    },
    {
        "question": "49 x 37",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1813
    },
    {
        "question": "90 + 27",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 117
    },
    {
        "question": "44 - 21",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 23
    },
    {
        "question": "85 - 49",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 36
    },
    {
        "question": "251 + 3",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 254
    },
    {
        "question": "102 - 67",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 35
    },
    {
        "question": "252 + 99",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 351
    },
    {
        "question": "361 x 71",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 25631
    },
    {
        "question": "288 + 63",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 351
    },
    {
        "question": "91 + 63",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 154
    },
    {
        "question": "127 x 35",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 4445
    },
    {
        "question": "360 x 59",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 21240
    },
    {
        "question": "378 - 93",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 285
    },
    {
        "question": "304 - 21",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 283
    },
    {
        "question": "49 x 65",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 3185
    },
    {
        "question": "346 + 87",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 433
    },
    {
        "question": "88 - 7",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 81
    },
    {
        "question": "326 x 49",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 15974
    },
    {
        "question": "128 x 73",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 9344
    },
    {
        "question": "263 + 15",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 278
    },
    {
        "question": "70 - 75",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -5
    },
    {
        "question": "340 x 69",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 23460
    },
    {
        "question": "233 - 43",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 190
    },
    {
        "question": "298 + 47",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 345
    },
    {
        "question": "38 + 95",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 133
    },
    {
        "question": "311 x 99",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 30789
    },
    {
        "question": "120 + 75",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 195
    },
    {
        "question": "256 - 83",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 173
    },
    {
        "question": "175 - 31",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 144
    },
    {
        "question": "231 x 99",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 22869
    },
    {
        "question": "341 - 39",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 302
    },
    {
        "question": "210 - 85",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 125
    },
    {
        "question": "105 x 13",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1365
    },
    {
        "question": "170 + 23",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 193
    },
    {
        "question": "374 - 95",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 279
    },
    {
        "question": "26 + 27",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 53
    },
    {
        "question": "11 + 81",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 92
    },
    {
        "question": "69 x 67",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 4623
    },
    {
        "question": "123 + 11",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 134
    },
    {
        "question": "227 x 9",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 2043
    },
    {
        "question": "212 - 63",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 149
    },
    {
        "question": "202 x 23",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 4646
    },
    {
        "question": "16 - 1",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 15
    },
    {
        "question": "152 x 51",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 7752
    },
    {
        "question": "152 - 71",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 81
    },
    {
        "question": "172 x 43",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 7396
    },
    {
        "question": "354 + 1",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 355
    },
    {
        "question": "57 - 59",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -2
    },
    {
        "question": "179 x 85",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 15215
    },
    {
        "question": "53 + 45",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 98
    },
    {
        "question": "290 - 49",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 241
    },
    {
        "question": "27 - 7",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 20
    },
    {
        "question": "336 x 65",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 21840
    },
    {
        "question": "108 - 25",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 83
    },
    {
        "question": "190 - 63",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 127
    },
    {
        "question": "331 x 67",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 22177
    },
    {
        "question": "226 x 27",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 6102
    },
    {
        "question": "99 - 41",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 58
    },
    {
        "question": "53 + 85",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 138
    },
    {
        "question": "218 - 15",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 203
    },
    {
        "question": "232 - 27",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 205
    },
    {
        "question": "385 + 7",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 392
    },
    {
        "question": "328 + 7",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 335
    },
    {
        "question": "174 + 51",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 225
    },
    {
        "question": "264 x 23",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 6072
    },
    {
        "question": "361 - 77",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 284
    },
    {
        "question": "9 + 13",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 22
    },
    {
        "question": "154 - 81",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 73
    },
    {
        "question": "55 + 35",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 90
    },
    {
        "question": "338 - 13",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 325
    },
    {
        "question": "301 + 23",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 324
    },
    {
        "question": "307 + 89",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 396
    },
    {
        "question": "71 x 45",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 3195
    },
    {
        "question": "53 x 51",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 2703
    },
    {
        "question": "206 - 55",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 151
    },
    {
        "question": "69 + 21",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 90
    },
    {
        "question": "75 x 75",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 5625
    },
    {
        "question": "79 + 43",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 122
    },
    {
        "question": "32 + 79",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 111
    },
    {
        "question": "322 x 25",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 8050
    },
    {
        "question": "217 - 97",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 120
    },
    {
        "question": "200 + 3",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 203
    },
    {
        "question": "370 + 61",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 431
    },
    {
        "question": "221 + 23",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 244
    },
    {
        "question": "60 x 1",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 60
    },
    {
        "question": "97 + 23",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 120
    },
    {
        "question": "310 x 55",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 17050
    },
    {
        "question": "346 + 5",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 351
    },
    {
        "question": "142 - 25",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 117
    },
    {
        "question": "122 x 89",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 10858
    },
    {
        "question": "189 x 49",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 9261
    },
    {
        "question": "287 - 65",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 222
    },
    {
        "question": "300 + 29",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 329
    },
    {
        "question": "62 - 35",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 27
    },
    {
        "question": "68 - 73",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -5
    },
    {
        "question": "141 x 19",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 2679
    },
    {
        "question": "243 - 69",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 174
    },
    {
        "question": "43 - 23",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 20
    },
    {
        "question": "45 - 55",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -10
    },
    {
        "question": "240 + 91",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 331
    },
    {
        "question": "183 - 23",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 160
    },
    {
        "question": "130 + 65",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 195
    },
    {
        "question": "146 x 29",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 4234
    },
    {
        "question": "51 x 35",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1785
    },
    {
        "question": "234 x 77",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 18018
    },
    {
        "question": "67 x 75",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 5025
    },
    {
        "question": "347 + 99",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 446
    },
    {
        "question": "345 - 77",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 268
    },
    {
        "question": "301 - 45",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 256
    },
    {
        "question": "173 + 43",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 216
    },
    {
        "question": "297 x 5",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1485
    },
    {
        "question": "211 - 97",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 114
    },
    {
        "question": "370 - 7",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 363
    },
    {
        "question": "389 x 87",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 33843
    },
    {
        "question": "110 - 19",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 91
    },
    {
        "question": "161 - 3",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 158
    },
    {
        "question": "189 - 33",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 156
    },
    {
        "question": "374 - 53",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 321
    },
    {
        "question": "280 - 45",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 235
    },
    {
        "question": "357 x 55",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 19635
    },
    {
        "question": "141 x 49",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 6909
    },
    {
        "question": "122 - 45",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 77
    },
    {
        "question": "244 - 69",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 175
    },
    {
        "question": "324 + 17",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 341
    },
    {
        "question": "212 x 73",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 15476
    },
    {
        "question": "354 + 93",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 447
    },
    {
        "question": "211 + 11",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 222
    },
    {
        "question": "95 + 25",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 120
    },
    {
        "question": "167 + 83",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 250
    },
    {
        "question": "298 + 65",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 363
    },
    {
        "question": "346 - 5",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 341
    },
    {
        "question": "240 - 91",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 149
    },
    {
        "question": "384 x 73",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 28032
    },
    {
        "question": "63 - 83",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -20
    },
    {
        "question": "259 - 1",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 258
    },
    {
        "question": "13 - 67",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -54
    },
    {
        "question": "327 + 37",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 364
    },
    {
        "question": "318 x 55",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 17490
    },
    {
        "question": "282 - 5",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 277
    },
    {
        "question": "184 x 67",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 12328
    },
    {
        "question": "32 + 87",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 119
    },
    {
        "question": "99 x 67",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 6633
    },
    {
        "question": "227 x 33",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 7491
    },
    {
        "question": "61 - 9",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 52
    },
    {
        "question": "236 + 11",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 247
    },
    {
        "question": "100 + 49",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 149
    },
    {
        "question": "101 - 33",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 68
    },
    {
        "question": "202 + 93",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 295
    },
    {
        "question": "139 + 45",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 184
    },
    {
        "question": "366 - 67",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 299
    },
    {
        "question": "399 - 23",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 376
    },
    {
        "question": "151 x 27",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 4077
    },
    {
        "question": "241 + 3",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 244
    },
    {
        "question": "234 + 29",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 263
    },
    {
        "question": "145 + 69",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 214
    },
    {
        "question": "242 + 33",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 275
    },
    {
        "question": "198 x 63",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 12474
    },
    {
        "question": "87 + 79",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 166
    },
    {
        "question": "335 - 21",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 314
    },
    {
        "question": "223 - 33",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 190
    },
    {
        "question": "5 - 31",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -26
    },
    {
        "question": "396 - 59",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 337
    },
    {
        "question": "265 x 29",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 7685
    },
    {
        "question": "30 + 9",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 39
    },
    {
        "question": "255 + 91",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 346
    },
    {
        "question": "164 - 81",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 83
    },
    {
        "question": "97 + 25",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 122
    },
    {
        "question": "338 + 27",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 365
    },
    {
        "question": "147 x 27",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 3969
    },
    {
        "question": "99 + 31",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 130
    },
    {
        "question": "254 + 23",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 277
    },
    {
        "question": "252 x 59",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 14868
    },
    {
        "question": "92 - 15",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 77
    },
    {
        "question": "178 + 87",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 265
    },
    {
        "question": "236 x 99",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 23364
    },
    {
        "question": "206 x 83",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 17098
    },
    {
        "question": "25 - 7",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 18
    },
    {
        "question": "77 x 43",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 3311
    },
    {
        "question": "172 x 57",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 9804
    },
    {
        "question": "257 x 27",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 6939
    },
    {
        "question": "2 x 33",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 66
    },
    {
        "question": "34 - 49",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -15
    },
    {
        "question": "196 + 9",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 205
    },
    {
        "question": "43 x 67",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 2881
    },
    {
        "question": "340 x 95",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 32300
    },
    {
        "question": "230 + 35",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 265
    },
    {
        "question": "306 + 53",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 359
    },
    {
        "question": "222 x 75",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 16650
    },
    {
        "question": "321 + 87",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 408
    },
    {
        "question": "152 x 23",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 3496
    },
    {
        "question": "204 - 67",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 137
    },
    {
        "question": "364 x 51",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 18564
    },
    {
        "question": "344 - 87",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 257
    },
    {
        "question": "346 - 23",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 323
    },
    {
        "question": "201 + 3",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 204
    },
    {
        "question": "217 + 43",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 260
    },
    {
        "question": "331 + 63",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 394
    },
    {
        "question": "154 + 25",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 179
    },
    {
        "question": "196 + 43",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 239
    },
    {
        "question": "47 x 87",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 4089
    },
    {
        "question": "221 + 51",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 272
    },
    {
        "question": "295 + 43",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 338
    },
    {
        "question": "12 - 51",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -39
    },
    {
        "question": "24 x 33",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 792
    },
    {
        "question": "244 - 17",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 227
    },
    {
        "question": "265 - 39",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 226
    },
    {
        "question": "234 + 23",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 257
    },
    {
        "question": "358 - 15",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 343
    },
    {
        "question": "381 + 41",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 422
    },
    {
        "question": "213 + 95",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 308
    },
    {
        "question": "309 + 65",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 374
    },
    {
        "question": "288 + 47",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 335
    },
    {
        "question": "301 - 71",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 230
    },
    {
        "question": "12 x 35",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 420
    },
    {
        "question": "40 x 77",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 3080
    },
    {
        "question": "297 + 81",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 378
    },
    {
        "question": "314 x 1",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 314
    },
    {
        "question": "372 + 21",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 393
    },
    {
        "question": "184 - 83",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 101
    },
    {
        "question": "367 x 95",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 34865
    },
    {
        "question": "270 - 85",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 185
    },
    {
        "question": "118 + 27",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 145
    },
    {
        "question": "216 - 31",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 185
    },
    {
        "question": "232 + 37",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 269
    },
    {
        "question": "380 - 77",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 303
    },
    {
        "question": "91 x 75",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 6825
    },
    {
        "question": "146 - 63",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 83
    },
    {
        "question": "173 + 59",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 232
    },
    {
        "question": "369 x 1",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 369
    },
    {
        "question": "163 + 59",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 222
    },
    {
        "question": "247 + 59",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 306
    },
    {
        "question": "111 - 59",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 52
    },
    {
        "question": "42 - 63",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -21
    },
    {
        "question": "338 - 21",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 317
    },
    {
        "question": "219 - 9",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 210
    },
    {
        "question": "89 x 7",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 623
    },
    {
        "question": "50 x 45",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 2250
    },
    {
        "question": "220 x 97",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 21340
    },
    {
        "question": "255 + 43",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 298
    },
    {
        "question": "111 - 69",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 42
    },
    {
        "question": "181 + 39",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 220
    },
    {
        "question": "86 + 83",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 169
    },
    {
        "question": "177 + 63",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 240
    },
    {
        "question": "75 - 55",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 20
    },
    {
        "question": "281 x 31",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 8711
    },
    {
        "question": "152 - 61",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 91
    },
    {
        "question": "188 - 73",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 115
    },
    {
        "question": "117 - 83",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 34
    },
    {
        "question": "342 - 63",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 279
    },
    {
        "question": "358 - 77",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 281
    },
    {
        "question": "319 - 47",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 272
    },
    {
        "question": "71 - 59",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 12
    },
    {
        "question": "196 - 17",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 179
    },
    {
        "question": "326 - 19",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 307
    },
    {
        "question": "172 - 31",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 141
    },
    {
        "question": "25 + 27",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 52
    },
    {
        "question": "121 + 55",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 176
    },
    {
        "question": "300 - 37",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 263
    },
    {
        "question": "1 x 81",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 81
    },
    {
        "question": "72 + 5",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 77
    },
    {
        "question": "353 x 97",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 34241
    },
    {
        "question": "67 x 81",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 5427
    },
    {
        "question": "194 - 37",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 157
    },
    {
        "question": "137 x 65",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 8905
    },
    {
        "question": "31 - 47",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -16
    },
    {
        "question": "225 x 13",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 2925
    },
    {
        "question": "383 + 89",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 472
    },
    {
        "question": "308 x 49",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 15092
    },
    {
        "question": "174 x 65",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 11310
    },
    {
        "question": "276 - 1",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 275
    },
    {
        "question": "193 + 3",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 196
    },
    {
        "question": "36 + 89",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 125
    },
    {
        "question": "351 + 19",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 370
    },
    {
        "question": "342 - 67",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 275
    },
    {
        "question": "92 - 23",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 69
    },
    {
        "question": "368 + 49",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 417
    },
    {
        "question": "27 - 79",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -52
    },
    {
        "question": "117 x 19",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 2223
    },
    {
        "question": "182 - 67",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 115
    },
    {
        "question": "230 - 43",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 187
    },
    {
        "question": "280 + 37",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 317
    },
    {
        "question": "62 + 5",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 67
    },
    {
        "question": "347 + 21",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 368
    },
    {
        "question": "194 x 97",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 18818
    },
    {
        "question": "74 x 23",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1702
    },
    {
        "question": "351 - 91",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 260
    },
    {
        "question": "191 + 37",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 228
    },
    {
        "question": "135 x 17",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 2295
    },
    {
        "question": "386 x 49",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 18914
    },
    {
        "question": "327 + 93",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 420
    },
    {
        "question": "366 x 1",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 366
    },
    {
        "question": "314 + 91",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 405
    },
    {
        "question": "292 - 13",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 279
    },
    {
        "question": "380 x 75",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 28500
    },
    {
        "question": "392 x 35",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 13720
    },
    {
        "question": "108 x 99",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 10692
    },
    {
        "question": "6 x 69",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 414
    },
    {
        "question": "163 x 17",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 2771
    },
    {
        "question": "203 x 41",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 8323
    },
    {
        "question": "168 x 17",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 2856
    },
    {
        "question": "100 + 13",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 113
    },
    {
        "question": "226 - 69",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 157
    },
    {
        "question": "205 + 33",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 238
    },
    {
        "question": "92 + 77",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 169
    },
    {
        "question": "254 + 37",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 291
    },
    {
        "question": "173 - 93",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 80
    },
    {
        "question": "199 + 59",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 258
    },
    {
        "question": "283 + 25",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 308
    },
    {
        "question": "328 + 29",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 357
    },
    {
        "question": "1 + 63",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 64
    },
    {
        "question": "14 + 39",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 53
    },
    {
        "question": "1 - 55",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -54
    },
    {
        "question": "307 x 3",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 921
    },
    {
        "question": "90 x 39",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 3510
    },
    {
        "question": "305 + 93",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 398
    },
    {
        "question": "214 - 75",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 139
    },
    {
        "question": "378 + 43",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 421
    },
    {
        "question": "87 + 81",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 168
    },
    {
        "question": "177 - 17",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 160
    },
    {
        "question": "325 x 23",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 7475
    },
    {
        "question": "361 + 19",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 380
    },
    {
        "question": "327 + 37",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 364
    },
    {
        "question": "307 x 41",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 12587
    },
    {
        "question": "227 x 97",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 22019
    },
    {
        "question": "116 - 25",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 91
    },
    {
        "question": "25 x 9",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 225
    },
    {
        "question": "119 - 29",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 90
    },
    {
        "question": "35 - 35",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "163 x 23",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 3749
    },
    {
        "question": "262 - 21",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 241
    },
    {
        "question": "341 - 67",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 274
    },
    {
        "question": "62 x 61",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 3782
    },
    {
        "question": "41 + 7",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 48
    },
    {
        "question": "67 x 77",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 5159
    },
    {
        "question": "10 + 63",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 73
    },
    {
        "question": "281 + 11",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 292
    },
    {
        "question": "167 + 91",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 258
    },
    {
        "question": "18 + 85",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 103
    },
    {
        "question": "375 + 3",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 378
    },
    {
        "question": "253 + 41",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 294
    },
    {
        "question": "153 + 57",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 210
    },
    {
        "question": "101 + 39",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 140
    },
    {
        "question": "139 x 81",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 11259
    },
    {
        "question": "84 - 35",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 49
    },
    {
        "question": "213 + 45",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 258
    },
    {
        "question": "123 x 15",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1845
    },
    {
        "question": "42 x 65",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 2730
    },
    {
        "question": "335 x 57",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 19095
    },
    {
        "question": "254 + 1",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 255
    },
    {
        "question": "249 x 41",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 10209
    },
    {
        "question": "266 x 29",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 7714
    },
    {
        "question": "316 - 5",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 311
    },
    {
        "question": "390 - 9",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 381
    },
    {
        "question": "40 + 41",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 81
    },
    {
        "question": "136 + 89",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 225
    },
    {
        "question": "107 + 71",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 178
    },
    {
        "question": "373 + 7",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 380
    },
    {
        "question": "346 + 45",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 391
    },
    {
        "question": "40 x 65",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 2600
    },
    {
        "question": "225 + 69",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 294
    },
    {
        "question": "88 + 65",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 153
    },
    {
        "question": "306 - 47",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 259
    },
    {
        "question": "121 + 7",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 128
    },
    {
        "question": "213 + 7",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 220
    },
    {
        "question": "104 - 7",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 97
    },
    {
        "question": "318 + 1",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 319
    },
    {
        "question": "129 + 25",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 154
    },
    {
        "question": "17 + 53",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 70
    },
    {
        "question": "237 x 43",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 10191
    },
    {
        "question": "39 + 63",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 102
    },
    {
        "question": "211 + 89",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 300
    },
    {
        "question": "80 x 17",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1360
    },
    {
        "question": "307 x 81",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 24867
    },
    {
        "question": "316 x 11",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 3476
    },
    {
        "question": "178 x 73",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 12994
    },
    {
        "question": "126 x 73",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 9198
    },
    {
        "question": "51 - 39",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 12
    },
    {
        "question": "130 + 71",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 201
    },
    {
        "question": "159 x 61",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 9699
    },
    {
        "question": "119 + 59",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 178
    },
    {
        "question": "381 + 49",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 430
    },
    {
        "question": "124 + 49",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 173
    },
    {
        "question": "122 + 57",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 179
    },
    {
        "question": "32 x 45",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1440
    },
    {
        "question": "13 - 67",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -54
    },
    {
        "question": "295 x 57",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 16815
    },
    {
        "question": "45 - 43",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "23 + 91",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 114
    },
    {
        "question": "352 x 39",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 13728
    },
    {
        "question": "196 - 69",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 127
    },
    {
        "question": "114 + 27",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 141
    },
    {
        "question": "29 - 11",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 18
    },
    {
        "question": "230 x 33",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 7590
    },
    {
        "question": "127 - 65",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 62
    },
    {
        "question": "16 - 25",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -9
    },
    {
        "question": "54 x 67",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 3618
    },
    {
        "question": "110 x 91",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 10010
    },
    {
        "question": "333 - 79",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 254
    },
    {
        "question": "212 - 21",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 191
    },
    {
        "question": "92 + 83",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 175
    },
    {
        "question": "65 - 25",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 40
    },
    {
        "question": "144 x 89",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 12816
    },
    {
        "question": "145 x 97",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 14065
    },
    {
        "question": "80 + 99",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 179
    },
    {
        "question": "98 - 45",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 53
    },
    {
        "question": "73 - 97",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -24
    },
    {
        "question": "143 x 41",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 5863
    },
    {
        "question": "153 x 87",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 13311
    },
    {
        "question": "367 x 33",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 12111
    },
    {
        "question": "254 + 83",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 337
    },
    {
        "question": "300 + 29",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 329
    },
    {
        "question": "128 + 33",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 161
    },
    {
        "question": "391 x 65",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 25415
    },
    {
        "question": "84 - 49",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 35
    },
    {
        "question": "176 x 89",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 15664
    },
    {
        "question": "144 x 37",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 5328
    },
    {
        "question": "66 - 15",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 51
    },
    {
        "question": "115 - 79",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 36
    },
    {
        "question": "376 x 43",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 16168
    },
    {
        "question": "378 - 41",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 337
    },
    {
        "question": "220 x 61",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 13420
    },
    {
        "question": "95 + 41",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 136
    },
    {
        "question": "85 - 39",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 46
    },
    {
        "question": "371 + 29",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 400
    },
    {
        "question": "74 - 17",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 57
    },
    {
        "question": "221 x 77",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 17017
    },
    {
        "question": "31 x 29",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 899
    },
    {
        "question": "152 - 35",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 117
    },
    {
        "question": "154 x 73",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 11242
    },
    {
        "question": "230 x 47",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 10810
    },
    {
        "question": "264 + 11",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 275
    },
    {
        "question": "67 x 17",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1139
    },
    {
        "question": "322 + 75",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 397
    },
    {
        "question": "68 + 77",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 145
    },
    {
        "question": "187 + 1",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 188
    },
    {
        "question": "147 - 11",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 136
    },
    {
        "question": "388 + 61",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 449
    },
    {
        "question": "155 x 87",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 13485
    },
    {
        "question": "261 + 3",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 264
    },
    {
        "question": "182 x 73",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 13286
    },
    {
        "question": "233 + 51",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 284
    },
    {
        "question": "241 x 87",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 20967
    },
    {
        "question": "50 + 37",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 87
    },
    {
        "question": "337 x 39",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 13143
    },
    {
        "question": "5 - 31",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -26
    },
    {
        "question": "240 + 63",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 303
    },
    {
        "question": "325 x 19",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 6175
    },
    {
        "question": "169 x 43",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 7267
    },
    {
        "question": "370 x 57",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 21090
    },
    {
        "question": "353 - 95",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 258
    },
    {
        "question": "369 - 21",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 348
    },
    {
        "question": "34 x 95",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 3230
    },
    {
        "question": "4 x 73",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 292
    },
    {
        "question": "180 + 1",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 181
    },
    {
        "question": "279 - 51",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 228
    },
    {
        "question": "365 x 17",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 6205
    },
    {
        "question": "316 - 83",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 233
    },
    {
        "question": "187 + 55",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 242
    },
    {
        "question": "253 x 63",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 15939
    },
    {
        "question": "11 + 33",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 44
    },
    {
        "question": "52 - 99",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -47
    },
    {
        "question": "229 - 59",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 170
    },
    {
        "question": "33 x 89",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 2937
    },
    {
        "question": "16 - 55",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -39
    },
    {
        "question": "17 x 67",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1139
    },
    {
        "question": "180 + 5",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 185
    },
    {
        "question": "262 - 7",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 255
    },
    {
        "question": "244 + 79",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 323
    },
    {
        "question": "310 + 11",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 321
    },
    {
        "question": "194 + 77",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 271
    },
    {
        "question": "287 + 85",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 372
    },
    {
        "question": "171 + 9",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 180
    },
    {
        "question": "203 + 29",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 232
    },
    {
        "question": "170 x 67",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 11390
    },
    {
        "question": "212 - 19",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 193
    },
    {
        "question": "145 + 99",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 244
    },
    {
        "question": "65 - 49",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 16
    },
    {
        "question": "119 x 57",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 6783
    },
    {
        "question": "373 x 53",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 19769
    },
    {
        "question": "204 x 47",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 9588
    },
    {
        "question": "68 - 81",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -13
    },
    {
        "question": "278 x 65",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 18070
    },
    {
        "question": "53 x 73",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 3869
    },
    {
        "question": "238 + 65",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 303
    },
    {
        "question": "309 x 81",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 25029
    },
    {
        "question": "84 x 9",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 756
    },
    {
        "question": "160 - 53",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 107
    },
    {
        "question": "166 x 85",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 14110
    },
    {
        "question": "58 x 59",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 3422
    },
    {
        "question": "392 + 61",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 453
    },
    {
        "question": "56 + 67",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 123
    },
    {
        "question": "274 - 39",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 235
    },
    {
        "question": "55 x 23",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1265
    },
    {
        "question": "6 + 9",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 15
    },
    {
        "question": "182 - 61",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 121
    },
    {
        "question": "283 x 77",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 21791
    },
    {
        "question": "311 + 79",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 390
    },
    {
        "question": "188 + 73",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 261
    },
    {
        "question": "148 - 63",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 85
    },
    {
        "question": "213 - 95",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 118
    },
    {
        "question": "130 x 17",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 2210
    },
    {
        "question": "70 - 53",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 17
    },
    {
        "question": "180 - 29",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 151
    },
    {
        "question": "322 + 85",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 407
    },
    {
        "question": "205 x 37",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 7585
    },
    {
        "question": "345 - 73",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 272
    },
    {
        "question": "262 x 59",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 15458
    },
    {
        "question": "386 - 87",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 299
    },
    {
        "question": "149 x 67",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 9983
    },
    {
        "question": "277 - 1",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 276
    },
    {
        "question": "348 x 3",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1044
    },
    {
        "question": "2 - 35",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -33
    },
    {
        "question": "84 + 71",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 155
    },
    {
        "question": "246 x 37",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 9102
    },
    {
        "question": "309 x 13",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 4017
    },
    {
        "question": "63 x 93",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 5859
    },
    {
        "question": "46 x 21",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 966
    },
    {
        "question": "377 + 77",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 454
    },
    {
        "question": "261 x 81",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 21141
    },
    {
        "question": "43 - 77",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -34
    },
    {
        "question": "348 + 31",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 379
    },
    {
        "question": "319 - 35",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 284
    },
    {
        "question": "368 + 49",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 417
    },
    {
        "question": "194 x 33",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 6402
    },
    {
        "question": "45 x 25",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1125
    },
    {
        "question": "49 + 27",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 76
    },
    {
        "question": "121 + 65",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 186
    },
    {
        "question": "268 - 83",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 185
    },
    {
        "question": "213 x 71",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 15123
    },
    {
        "question": "191 x 91",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 17381
    },
    {
        "question": "356 - 97",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 259
    },
    {
        "question": "280 - 25",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 255
    },
    {
        "question": "7 - 25",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -18
    },
    {
        "question": "43 + 29",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 72
    },
    {
        "question": "44 - 5",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 39
    },
    {
        "question": "372 + 35",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 407
    },
    {
        "question": "109 - 67",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 42
    },
    {
        "question": "32 - 63",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -31
    },
    {
        "question": "14 x 51",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 714
    },
    {
        "question": "91 + 5",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 96
    },
    {
        "question": "339 - 85",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 254
    },
    {
        "question": "370 - 19",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 351
    },
    {
        "question": "297 - 9",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 288
    },
    {
        "question": "125 - 95",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 30
    },
    {
        "question": "186 x 13",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 2418
    },
    {
        "question": "90 x 75",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 6750
    },
    {
        "question": "58 x 1",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 58
    },
    {
        "question": "142 - 85",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 57
    },
    {
        "question": "2 + 55",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 57
    },
    {
        "question": "25 + 35",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 60
    },
    {
        "question": "365 - 57",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 308
    },
    {
        "question": "268 - 35",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 233
    },
    {
        "question": "345 + 43",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 388
    },
    {
        "question": "375 + 37",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 412
    },
    {
        "question": "349 x 81",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 28269
    },
    {
        "question": "283 - 91",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 192
    },
    {
        "question": "25 + 67",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 92
    },
    {
        "question": "53 - 57",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -4
    },
    {
        "question": "275 x 19",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 5225
    },
    {
        "question": "392 - 9",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 383
    },
    {
        "question": "113 - 73",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 40
    },
    {
        "question": "43 + 99",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 142
    },
    {
        "question": "42 x 67",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 2814
    },
    {
        "question": "356 x 49",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 17444
    },
    {
        "question": "101 + 69",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 170
    },
    {
        "question": "262 + 19",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 281
    },
    {
        "question": "319 + 65",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 384
    },
    {
        "question": "120 x 21",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 2520
    },
    {
        "question": "34 + 1",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 35
    },
    {
        "question": "334 + 15",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 349
    },
    {
        "question": "259 x 1",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 259
    },
    {
        "question": "248 - 79",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 169
    },
    {
        "question": "362 x 93",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 33666
    },
    {
        "question": "137 + 27",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 164
    },
    {
        "question": "389 + 69",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 458
    },
    {
        "question": "357 - 51",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 306
    },
    {
        "question": "62 x 31",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1922
    },
    {
        "question": "360 + 45",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 405
    },
    {
        "question": "22 x 31",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 682
    },
    {
        "question": "1 + 13",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 14
    },
    {
        "question": "226 x 47",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 10622
    },
    {
        "question": "312 + 79",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 391
    },
    {
        "question": "170 x 87",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 14790
    },
    {
        "question": "71 x 91",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 6461
    },
    {
        "question": "195 + 35",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 230
    },
    {
        "question": "142 x 15",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 2130
    },
    {
        "question": "289 x 57",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 16473
    },
    {
        "question": "67 + 5",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 72
    },
    {
        "question": "112 x 15",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1680
    },
    {
        "question": "271 + 33",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 304
    },
    {
        "question": "342 + 1",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 343
    },
    {
        "question": "270 - 89",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 181
    },
    {
        "question": "33 x 63",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 2079
    },
    {
        "question": "103 + 7",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 110
    },
    {
        "question": "216 + 47",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 263
    },
    {
        "question": "362 - 31",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 331
    },
    {
        "question": "310 x 97",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 30070
    },
    {
        "question": "273 - 85",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 188
    },
    {
        "question": "205 - 99",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 106
    },
    {
        "question": "52 + 75",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 127
    },
    {
        "question": "206 - 9",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 197
    },
    {
        "question": "1 x 37",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 37
    },
    {
        "question": "348 + 23",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 371
    },
    {
        "question": "224 - 35",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 189
    },
    {
        "question": "124 + 81",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 205
    },
    {
        "question": "12 x 39",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 468
    },
    {
        "question": "127 x 71",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 9017
    },
    {
        "question": "277 + 81",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 358
    },
    {
        "question": "265 + 81",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 346
    },
    {
        "question": "305 - 11",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 294
    },
    {
        "question": "169 x 89",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 15041
    },
    {
        "question": "275 + 49",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 324
    },
    {
        "question": "89 + 35",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 124
    },
    {
        "question": "275 x 85",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 23375
    },
    {
        "question": "331 + 39",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 370
    },
    {
        "question": "324 x 51",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 16524
    },
    {
        "question": "389 + 33",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 422
    },
    {
        "question": "385 - 15",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 370
    },
    {
        "question": "261 - 5",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 256
    },
    {
        "question": "396 - 89",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 307
    },
    {
        "question": "336 + 7",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 343
    },
    {
        "question": "350 + 57",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 407
    },
    {
        "question": "101 - 57",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 44
    },
    {
        "question": "193 - 91",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 102
    },
    {
        "question": "303 - 55",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 248
    },
    {
        "question": "229 + 31",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 260
    },
    {
        "question": "240 x 25",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 6000
    },
    {
        "question": "12 x 79",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 948
    },
    {
        "question": "212 - 61",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 151
    },
    {
        "question": "100 + 33",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 133
    },
    {
        "question": "2 - 9",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -7
    },
    {
        "question": "63 - 29",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 34
    },
    {
        "question": "268 x 73",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 19564
    },
    {
        "question": "398 + 65",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 463
    },
    {
        "question": "348 - 1",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 347
    },
    {
        "question": "126 x 15",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1890
    },
    {
        "question": "44 x 91",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 4004
    },
    {
        "question": "93 x 59",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 5487
    },
    {
        "question": "33 + 15",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 48
    },
    {
        "question": "359 + 59",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 418
    },
    {
        "question": "167 x 1",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 167
    },
    {
        "question": "360 x 27",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 9720
    },
    {
        "question": "350 + 97",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 447
    },
    {
        "question": "164 - 53",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 111
    },
    {
        "question": "74 - 77",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -3
    },
    {
        "question": "71 x 91",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 6461
    },
    {
        "question": "8 x 81",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 648
    },
    {
        "question": "2 + 85",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 87
    },
    {
        "question": "291 - 53",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 238
    },
    {
        "question": "388 + 77",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 465
    },
    {
        "question": "341 - 39",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 302
    },
    {
        "question": "177 x 31",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 5487
    },
    {
        "question": "379 + 53",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 432
    },
    {
        "question": "353 x 55",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 19415
    },
    {
        "question": "373 x 47",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 17531
    },
    {
        "question": "120 x 75",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 9000
    },
    {
        "question": "80 x 97",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 7760
    },
    {
        "question": "58 x 21",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1218
    },
    {
        "question": "30 - 1",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 29
    },
    {
        "question": "359 x 87",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 31233
    },
    {
        "question": "266 + 87",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 353
    },
    {
        "question": "311 - 61",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 250
    },
    {
        "question": "396 x 61",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 24156
    },
    {
        "question": "183 + 69",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 252
    },
    {
        "question": "162 x 81",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 13122
    },
    {
        "question": "370 x 25",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 9250
    },
    {
        "question": "24 + 45",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 69
    },
    {
        "question": "342 - 63",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 279
    },
    {
        "question": "162 x 49",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 7938
    },
    {
        "question": "349 + 25",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 374
    },
    {
        "question": "11 + 77",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 88
    },
    {
        "question": "318 + 7",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 325
    },
    {
        "question": "99 - 63",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 36
    },
    {
        "question": "70 - 7",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 63
    },
    {
        "question": "379 - 19",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 360
    },
    {
        "question": "373 - 61",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 312
    },
    {
        "question": "8 + 77",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 85
    },
    {
        "question": "248 - 49",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 199
    },
    {
        "question": "187 x 53",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 9911
    },
    {
        "question": "171 + 65",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 236
    },
    {
        "question": "174 + 7",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 181
    },
    {
        "question": "235 + 87",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 322
    },
    {
        "question": "58 - 83",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -25
    },
    {
        "question": "126 x 49",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 6174
    },
    {
        "question": "309 - 3",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 306
    },
    {
        "question": "325 x 89",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 28925
    },
    {
        "question": "238 - 47",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 191
    },
    {
        "question": "59 + 95",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 154
    },
    {
        "question": "152 + 67",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 219
    },
    {
        "question": "296 x 55",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 16280
    },
    {
        "question": "17 + 41",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 58
    },
    {
        "question": "251 x 3",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 753
    },
    {
        "question": "83 - 15",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 68
    },
    {
        "question": "354 + 71",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 425
    },
    {
        "question": "92 + 67",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 159
    },
    {
        "question": "311 x 19",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 5909
    },
    {
        "question": "371 + 93",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 464
    },
    {
        "question": "336 - 75",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 261
    },
    {
        "question": "20 - 73",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -53
    },
    {
        "question": "307 - 3",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 304
    },
    {
        "question": "285 x 5",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1425
    },
    {
        "question": "225 x 75",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 16875
    },
    {
        "question": "318 x 7",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 2226
    },
    {
        "question": "49 - 59",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -10
    },
    {
        "question": "382 x 57",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 21774
    },
    {
        "question": "277 - 51",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 226
    },
    {
        "question": "359 x 85",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 30515
    },
    {
        "question": "202 x 7",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1414
    },
    {
        "question": "240 + 57",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 297
    },
    {
        "question": "255 + 95",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 350
    },
    {
        "question": "12 x 49",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 588
    },
    {
        "question": "94 x 69",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 6486
    },
    {
        "question": "340 + 29",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 369
    },
    {
        "question": "265 - 17",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 248
    },
    {
        "question": "325 x 11",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 3575
    },
    {
        "question": "84 + 95",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 179
    },
    {
        "question": "249 x 45",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 11205
    },
    {
        "question": "222 - 85",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 137
    },
    {
        "question": "290 - 43",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 247
    },
    {
        "question": "145 - 73",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 72
    },
    {
        "question": "12 + 67",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 79
    },
    {
        "question": "397 + 23",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 420
    },
    {
        "question": "289 x 77",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 22253
    },
    {
        "question": "348 x 99",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 34452
    },
    {
        "question": "340 x 81",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 27540
    },
    {
        "question": "377 + 33",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 410
    },
    {
        "question": "291 - 53",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 238
    },
    {
        "question": "103 - 5",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 98
    },
    {
        "question": "156 + 1",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 157
    },
    {
        "question": "291 + 45",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 336
    },
    {
        "question": "184 + 43",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 227
    },
    {
        "question": "215 + 17",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 232
    },
    {
        "question": "366 + 29",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 395
    },
    {
        "question": "83 - 49",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 34
    },
    {
        "question": "202 x 29",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 5858
    },
    {
        "question": "234 x 35",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 8190
    },
    {
        "question": "167 - 53",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 114
    },
    {
        "question": "358 x 37",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 13246
    },
    {
        "question": "188 x 9",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1692
    },
    {
        "question": "182 x 77",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 14014
    },
    {
        "question": "179 - 21",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 158
    },
    {
        "question": "60 - 93",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -33
    },
    {
        "question": "41 x 73",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 2993
    },
    {
        "question": "206 - 53",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 153
    },
    {
        "question": "346 - 55",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 291
    },
    {
        "question": "101 x 71",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 7171
    },
    {
        "question": "166 - 9",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 157
    },
    {
        "question": "41 x 35",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1435
    },
    {
        "question": "250 x 7",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1750
    },
    {
        "question": "105 x 29",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 3045
    },
    {
        "question": "204 x 65",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 13260
    },
    {
        "question": "60 - 77",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -17
    },
    {
        "question": "310 - 59",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 251
    },
    {
        "question": "22 x 71",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1562
    },
    {
        "question": "210 - 41",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 169
    },
    {
        "question": "126 + 9",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 135
    },
    {
        "question": "71 + 39",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 110
    },
    {
        "question": "399 - 15",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 384
    },
    {
        "question": "366 + 3",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 369
    },
    {
        "question": "218 - 57",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 161
    },
    {
        "question": "350 x 89",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 31150
    },
    {
        "question": "224 x 21",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 4704
    },
    {
        "question": "376 x 53",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 19928
    },
    {
        "question": "273 - 95",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 178
    },
    {
        "question": "295 + 3",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 298
    },
    {
        "question": "44 + 7",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 51
    },
    {
        "question": "226 x 29",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 6554
    },
    {
        "question": "58 - 9",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 49
    },
    {
        "question": "306 - 65",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 241
    },
    {
        "question": "57 - 37",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 20
    },
    {
        "question": "27 - 89",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -62
    },
    {
        "question": "169 + 17",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 186
    },
    {
        "question": "71 - 13",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 58
    },
    {
        "question": "309 x 3",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 927
    },
    {
        "question": "34 + 25",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 59
    },
    {
        "question": "98 + 57",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 155
    },
    {
        "question": "215 x 87",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 18705
    },
    {
        "question": "99 + 77",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 176
    },
    {
        "question": "29 + 41",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 70
    },
    {
        "question": "92 + 27",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 119
    },
    {
        "question": "223 x 11",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 2453
    },
    {
        "question": "121 - 69",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 52
    },
    {
        "question": "359 + 99",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 458
    },
    {
        "question": "182 - 19",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 163
    },
    {
        "question": "372 x 9",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 3348
    },
    {
        "question": "302 + 77",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 379
    },
    {
        "question": "233 + 21",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 254
    },
    {
        "question": "24 + 5",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 29
    },
    {
        "question": "148 - 61",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 87
    },
    {
        "question": "225 + 21",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 246
    },
    {
        "question": "191 x 89",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 16999
    },
    {
        "question": "209 + 85",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 294
    },
    {
        "question": "99 x 55",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 5445
    },
    {
        "question": "261 - 47",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 214
    },
    {
        "question": "94 x 21",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1974
    },
    {
        "question": "335 - 83",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 252
    },
    {
        "question": "373 - 93",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 280
    },
    {
        "question": "13 - 53",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -40
    },
    {
        "question": "308 + 33",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 341
    },
    {
        "question": "338 x 93",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 31434
    },
    {
        "question": "383 - 39",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 344
    },
    {
        "question": "160 + 33",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 193
    },
    {
        "question": "89 - 69",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 20
    },
    {
        "question": "375 + 11",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 386
    },
    {
        "question": "272 - 85",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 187
    },
    {
        "question": "215 - 3",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 212
    },
    {
        "question": "183 - 33",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 150
    },
    {
        "question": "210 x 5",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1050
    },
    {
        "question": "251 + 31",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 282
    },
    {
        "question": "260 x 9",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 2340
    },
    {
        "question": "273 + 11",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 284
    },
    {
        "question": "270 + 71",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 341
    },
    {
        "question": "160 x 5",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 800
    },
    {
        "question": "239 + 5",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 244
    },
    {
        "question": "277 + 33",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 310
    },
    {
        "question": "230 + 97",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 327
    },
    {
        "question": "331 - 93",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 238
    },
    {
        "question": "102 - 93",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 9
    },
    {
        "question": "212 - 25",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 187
    },
    {
        "question": "77 x 73",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 5621
    },
    {
        "question": "368 + 47",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 415
    },
    {
        "question": "346 - 85",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 261
    },
    {
        "question": "293 + 95",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 388
    },
    {
        "question": "335 x 93",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 31155
    },
    {
        "question": "373 - 47",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 326
    },
    {
        "question": "192 - 41",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 151
    },
    {
        "question": "220 - 23",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 197
    },
    {
        "question": "244 - 63",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 181
    },
    {
        "question": "308 x 21",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 6468
    },
    {
        "question": "7 - 63",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -56
    },
    {
        "question": "143 - 39",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 104
    },
    {
        "question": "236 + 85",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 321
    },
    {
        "question": "306 - 49",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 257
    },
    {
        "question": "207 x 99",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 20493
    },
    {
        "question": "112 + 37",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 149
    },
    {
        "question": "217 + 27",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 244
    },
    {
        "question": "380 x 33",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 12540
    },
    {
        "question": "208 - 67",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 141
    },
    {
        "question": "235 - 29",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 206
    },
    {
        "question": "179 + 91",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 270
    },
    {
        "question": "333 x 59",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 19647
    },
    {
        "question": "212 + 77",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 289
    },
    {
        "question": "65 + 39",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 104
    },
    {
        "question": "368 - 83",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 285
    },
    {
        "question": "304 + 31",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 335
    },
    {
        "question": "145 x 71",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 10295
    },
    {
        "question": "284 + 91",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 375
    },
    {
        "question": "287 + 13",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 300
    },
    {
        "question": "313 x 47",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 14711
    },
    {
        "question": "83 - 33",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 50
    },
    {
        "question": "347 + 49",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 396
    },
    {
        "question": "107 - 91",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 16
    },
    {
        "question": "313 - 11",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 302
    },
    {
        "question": "162 + 79",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 241
    },
    {
        "question": "340 x 13",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 4420
    },
    {
        "question": "209 + 5",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 214
    },
    {
        "question": "253 - 21",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 232
    },
    {
        "question": "229 x 81",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 18549
    },
    {
        "question": "277 + 27",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 304
    },
    {
        "question": "228 - 89",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 139
    },
    {
        "question": "93 x 31",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 2883
    },
    {
        "question": "174 + 81",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 255
    },
    {
        "question": "63 - 71",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -8
    },
    {
        "question": "341 x 15",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 5115
    },
    {
        "question": "185 - 53",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 132
    },
    {
        "question": "97 + 75",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 172
    },
    {
        "question": "373 + 47",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 420
    },
    {
        "question": "229 - 47",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 182
    },
    {
        "question": "336 - 13",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 323
    },
    {
        "question": "80 - 51",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 29
    },
    {
        "question": "205 x 55",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 11275
    },
    {
        "question": "275 x 43",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 11825
    },
    {
        "question": "287 x 5",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1435
    },
    {
        "question": "156 + 29",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 185
    },
    {
        "question": "251 + 39",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 290
    },
    {
        "question": "233 + 43",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 276
    },
    {
        "question": "286 - 17",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 269
    },
    {
        "question": "24 - 65",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -41
    },
    {
        "question": "324 + 25",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 349
    },
    {
        "question": "19 + 67",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 86
    },
    {
        "question": "128 + 37",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 165
    },
    {
        "question": "381 x 13",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 4953
    },
    {
        "question": "116 x 95",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 11020
    },
    {
        "question": "131 - 55",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 76
    },
    {
        "question": "186 x 29",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 5394
    },
    {
        "question": "27 x 71",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1917
    },
    {
        "question": "236 + 21",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 257
    },
    {
        "question": "53 + 83",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 136
    },
    {
        "question": "376 + 53",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 429
    },
    {
        "question": "276 + 19",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 295
    },
    {
        "question": "377 x 45",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 16965
    },
    {
        "question": "307 x 65",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 19955
    },
    {
        "question": "151 x 79",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 11929
    },
    {
        "question": "268 + 99",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 367
    },
    {
        "question": "216 - 29",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 187
    },
    {
        "question": "227 + 13",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 240
    },
    {
        "question": "25 x 69",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1725
    },
    {
        "question": "107 - 39",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 68
    },
    {
        "question": "333 + 45",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 378
    },
    {
        "question": "20 - 41",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -21
    },
    {
        "question": "112 x 95",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 10640
    },
    {
        "question": "47 - 87",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -40
    },
    {
        "question": "164 x 37",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 6068
    },
    {
        "question": "346 x 73",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 25258
    },
    {
        "question": "249 - 97",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 152
    },
    {
        "question": "382 x 77",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 29414
    },
    {
        "question": "97 x 57",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 5529
    },
    {
        "question": "291 - 27",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 264
    },
    {
        "question": "123 x 29",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 3567
    },
    {
        "question": "156 - 35",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 121
    },
    {
        "question": "219 x 95",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 20805
    },
    {
        "question": "79 + 79",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 158
    },
    {
        "question": "375 x 61",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 22875
    },
    {
        "question": "20 x 33",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 660
    },
    {
        "question": "174 x 31",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 5394
    },
    {
        "question": "289 - 63",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 226
    },
    {
        "question": "353 - 37",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 316
    },
    {
        "question": "298 - 25",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 273
    },
    {
        "question": "266 + 73",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 339
    },
    {
        "question": "259 x 59",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 15281
    },
    {
        "question": "323 - 33",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 290
    },
    {
        "question": "257 + 57",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 314
    },
    {
        "question": "372 + 13",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 385
    },
    {
        "question": "77 x 73",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 5621
    },
    {
        "question": "326 + 79",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 405
    },
    {
        "question": "373 - 75",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 298
    },
    {
        "question": "173 x 17",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 2941
    },
    {
        "question": "58 x 33",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1914
    },
    {
        "question": "302 + 99",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 401
    },
    {
        "question": "164 - 25",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 139
    },
    {
        "question": "338 + 15",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 353
    },
    {
        "question": "100 - 89",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 11
    },
    {
        "question": "218 x 41",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 8938
    },
    {
        "question": "358 + 69",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 427
    },
    {
        "question": "5 + 89",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 94
    },
    {
        "question": "238 - 59",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 179
    },
    {
        "question": "307 + 57",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 364
    },
    {
        "question": "351 x 99",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 34749
    },
    {
        "question": "31 - 3",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 28
    },
    {
        "question": "302 - 23",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 279
    },
    {
        "question": "287 - 45",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 242
    },
    {
        "question": "152 - 39",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 113
    },
    {
        "question": "170 - 89",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 81
    },
    {
        "question": "231 x 37",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 8547
    },
    {
        "question": "55 + 89",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 144
    },
    {
        "question": "13 - 41",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -28
    },
    {
        "question": "145 - 43",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 102
    },
    {
        "question": "119 - 23",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 96
    },
    {
        "question": "377 x 11",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 4147
    },
    {
        "question": "390 + 43",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 433
    },
    {
        "question": "242 - 67",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 175
    },
    {
        "question": "123 x 37",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 4551
    },
    {
        "question": "30 x 25",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 750
    },
    {
        "question": "219 + 73",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 292
    },
    {
        "question": "396 + 45",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 441
    },
    {
        "question": "78 x 83",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 6474
    },
    {
        "question": "325 - 97",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 228
    },
    {
        "question": "304 + 21",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 325
    },
    {
        "question": "301 - 49",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 252
    },
    {
        "question": "118 x 47",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 5546
    },
    {
        "question": "55 x 93",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 5115
    },
    {
        "question": "36 + 37",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 73
    },
    {
        "question": "257 + 49",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 306
    },
    {
        "question": "373 x 41",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 15293
    },
    {
        "question": "335 + 91",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 426
    },
    {
        "question": "280 x 39",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 10920
    },
    {
        "question": "165 - 93",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 72
    },
    {
        "question": "68 - 83",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -15
    },
    {
        "question": "8 x 27",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 216
    },
    {
        "question": "132 x 93",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 12276
    },
    {
        "question": "22 - 63",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -41
    },
    {
        "question": "304 + 5",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 309
    },
    {
        "question": "196 - 41",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 155
    },
    {
        "question": "232 + 5",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 237
    },
    {
        "question": "251 x 31",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 7781
    },
    {
        "question": "360 - 89",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 271
    },
    {
        "question": "186 + 65",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 251
    },
    {
        "question": "287 + 59",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 346
    },
    {
        "question": "270 - 7",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 263
    },
    {
        "question": "187 x 87",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 16269
    },
    {
        "question": "213 + 11",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 224
    },
    {
        "question": "69 + 29",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 98
    },
    {
        "question": "149 - 25",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 124
    },
    {
        "question": "277 - 11",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 266
    },
    {
        "question": "218 + 95",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 313
    },
    {
        "question": "20 - 35",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -15
    },
    {
        "question": "389 - 79",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 310
    },
    {
        "question": "125 x 7",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 875
    },
    {
        "question": "217 x 47",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 10199
    },
    {
        "question": "19 x 25",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 475
    },
    {
        "question": "255 + 7",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 262
    },
    {
        "question": "215 x 29",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 6235
    },
    {
        "question": "273 x 97",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 26481
    },
    {
        "question": "202 - 21",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 181
    },
    {
        "question": "341 + 63",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 404
    },
    {
        "question": "256 x 85",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 21760
    },
    {
        "question": "164 - 21",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 143
    },
    {
        "question": "326 - 47",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 279
    },
    {
        "question": "204 - 25",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 179
    },
    {
        "question": "150 - 23",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 127
    },
    {
        "question": "307 + 43",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 350
    },
    {
        "question": "64 - 1",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 63
    },
    {
        "question": "287 x 61",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 17507
    },
    {
        "question": "104 - 81",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 23
    },
    {
        "question": "9 - 35",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -26
    },
    {
        "question": "106 + 91",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 197
    },
    {
        "question": "355 - 15",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 340
    },
    {
        "question": "59 - 27",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 32
    },
    {
        "question": "10 - 79",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -69
    },
    {
        "question": "358 - 9",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 349
    },
    {
        "question": "352 x 45",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 15840
    },
    {
        "question": "341 - 11",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 330
    },
    {
        "question": "393 + 17",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 410
    },
    {
        "question": "74 + 71",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 145
    },
    {
        "question": "289 - 15",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 274
    },
    {
        "question": "112 - 43",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 69
    },
    {
        "question": "309 x 79",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 24411
    },
    {
        "question": "220 x 17",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 3740
    },
    {
        "question": "310 x 47",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 14570
    },
    {
        "question": "295 + 27",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 322
    },
    {
        "question": "212 x 75",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 15900
    },
    {
        "question": "117 - 65",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 52
    },
    {
        "question": "171 - 67",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 104
    },
    {
        "question": "357 + 45",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 402
    },
    {
        "question": "143 - 49",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 94
    },
    {
        "question": "108 - 9",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 99
    },
    {
        "question": "66 - 71",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -5
    },
    {
        "question": "157 x 79",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 12403
    },
    {
        "question": "280 - 59",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 221
    },
    {
        "question": "260 - 3",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 257
    },
    {
        "question": "214 x 25",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 5350
    },
    {
        "question": "73 + 65",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 138
    },
    {
        "question": "175 + 7",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 182
    },
    {
        "question": "169 - 5",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 164
    },
    {
        "question": "167 - 19",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 148
    },
    {
        "question": "300 - 19",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 281
    },
    {
        "question": "120 x 39",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 4680
    },
    {
        "question": "339 - 57",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 282
    },
    {
        "question": "315 - 13",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 302
    },
    {
        "question": "75 - 29",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 46
    },
    {
        "question": "6 x 35",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 210
    },
    {
        "question": "316 x 51",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 16116
    },
    {
        "question": "43 x 33",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1419
    },
    {
        "question": "323 + 91",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 414
    },
    {
        "question": "364 + 69",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 433
    },
    {
        "question": "77 - 65",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 12
    },
    {
        "question": "303 + 69",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 372
    },
    {
        "question": "329 x 53",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 17437
    },
    {
        "question": "203 x 43",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 8729
    },
    {
        "question": "36 - 43",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -7
    },
    {
        "question": "162 - 9",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 153
    },
    {
        "question": "253 - 43",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 210
    },
    {
        "question": "209 - 79",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 130
    },
    {
        "question": "292 - 17",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 275
    },
    {
        "question": "205 - 85",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 120
    },
    {
        "question": "93 + 39",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 132
    },
    {
        "question": "40 - 41",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -1
    },
    {
        "question": "322 x 93",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 29946
    },
    {
        "question": "355 + 89",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 444
    },
    {
        "question": "221 + 49",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 270
    },
    {
        "question": "92 x 35",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 3220
    },
    {
        "question": "343 + 85",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 428
    },
    {
        "question": "162 x 29",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 4698
    },
    {
        "question": "391 - 41",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 350
    },
    {
        "question": "303 + 73",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 376
    },
    {
        "question": "74 + 53",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 127
    },
    {
        "question": "398 - 97",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 301
    },
    {
        "question": "112 x 29",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 3248
    },
    {
        "question": "38 - 23",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 15
    },
    {
        "question": "333 - 13",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 320
    },
    {
        "question": "69 + 53",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 122
    },
    {
        "question": "119 + 1",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 120
    },
    {
        "question": "90 + 65",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 155
    },
    {
        "question": "15 x 71",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1065
    },
    {
        "question": "358 + 59",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 417
    },
    {
        "question": "261 - 75",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 186
    },
    {
        "question": "112 - 21",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 91
    },
    {
        "question": "354 + 15",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 369
    },
    {
        "question": "226 x 1",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 226
    },
    {
        "question": "307 x 69",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 21183
    },
    {
        "question": "289 x 73",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 21097
    },
    {
        "question": "266 + 85",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 351
    },
    {
        "question": "116 + 11",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 127
    },
    {
        "question": "394 - 39",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 355
    },
    {
        "question": "315 - 55",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 260
    },
    {
        "question": "57 + 87",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 144
    },
    {
        "question": "319 + 35",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 354
    },
    {
        "question": "25 + 93",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 118
    },
    {
        "question": "157 x 7",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1099
    },
    {
        "question": "182 x 35",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 6370
    },
    {
        "question": "297 x 23",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 6831
    },
    {
        "question": "307 - 35",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 272
    },
    {
        "question": "308 - 25",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 283
    },
    {
        "question": "57 - 99",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -42
    },
    {
        "question": "74 + 31",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 105
    },
    {
        "question": "177 - 83",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 94
    },
    {
        "question": "216 x 59",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 12744
    },
    {
        "question": "211 - 19",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 192
    },
    {
        "question": "28 + 73",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 101
    },
    {
        "question": "374 + 87",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 461
    },
    {
        "question": "354 - 69",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 285
    },
    {
        "question": "304 + 67",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 371
    },
    {
        "question": "118 + 57",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 175
    },
    {
        "question": "92 + 5",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 97
    },
    {
        "question": "394 + 87",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 481
    },
    {
        "question": "321 x 57",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 18297
    },
    {
        "question": "194 + 99",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 293
    },
    {
        "question": "395 - 3",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 392
    },
    {
        "question": "249 - 83",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 166
    },
    {
        "question": "354 + 79",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 433
    },
    {
        "question": "199 - 55",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 144
    },
    {
        "question": "199 x 1",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 199
    },
    {
        "question": "27 - 27",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 0
    },
    {
        "question": "49 - 23",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 26
    },
    {
        "question": "348 + 25",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 373
    },
    {
        "question": "164 - 9",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 155
    },
    {
        "question": "339 x 9",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 3051
    },
    {
        "question": "388 - 33",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 355
    },
    {
        "question": "180 x 39",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 7020
    },
    {
        "question": "193 x 63",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 12159
    },
    {
        "question": "54 + 31",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 85
    },
    {
        "question": "269 + 43",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 312
    },
    {
        "question": "325 + 85",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 410
    },
    {
        "question": "148 - 37",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 111
    },
    {
        "question": "103 + 51",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 154
    },
    {
        "question": "393 x 19",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 7467
    },
    {
        "question": "153 + 59",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 212
    },
    {
        "question": "280 - 71",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 209
    },
    {
        "question": "262 + 31",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 293
    },
    {
        "question": "259 - 21",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 238
    },
    {
        "question": "356 x 77",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 27412
    },
    {
        "question": "106 + 5",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 111
    },
    {
        "question": "133 x 69",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 9177
    },
    {
        "question": "114 x 67",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 7638
    },
    {
        "question": "45 x 95",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 4275
    },
    {
        "question": "61 x 51",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 3111
    },
    {
        "question": "238 - 77",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 161
    },
    {
        "question": "180 - 49",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 131
    },
    {
        "question": "43 - 97",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -54
    },
    {
        "question": "176 - 1",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 175
    },
    {
        "question": "197 + 95",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 292
    },
    {
        "question": "334 + 81",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 415
    },
    {
        "question": "323 - 5",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 318
    },
    {
        "question": "393 - 53",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 340
    },
    {
        "question": "64 x 5",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 320
    },
    {
        "question": "274 + 99",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 373
    },
    {
        "question": "55 + 3",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 58
    },
    {
        "question": "149 + 59",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 208
    },
    {
        "question": "322 + 31",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 353
    },
    {
        "question": "33 x 91",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 3003
    },
    {
        "question": "24 x 71",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1704
    },
    {
        "question": "62 - 99",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -37
    },
    {
        "question": "254 - 61",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 193
    },
    {
        "question": "176 + 31",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 207
    },
    {
        "question": "395 - 1",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 394
    },
    {
        "question": "397 - 11",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 386
    },
    {
        "question": "214 - 83",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 131
    },
    {
        "question": "376 + 23",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 399
    },
    {
        "question": "210 x 85",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 17850
    },
    {
        "question": "23 + 81",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 104
    },
    {
        "question": "248 x 41",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 10168
    },
    {
        "question": "239 + 69",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 308
    },
    {
        "question": "376 + 15",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 391
    },
    {
        "question": "266 - 85",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 181
    },
    {
        "question": "390 x 21",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 8190
    },
    {
        "question": "389 - 87",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 302
    },
    {
        "question": "397 - 85",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 312
    },
    {
        "question": "255 + 47",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 302
    },
    {
        "question": "320 + 39",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 359
    },
    {
        "question": "254 x 93",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 23622
    },
    {
        "question": "156 - 61",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 95
    },
    {
        "question": "122 x 9",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1098
    },
    {
        "question": "356 x 45",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 16020
    },
    {
        "question": "354 x 29",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 10266
    },
    {
        "question": "382 x 9",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 3438
    },
    {
        "question": "334 x 51",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 17034
    },
    {
        "question": "235 - 79",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 156
    },
    {
        "question": "212 x 59",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 12508
    },
    {
        "question": "16 x 77",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1232
    },
    {
        "question": "313 + 37",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 350
    },
    {
        "question": "239 - 11",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 228
    },
    {
        "question": "321 - 61",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 260
    },
    {
        "question": "365 + 67",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 432
    },
    {
        "question": "264 - 95",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 169
    },
    {
        "question": "79 x 25",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1975
    },
    {
        "question": "196 - 41",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 155
    },
    {
        "question": "170 - 43",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 127
    },
    {
        "question": "167 - 49",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 118
    },
    {
        "question": "272 x 45",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 12240
    },
    {
        "question": "319 + 11",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 330
    },
    {
        "question": "346 - 97",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 249
    },
    {
        "question": "122 x 53",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 6466
    },
    {
        "question": "19 - 91",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -72
    },
    {
        "question": "320 + 33",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 353
    },
    {
        "question": "63 - 79",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -16
    },
    {
        "question": "235 - 49",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 186
    },
    {
        "question": "84 + 13",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 97
    },
    {
        "question": "288 + 33",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 321
    },
    {
        "question": "40 x 51",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 2040
    },
    {
        "question": "174 x 81",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 14094
    },
    {
        "question": "394 + 23",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 417
    },
    {
        "question": "11 - 79",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -68
    },
    {
        "question": "354 + 5",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 359
    },
    {
        "question": "29 x 33",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 957
    },
    {
        "question": "379 x 53",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 20087
    },
    {
        "question": "325 - 27",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 298
    },
    {
        "question": "44 + 67",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 111
    },
    {
        "question": "81 + 43",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 124
    },
    {
        "question": "111 - 63",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 48
    },
    {
        "question": "250 x 65",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 16250
    },
    {
        "question": "362 x 57",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 20634
    },
    {
        "question": "281 + 3",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 284
    },
    {
        "question": "76 + 35",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 111
    },
    {
        "question": "298 + 53",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 351
    },
    {
        "question": "336 + 83",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 419
    },
    {
        "question": "106 x 9",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 954
    },
    {
        "question": "132 + 69",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 201
    },
    {
        "question": "67 - 69",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -2
    },
    {
        "question": "52 - 73",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -21
    },
    {
        "question": "67 + 65",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 132
    },
    {
        "question": "40 + 77",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 117
    },
    {
        "question": "339 + 7",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 346
    },
    {
        "question": "103 x 71",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 7313
    },
    {
        "question": "232 - 7",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 225
    },
    {
        "question": "347 x 89",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 30883
    },
    {
        "question": "245 x 79",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 19355
    },
    {
        "question": "72 - 73",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -1
    },
    {
        "question": "84 + 71",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 155
    },
    {
        "question": "11 x 1",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 11
    },
    {
        "question": "394 - 43",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 351
    },
    {
        "question": "294 + 65",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 359
    },
    {
        "question": "367 + 13",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 380
    },
    {
        "question": "44 + 27",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 71
    },
    {
        "question": "6 - 85",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -79
    },
    {
        "question": "48 x 67",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 3216
    },
    {
        "question": "205 + 65",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 270
    },
    {
        "question": "191 - 5",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 186
    },
    {
        "question": "138 + 55",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 193
    },
    {
        "question": "103 + 83",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 186
    },
    {
        "question": "74 - 31",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 43
    },
    {
        "question": "210 + 95",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 305
    },
    {
        "question": "23 - 37",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -14
    },
    {
        "question": "144 - 69",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 75
    },
    {
        "question": "212 x 57",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 12084
    },
    {
        "question": "370 - 65",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 305
    },
    {
        "question": "324 + 3",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 327
    },
    {
        "question": "256 x 25",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 6400
    },
    {
        "question": "75 x 77",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 5775
    },
    {
        "question": "95 + 39",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 134
    },
    {
        "question": "331 x 1",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 331
    },
    {
        "question": "396 - 97",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 299
    },
    {
        "question": "21 x 85",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1785
    },
    {
        "question": "155 + 89",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 244
    },
    {
        "question": "223 + 75",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 298
    },
    {
        "question": "384 - 33",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 351
    },
    {
        "question": "130 - 11",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 119
    },
    {
        "question": "152 x 29",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 4408
    },
    {
        "question": "390 + 93",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 483
    },
    {
        "question": "99 + 71",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 170
    },
    {
        "question": "22 x 21",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 462
    },
    {
        "question": "159 x 79",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 12561
    },
    {
        "question": "8 + 43",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 51
    },
    {
        "question": "333 - 79",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 254
    },
    {
        "question": "127 x 33",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 4191
    },
    {
        "question": "136 - 77",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 59
    },
    {
        "question": "285 x 11",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 3135
    },
    {
        "question": "174 - 79",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 95
    },
    {
        "question": "391 x 51",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 19941
    },
    {
        "question": "98 x 11",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1078
    },
    {
        "question": "150 - 75",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 75
    },
    {
        "question": "285 x 61",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 17385
    },
    {
        "question": "368 x 83",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 30544
    },
    {
        "question": "47 + 45",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 92
    },
    {
        "question": "280 x 81",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 22680
    },
    {
        "question": "120 x 77",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 9240
    },
    {
        "question": "253 - 33",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 220
    },
    {
        "question": "65 x 95",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 6175
    },
    {
        "question": "33 + 75",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 108
    },
    {
        "question": "162 + 85",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 247
    },
    {
        "question": "184 + 65",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 249
    },
    {
        "question": "333 - 29",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 304
    },
    {
        "question": "170 x 15",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 2550
    },
    {
        "question": "282 x 11",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 3102
    },
    {
        "question": "157 - 23",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 134
    },
    {
        "question": "343 + 37",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 380
    },
    {
        "question": "131 x 49",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 6419
    },
    {
        "question": "78 - 55",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 23
    },
    {
        "question": "2 + 31",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 33
    },
    {
        "question": "334 - 29",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 305
    },
    {
        "question": "172 - 17",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 155
    },
    {
        "question": "174 x 99",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 17226
    },
    {
        "question": "305 - 1",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 304
    },
    {
        "question": "399 - 7",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 392
    },
    {
        "question": "270 + 25",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 295
    },
    {
        "question": "136 - 41",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 95
    },
    {
        "question": "359 + 29",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 388
    },
    {
        "question": "179 + 97",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 276
    },
    {
        "question": "235 + 81",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 316
    },
    {
        "question": "334 - 1",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 333
    },
    {
        "question": "238 x 65",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 15470
    },
    {
        "question": "261 + 95",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 356
    },
    {
        "question": "71 - 1",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 70
    },
    {
        "question": "279 - 47",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 232
    },
    {
        "question": "278 x 1",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 278
    },
    {
        "question": "145 x 11",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1595
    },
    {
        "question": "277 - 47",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 230
    },
    {
        "question": "144 - 3",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 141
    },
    {
        "question": "266 x 25",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 6650
    },
    {
        "question": "109 + 19",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 128
    },
    {
        "question": "316 + 9",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 325
    },
    {
        "question": "298 - 93",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 205
    },
    {
        "question": "292 + 77",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 369
    },
    {
        "question": "267 + 87",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 354
    },
    {
        "question": "301 x 89",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 26789
    },
    {
        "question": "39 - 37",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "19 - 93",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -74
    },
    {
        "question": "79 x 19",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1501
    },
    {
        "question": "49 - 13",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 36
    },
    {
        "question": "187 x 13",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 2431
    },
    {
        "question": "264 - 21",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 243
    },
    {
        "question": "87 + 81",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 168
    },
    {
        "question": "365 - 5",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 360
    },
    {
        "question": "212 + 11",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 223
    },
    {
        "question": "343 + 59",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 402
    },
    {
        "question": "133 - 73",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 60
    },
    {
        "question": "168 + 77",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 245
    },
    {
        "question": "77 - 97",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -20
    },
    {
        "question": "71 x 59",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 4189
    },
    {
        "question": "278 - 81",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 197
    },
    {
        "question": "250 - 13",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 237
    },
    {
        "question": "168 - 17",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 151
    },
    {
        "question": "186 + 75",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 261
    },
    {
        "question": "277 + 39",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 316
    },
    {
        "question": "112 + 77",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 189
    },
    {
        "question": "329 x 41",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 13489
    },
    {
        "question": "148 - 81",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 67
    },
    {
        "question": "311 x 93",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 28923
    },
    {
        "question": "315 + 27",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 342
    },
    {
        "question": "219 x 13",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 2847
    },
    {
        "question": "356 + 1",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 357
    },
    {
        "question": "370 x 7",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 2590
    },
    {
        "question": "266 - 11",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 255
    },
    {
        "question": "138 - 69",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 69
    },
    {
        "question": "203 x 5",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1015
    },
    {
        "question": "51 x 35",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1785
    },
    {
        "question": "115 x 75",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 8625
    },
    {
        "question": "222 + 9",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 231
    },
    {
        "question": "386 - 55",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 331
    },
    {
        "question": "86 + 55",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 141
    },
    {
        "question": "213 - 53",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 160
    },
    {
        "question": "256 x 91",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 23296
    },
    {
        "question": "38 - 63",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -25
    },
    {
        "question": "245 - 79",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 166
    },
    {
        "question": "344 + 85",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 429
    },
    {
        "question": "212 x 61",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 12932
    },
    {
        "question": "317 + 21",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 338
    },
    {
        "question": "172 x 95",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 16340
    },
    {
        "question": "231 + 47",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 278
    },
    {
        "question": "210 x 75",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 15750
    },
    {
        "question": "318 + 65",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 383
    },
    {
        "question": "267 + 43",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 310
    },
    {
        "question": "16 + 21",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 37
    },
    {
        "question": "2 x 1",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "346 x 33",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 11418
    },
    {
        "question": "63 x 7",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 441
    },
    {
        "question": "325 - 73",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 252
    },
    {
        "question": "321 - 47",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 274
    },
    {
        "question": "251 x 3",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 753
    },
    {
        "question": "212 + 39",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 251
    },
    {
        "question": "140 x 19",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 2660
    },
    {
        "question": "280 - 81",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 199
    },
    {
        "question": "352 - 33",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 319
    },
    {
        "question": "358 - 21",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 337
    },
    {
        "question": "51 + 37",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 88
    },
    {
        "question": "199 - 97",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 102
    },
    {
        "question": "88 x 53",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 4664
    },
    {
        "question": "96 - 35",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 61
    },
    {
        "question": "351 + 93",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 444
    },
    {
        "question": "292 x 73",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 21316
    },
    {
        "question": "25 + 91",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 116
    },
    {
        "question": "29 x 41",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1189
    },
    {
        "question": "204 + 21",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 225
    },
    {
        "question": "171 + 29",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 200
    },
    {
        "question": "102 + 13",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 115
    },
    {
        "question": "129 + 53",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 182
    },
    {
        "question": "187 - 57",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 130
    },
    {
        "question": "133 x 23",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 3059
    },
    {
        "question": "97 x 87",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 8439
    },
    {
        "question": "62 - 75",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -13
    },
    {
        "question": "346 + 3",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 349
    },
    {
        "question": "151 + 23",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 174
    },
    {
        "question": "210 + 91",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 301
    },
    {
        "question": "243 + 5",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 248
    },
    {
        "question": "370 x 41",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 15170
    },
    {
        "question": "375 + 65",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 440
    },
    {
        "question": "247 - 59",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 188
    },
    {
        "question": "29 x 1",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 29
    },
    {
        "question": "131 x 49",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 6419
    },
    {
        "question": "163 x 73",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 11899
    },
    {
        "question": "11 - 87",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -76
    },
    {
        "question": "231 x 53",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 12243
    },
    {
        "question": "259 - 35",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 224
    },
    {
        "question": "273 + 23",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 296
    },
    {
        "question": "334 + 29",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 363
    },
    {
        "question": "188 - 37",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 151
    },
    {
        "question": "254 + 91",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 345
    },
    {
        "question": "240 - 69",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 171
    },
    {
        "question": "362 x 63",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 22806
    },
    {
        "question": "183 x 11",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 2013
    },
    {
        "question": "22 + 67",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 89
    },
    {
        "question": "246 x 7",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1722
    },
    {
        "question": "393 - 11",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 382
    },
    {
        "question": "6 - 11",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -5
    },
    {
        "question": "163 - 67",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 96
    },
    {
        "question": "158 - 63",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 95
    },
    {
        "question": "130 x 23",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 2990
    },
    {
        "question": "151 x 15",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 2265
    },
    {
        "question": "120 x 35",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 4200
    },
    {
        "question": "306 - 77",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 229
    },
    {
        "question": "84 + 57",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 141
    },
    {
        "question": "30 - 95",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -65
    },
    {
        "question": "341 x 61",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 20801
    },
    {
        "question": "75 x 19",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1425
    },
    {
        "question": "155 x 23",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 3565
    },
    {
        "question": "109 - 77",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 32
    },
    {
        "question": "112 x 87",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 9744
    },
    {
        "question": "212 - 79",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 133
    },
    {
        "question": "63 x 61",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 3843
    },
    {
        "question": "251 - 45",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 206
    },
    {
        "question": "24 - 11",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 13
    },
    {
        "question": "294 - 79",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 215
    },
    {
        "question": "72 - 95",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -23
    },
    {
        "question": "270 x 73",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 19710
    },
    {
        "question": "225 x 5",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1125
    },
    {
        "question": "289 - 83",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 206
    },
    {
        "question": "277 - 93",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 184
    },
    {
        "question": "382 + 55",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 437
    },
    {
        "question": "243 x 37",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 8991
    },
    {
        "question": "112 x 83",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 9296
    },
    {
        "question": "29 x 21",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 609
    },
    {
        "question": "306 + 47",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 353
    },
    {
        "question": "353 + 85",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 438
    },
    {
        "question": "38 x 63",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 2394
    },
    {
        "question": "91 x 59",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 5369
    },
    {
        "question": "362 - 37",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 325
    },
    {
        "question": "196 x 81",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 15876
    },
    {
        "question": "136 - 53",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 83
    },
    {
        "question": "94 x 61",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 5734
    },
    {
        "question": "31 x 31",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 961
    },
    {
        "question": "333 x 79",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 26307
    },
    {
        "question": "325 + 63",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 388
    },
    {
        "question": "289 - 17",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 272
    },
    {
        "question": "105 x 73",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 7665
    },
    {
        "question": "292 + 83",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 375
    },
    {
        "question": "13 + 23",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 36
    },
    {
        "question": "395 - 67",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 328
    },
    {
        "question": "329 + 29",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 358
    },
    {
        "question": "253 x 25",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 6325
    },
    {
        "question": "47 + 65",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 112
    },
    {
        "question": "397 x 87",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 34539
    },
    {
        "question": "331 + 67",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 398
    },
    {
        "question": "25 + 13",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 38
    },
    {
        "question": "82 + 21",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 103
    },
    {
        "question": "169 + 41",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 210
    },
    {
        "question": "63 - 41",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 22
    },
    {
        "question": "136 - 81",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 55
    },
    {
        "question": "279 + 9",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 288
    },
    {
        "question": "33 - 97",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -64
    },
    {
        "question": "26 - 7",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 19
    },
    {
        "question": "241 + 27",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 268
    },
    {
        "question": "1 + 39",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 40
    },
    {
        "question": "359 x 75",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 26925
    },
    {
        "question": "106 - 45",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 61
    },
    {
        "question": "246 - 25",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 221
    },
    {
        "question": "67 - 75",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -8
    },
    {
        "question": "291 + 51",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 342
    },
    {
        "question": "75 - 37",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 38
    },
    {
        "question": "363 + 1",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 364
    },
    {
        "question": "282 x 67",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 18894
    },
    {
        "question": "285 + 27",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 312
    },
    {
        "question": "176 x 55",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 9680
    },
    {
        "question": "201 x 55",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 11055
    },
    {
        "question": "161 - 23",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 138
    },
    {
        "question": "218 - 91",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 127
    },
    {
        "question": "20 - 1",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 19
    },
    {
        "question": "9 - 51",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -42
    },
    {
        "question": "35 + 73",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 108
    },
    {
        "question": "203 - 43",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 160
    },
    {
        "question": "5 x 45",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 225
    },
    {
        "question": "336 - 99",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 237
    },
    {
        "question": "257 + 73",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 330
    },
    {
        "question": "73 - 95",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -22
    },
    {
        "question": "289 + 93",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 382
    },
    {
        "question": "300 + 57",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 357
    },
    {
        "question": "292 - 15",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 277
    },
    {
        "question": "187 - 65",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 122
    },
    {
        "question": "91 + 93",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 184
    },
    {
        "question": "220 x 17",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 3740
    },
    {
        "question": "249 x 27",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 6723
    },
    {
        "question": "309 - 49",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 260
    },
    {
        "question": "342 x 37",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 12654
    },
    {
        "question": "66 + 65",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 131
    },
    {
        "question": "364 x 91",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 33124
    },
    {
        "question": "264 - 1",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 263
    },
    {
        "question": "220 + 89",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 309
    },
    {
        "question": "53 x 29",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1537
    },
    {
        "question": "166 - 55",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 111
    },
    {
        "question": "58 - 3",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 55
    },
    {
        "question": "42 - 67",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -25
    },
    {
        "question": "259 + 13",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 272
    },
    {
        "question": "130 - 59",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 71
    },
    {
        "question": "206 + 85",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 291
    },
    {
        "question": "38 + 17",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 55
    },
    {
        "question": "169 x 53",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 8957
    },
    {
        "question": "359 - 5",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 354
    },
    {
        "question": "380 x 13",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 4940
    },
    {
        "question": "317 + 91",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 408
    },
    {
        "question": "390 - 21",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 369
    },
    {
        "question": "307 + 71",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 378
    },
    {
        "question": "24 x 89",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 2136
    },
    {
        "question": "212 + 77",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 289
    },
    {
        "question": "145 x 49",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 7105
    },
    {
        "question": "372 x 91",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 33852
    },
    {
        "question": "161 - 17",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 144
    },
    {
        "question": "363 x 73",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 26499
    },
    {
        "question": "72 x 49",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 3528
    },
    {
        "question": "87 + 67",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 154
    },
    {
        "question": "91 x 69",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 6279
    },
    {
        "question": "319 x 63",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 20097
    },
    {
        "question": "334 x 11",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 3674
    },
    {
        "question": "329 + 23",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 352
    },
    {
        "question": "176 + 89",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 265
    },
    {
        "question": "229 x 99",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 22671
    },
    {
        "question": "17 + 95",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 112
    },
    {
        "question": "95 + 17",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 112
    },
    {
        "question": "260 - 51",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 209
    },
    {
        "question": "99 x 85",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 8415
    },
    {
        "question": "120 - 7",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 113
    },
    {
        "question": "384 x 57",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 21888
    },
    {
        "question": "390 x 89",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 34710
    },
    {
        "question": "260 x 7",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1820
    },
    {
        "question": "255 - 25",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 230
    },
    {
        "question": "366 + 7",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 373
    },
    {
        "question": "379 - 85",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 294
    },
    {
        "question": "232 + 31",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 263
    },
    {
        "question": "222 - 73",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 149
    },
    {
        "question": "92 x 73",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 6716
    },
    {
        "question": "324 - 3",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 321
    },
    {
        "question": "210 + 93",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 303
    },
    {
        "question": "2 x 31",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 62
    },
    {
        "question": "327 + 71",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 398
    },
    {
        "question": "231 + 1",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 232
    },
    {
        "question": "172 x 95",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 16340
    },
    {
        "question": "128 x 59",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 7552
    },
    {
        "question": "159 + 79",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 238
    },
    {
        "question": "12 + 47",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 59
    },
    {
        "question": "54 x 1",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 54
    },
    {
        "question": "279 - 57",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 222
    },
    {
        "question": "240 + 61",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 301
    },
    {
        "question": "16 + 61",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 77
    },
    {
        "question": "138 - 29",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 109
    },
    {
        "question": "7 - 17",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -10
    },
    {
        "question": "334 x 89",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 29726
    },
    {
        "question": "146 x 21",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 3066
    },
    {
        "question": "153 + 35",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 188
    },
    {
        "question": "23 + 77",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 100
    },
    {
        "question": "132 - 57",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 75
    },
    {
        "question": "150 + 55",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 205
    },
    {
        "question": "285 x 55",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 15675
    },
    {
        "question": "304 + 17",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 321
    },
    {
        "question": "261 x 43",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 11223
    },
    {
        "question": "46 - 15",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 31
    },
    {
        "question": "113 - 11",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 102
    },
    {
        "question": "299 x 57",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 17043
    },
    {
        "question": "16 + 99",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 115
    },
    {
        "question": "305 x 69",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 21045
    },
    {
        "question": "231 + 79",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 310
    },
    {
        "question": "58 x 1",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 58
    },
    {
        "question": "3 - 15",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -12
    },
    {
        "question": "71 + 27",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 98
    },
    {
        "question": "174 - 57",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 117
    },
    {
        "question": "277 + 21",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 298
    },
    {
        "question": "320 - 19",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 301
    },
    {
        "question": "255 + 55",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 310
    },
    {
        "question": "90 + 47",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 137
    },
    {
        "question": "34 - 55",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -21
    },
    {
        "question": "211 x 43",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 9073
    },
    {
        "question": "248 + 97",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 345
    },
    {
        "question": "366 x 47",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 17202
    },
    {
        "question": "150 x 67",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 10050
    },
    {
        "question": "326 - 95",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 231
    },
    {
        "question": "27 - 79",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -52
    },
    {
        "question": "380 x 53",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 20140
    },
    {
        "question": "63 - 19",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 44
    },
    {
        "question": "136 - 33",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 103
    },
    {
        "question": "4 - 93",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -89
    },
    {
        "question": "333 x 45",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 14985
    },
    {
        "question": "199 - 65",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 134
    },
    {
        "question": "386 x 15",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 5790
    },
    {
        "question": "188 - 73",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 115
    },
    {
        "question": "346 x 89",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 30794
    },
    {
        "question": "252 x 93",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 23436
    },
    {
        "question": "127 x 35",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 4445
    },
    {
        "question": "329 - 49",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 280
    },
    {
        "question": "327 x 59",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 19293
    },
    {
        "question": "17 x 47",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 799
    },
    {
        "question": "77 x 59",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 4543
    },
    {
        "question": "52 x 27",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1404
    },
    {
        "question": "291 x 69",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 20079
    },
    {
        "question": "268 x 13",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 3484
    },
    {
        "question": "277 + 79",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 356
    },
    {
        "question": "263 + 19",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 282
    },
    {
        "question": "232 + 51",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 283
    },
    {
        "question": "338 + 73",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 411
    },
    {
        "question": "377 + 53",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 430
    },
    {
        "question": "189 - 95",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 94
    },
    {
        "question": "257 - 31",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 226
    },
    {
        "question": "247 - 39",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 208
    },
    {
        "question": "342 - 49",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 293
    },
    {
        "question": "310 x 85",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 26350
    },
    {
        "question": "219 - 19",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 200
    },
    {
        "question": "290 - 85",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 205
    },
    {
        "question": "115 - 5",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 110
    },
    {
        "question": "11 - 35",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -24
    },
    {
        "question": "119 x 7",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 833
    },
    {
        "question": "58 x 67",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 3886
    },
    {
        "question": "379 - 1",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 378
    },
    {
        "question": "232 x 9",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 2088
    },
    {
        "question": "352 x 69",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 24288
    },
    {
        "question": "128 + 1",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 129
    },
    {
        "question": "76 - 7",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 69
    },
    {
        "question": "106 x 41",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 4346
    },
    {
        "question": "213 + 89",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 302
    },
    {
        "question": "203 x 57",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 11571
    },
    {
        "question": "386 - 33",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 353
    },
    {
        "question": "234 x 55",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 12870
    },
    {
        "question": "232 - 63",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 169
    },
    {
        "question": "261 + 11",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 272
    },
    {
        "question": "3 - 5",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -2
    },
    {
        "question": "162 + 43",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 205
    },
    {
        "question": "35 x 85",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 2975
    },
    {
        "question": "194 + 75",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 269
    },
    {
        "question": "160 x 9",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1440
    },
    {
        "question": "1 - 63",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -62
    },
    {
        "question": "257 + 19",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 276
    },
    {
        "question": "306 - 43",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 263
    },
    {
        "question": "40 - 19",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 21
    },
    {
        "question": "384 + 59",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 443
    },
    {
        "question": "95 - 37",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 58
    },
    {
        "question": "379 + 63",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 442
    },
    {
        "question": "292 - 81",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 211
    },
    {
        "question": "203 - 11",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 192
    },
    {
        "question": "73 + 61",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 134
    },
    {
        "question": "16 x 85",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1360
    },
    {
        "question": "384 x 27",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 10368
    },
    {
        "question": "162 - 17",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 145
    },
    {
        "question": "231 + 95",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 326
    },
    {
        "question": "316 + 45",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 361
    },
    {
        "question": "182 x 37",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 6734
    },
    {
        "question": "351 + 81",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 432
    },
    {
        "question": "171 + 99",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 270
    },
    {
        "question": "99 x 73",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 7227
    },
    {
        "question": "170 + 83",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 253
    },
    {
        "question": "125 + 85",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 210
    },
    {
        "question": "233 + 63",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 296
    },
    {
        "question": "378 - 55",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 323
    },
    {
        "question": "267 x 65",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 17355
    },
    {
        "question": "178 - 93",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 85
    },
    {
        "question": "80 + 15",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 95
    },
    {
        "question": "278 + 1",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 279
    },
    {
        "question": "232 + 21",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 253
    },
    {
        "question": "382 - 19",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 363
    },
    {
        "question": "267 x 9",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 2403
    },
    {
        "question": "283 + 97",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 380
    },
    {
        "question": "368 + 93",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 461
    },
    {
        "question": "261 - 15",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 246
    },
    {
        "question": "295 x 33",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 9735
    },
    {
        "question": "107 + 43",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 150
    },
    {
        "question": "301 x 61",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 18361
    },
    {
        "question": "29 x 11",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 319
    },
    {
        "question": "378 x 83",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 31374
    },
    {
        "question": "186 + 61",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 247
    },
    {
        "question": "297 x 45",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 13365
    },
    {
        "question": "203 + 5",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 208
    },
    {
        "question": "236 + 13",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 249
    },
    {
        "question": "307 - 17",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 290
    },
    {
        "question": "226 + 75",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 301
    },
    {
        "question": "143 + 29",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 172
    },
    {
        "question": "286 - 49",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 237
    },
    {
        "question": "108 x 57",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 6156
    },
    {
        "question": "165 x 79",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 13035
    },
    {
        "question": "152 - 91",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 61
    },
    {
        "question": "381 - 55",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 326
    },
    {
        "question": "292 x 29",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 8468
    },
    {
        "question": "391 + 27",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 418
    },
    {
        "question": "31 - 89",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -58
    },
    {
        "question": "68 - 55",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 13
    },
    {
        "question": "336 + 25",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 361
    },
    {
        "question": "275 - 11",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 264
    },
    {
        "question": "70 x 81",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 5670
    },
    {
        "question": "216 - 65",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 151
    },
    {
        "question": "272 + 15",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 287
    },
    {
        "question": "373 - 27",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 346
    },
    {
        "question": "230 + 95",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 325
    },
    {
        "question": "247 x 43",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 10621
    },
    {
        "question": "109 x 21",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 2289
    },
    {
        "question": "56 + 73",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 129
    },
    {
        "question": "125 - 99",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 26
    },
    {
        "question": "194 - 53",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 141
    },
    {
        "question": "371 - 13",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 358
    },
    {
        "question": "361 - 23",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 338
    },
    {
        "question": "377 - 69",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 308
    },
    {
        "question": "44 + 61",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 105
    },
    {
        "question": "342 x 23",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 7866
    },
    {
        "question": "240 - 57",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 183
    },
    {
        "question": "63 - 7",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 56
    },
    {
        "question": "119 + 55",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 174
    },
    {
        "question": "88 - 7",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 81
    },
    {
        "question": "224 - 35",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 189
    },
    {
        "question": "42 x 85",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 3570
    },
    {
        "question": "362 - 63",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 299
    },
    {
        "question": "237 - 75",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 162
    },
    {
        "question": "124 x 57",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 7068
    },
    {
        "question": "93 + 83",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 176
    },
    {
        "question": "243 - 97",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 146
    },
    {
        "question": "45 - 67",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -22
    },
    {
        "question": "56 - 91",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -35
    },
    {
        "question": "12 x 39",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 468
    },
    {
        "question": "62 x 95",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 5890
    },
    {
        "question": "295 x 35",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 10325
    },
    {
        "question": "218 - 1",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 217
    },
    {
        "question": "121 - 7",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 114
    },
    {
        "question": "334 - 65",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 269
    },
    {
        "question": "365 - 1",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 364
    },
    {
        "question": "139 x 71",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 9869
    },
    {
        "question": "77 x 13",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1001
    },
    {
        "question": "248 + 37",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 285
    },
    {
        "question": "156 - 61",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 95
    },
    {
        "question": "70 - 13",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 57
    },
    {
        "question": "19 x 49",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 931
    },
    {
        "question": "183 - 15",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 168
    },
    {
        "question": "248 - 99",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 149
    },
    {
        "question": "126 + 85",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 211
    },
    {
        "question": "269 + 99",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 368
    },
    {
        "question": "41 - 53",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -12
    },
    {
        "question": "113 + 75",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 188
    },
    {
        "question": "51 + 3",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 54
    },
    {
        "question": "206 + 59",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 265
    },
    {
        "question": "182 x 93",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 16926
    },
    {
        "question": "349 + 45",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 394
    },
    {
        "question": "89 x 55",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 4895
    },
    {
        "question": "68 + 69",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 137
    },
    {
        "question": "162 - 73",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 89
    },
    {
        "question": "337 - 87",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 250
    },
    {
        "question": "49 + 21",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 70
    },
    {
        "question": "164 + 57",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 221
    },
    {
        "question": "309 + 69",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 378
    },
    {
        "question": "309 x 7",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 2163
    },
    {
        "question": "186 - 53",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 133
    },
    {
        "question": "267 - 1",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 266
    },
    {
        "question": "236 - 51",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 185
    },
    {
        "question": "339 + 37",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 376
    },
    {
        "question": "179 - 71",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 108
    },
    {
        "question": "15 x 61",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 915
    },
    {
        "question": "19 + 37",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 56
    },
    {
        "question": "116 - 49",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 67
    },
    {
        "question": "148 - 97",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 51
    },
    {
        "question": "102 - 83",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 19
    },
    {
        "question": "371 + 87",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 458
    },
    {
        "question": "239 x 73",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 17447
    },
    {
        "question": "61 - 39",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 22
    },
    {
        "question": "53 x 95",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 5035
    },
    {
        "question": "218 + 65",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 283
    },
    {
        "question": "327 - 19",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 308
    },
    {
        "question": "388 x 67",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 25996
    },
    {
        "question": "54 + 81",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 135
    },
    {
        "question": "394 - 85",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 309
    },
    {
        "question": "214 - 3",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 211
    },
    {
        "question": "165 x 35",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 5775
    },
    {
        "question": "171 + 41",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 212
    },
    {
        "question": "136 + 35",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 171
    },
    {
        "question": "70 + 57",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 127
    },
    {
        "question": "43 x 49",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 2107
    },
    {
        "question": "365 - 65",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 300
    },
    {
        "question": "154 + 35",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 189
    },
    {
        "question": "324 + 77",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 401
    },
    {
        "question": "243 - 67",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 176
    },
    {
        "question": "392 x 15",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 5880
    },
    {
        "question": "109 - 57",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 52
    },
    {
        "question": "25 - 95",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -70
    },
    {
        "question": "16 + 19",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 35
    },
    {
        "question": "110 - 93",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 17
    },
    {
        "question": "274 + 47",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 321
    },
    {
        "question": "41 x 71",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 2911
    },
    {
        "question": "159 x 55",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 8745
    },
    {
        "question": "330 x 3",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 990
    },
    {
        "question": "16 - 25",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -9
    },
    {
        "question": "121 x 71",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 8591
    },
    {
        "question": "180 x 9",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1620
    },
    {
        "question": "83 x 59",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 4897
    },
    {
        "question": "218 - 93",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 125
    },
    {
        "question": "172 + 35",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 207
    },
    {
        "question": "204 + 13",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 217
    },
    {
        "question": "18 + 83",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 101
    },
    {
        "question": "378 - 41",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 337
    },
    {
        "question": "176 x 47",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 8272
    },
    {
        "question": "306 - 39",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 267
    },
    {
        "question": "179 - 83",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 96
    },
    {
        "question": "178 x 41",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 7298
    },
    {
        "question": "233 - 95",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 138
    },
    {
        "question": "50 x 33",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1650
    },
    {
        "question": "132 + 47",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 179
    },
    {
        "question": "73 x 89",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 6497
    },
    {
        "question": "16 - 71",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -55
    },
    {
        "question": "223 + 51",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 274
    },
    {
        "question": "27 + 61",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 88
    },
    {
        "question": "151 + 35",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 186
    },
    {
        "question": "375 - 67",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 308
    },
    {
        "question": "275 x 81",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 22275
    },
    {
        "question": "245 x 7",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1715
    },
    {
        "question": "158 + 79",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 237
    },
    {
        "question": "167 - 75",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 92
    },
    {
        "question": "263 x 41",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 10783
    },
    {
        "question": "4 - 47",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -43
    },
    {
        "question": "282 x 35",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 9870
    },
    {
        "question": "149 x 57",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 8493
    },
    {
        "question": "20 - 79",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -59
    },
    {
        "question": "330 x 37",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 12210
    },
    {
        "question": "368 + 61",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 429
    },
    {
        "question": "327 + 83",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 410
    },
    {
        "question": "127 + 3",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 130
    },
    {
        "question": "129 - 47",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 82
    },
    {
        "question": "391 - 3",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 388
    },
    {
        "question": "60 x 53",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 3180
    },
    {
        "question": "378 x 75",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 28350
    },
    {
        "question": "370 - 17",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 353
    },
    {
        "question": "320 - 45",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 275
    },
    {
        "question": "267 x 5",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1335
    },
    {
        "question": "318 + 97",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 415
    },
    {
        "question": "383 + 71",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 454
    },
    {
        "question": "338 x 47",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 15886
    },
    {
        "question": "198 + 7",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 205
    },
    {
        "question": "215 x 21",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 4515
    },
    {
        "question": "271 + 37",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 308
    },
    {
        "question": "84 - 21",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 63
    },
    {
        "question": "216 + 45",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 261
    },
    {
        "question": "389 x 31",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 12059
    },
    {
        "question": "257 + 25",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 282
    },
    {
        "question": "138 - 21",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 117
    },
    {
        "question": "125 x 31",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 3875
    },
    {
        "question": "285 - 59",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 226
    },
    {
        "question": "83 x 91",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 7553
    },
    {
        "question": "109 - 29",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 80
    },
    {
        "question": "305 + 31",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 336
    },
    {
        "question": "115 - 95",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 20
    },
    {
        "question": "56 + 63",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 119
    },
    {
        "question": "250 - 11",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 239
    },
    {
        "question": "261 x 9",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 2349
    },
    {
        "question": "215 x 55",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 11825
    },
    {
        "question": "170 - 27",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 143
    },
    {
        "question": "247 x 43",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 10621
    },
    {
        "question": "79 + 15",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 94
    },
    {
        "question": "356 x 51",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 18156
    },
    {
        "question": "186 + 63",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 249
    },
    {
        "question": "287 - 55",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 232
    },
    {
        "question": "134 + 99",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 233
    },
    {
        "question": "330 x 11",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 3630
    },
    {
        "question": "99 + 61",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 160
    },
    {
        "question": "162 x 73",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 11826
    },
    {
        "question": "341 x 59",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 20119
    },
    {
        "question": "342 + 25",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 367
    },
    {
        "question": "313 x 99",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 30987
    },
    {
        "question": "39 x 47",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1833
    },
    {
        "question": "12 - 97",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -85
    },
    {
        "question": "192 - 39",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 153
    },
    {
        "question": "163 x 53",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 8639
    },
    {
        "question": "127 - 63",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 64
    },
    {
        "question": "221 - 91",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 130
    },
    {
        "question": "33 x 39",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1287
    },
    {
        "question": "299 - 19",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 280
    },
    {
        "question": "115 x 17",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1955
    },
    {
        "question": "173 - 39",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 134
    },
    {
        "question": "14 + 53",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 67
    },
    {
        "question": "285 + 13",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 298
    },
    {
        "question": "36 - 39",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -3
    },
    {
        "question": "313 + 71",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 384
    },
    {
        "question": "107 x 27",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 2889
    },
    {
        "question": "47 - 7",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 40
    },
    {
        "question": "150 x 9",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1350
    },
    {
        "question": "103 x 17",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1751
    },
    {
        "question": "68 - 43",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 25
    },
    {
        "question": "162 + 77",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 239
    },
    {
        "question": "67 x 47",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 3149
    },
    {
        "question": "341 + 57",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 398
    },
    {
        "question": "12 x 81",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 972
    },
    {
        "question": "143 x 25",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 3575
    },
    {
        "question": "163 - 83",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 80
    },
    {
        "question": "307 - 25",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 282
    },
    {
        "question": "285 - 67",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 218
    },
    {
        "question": "254 + 51",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 305
    },
    {
        "question": "39 + 19",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 58
    },
    {
        "question": "280 - 75",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 205
    },
    {
        "question": "282 - 49",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 233
    },
    {
        "question": "53 x 47",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 2491
    },
    {
        "question": "275 - 69",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 206
    },
    {
        "question": "123 x 31",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 3813
    },
    {
        "question": "333 + 19",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 352
    },
    {
        "question": "328 x 27",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 8856
    },
    {
        "question": "212 - 49",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 163
    },
    {
        "question": "326 + 67",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 393
    },
    {
        "question": "331 + 53",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 384
    },
    {
        "question": "201 + 35",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 236
    },
    {
        "question": "15 - 87",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -72
    },
    {
        "question": "195 + 77",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 272
    },
    {
        "question": "371 + 57",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 428
    },
    {
        "question": "72 - 57",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 15
    },
    {
        "question": "148 + 47",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 195
    },
    {
        "question": "33 - 27",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 6
    },
    {
        "question": "346 - 19",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 327
    },
    {
        "question": "158 + 89",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 247
    },
    {
        "question": "336 + 39",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 375
    },
    {
        "question": "1 - 69",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -68
    },
    {
        "question": "77 - 45",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 32
    },
    {
        "question": "195 + 73",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 268
    },
    {
        "question": "360 + 41",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 401
    },
    {
        "question": "351 + 57",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 408
    },
    {
        "question": "381 - 33",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 348
    },
    {
        "question": "151 + 61",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 212
    },
    {
        "question": "374 + 21",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 395
    },
    {
        "question": "161 x 39",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 6279
    },
    {
        "question": "335 + 37",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 372
    },
    {
        "question": "88 + 51",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 139
    },
    {
        "question": "239 - 7",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 232
    },
    {
        "question": "11 x 95",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1045
    },
    {
        "question": "166 - 69",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 97
    },
    {
        "question": "279 - 75",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 204
    },
    {
        "question": "128 - 3",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 125
    },
    {
        "question": "215 x 85",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 18275
    },
    {
        "question": "299 + 79",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 378
    },
    {
        "question": "340 - 83",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 257
    },
    {
        "question": "159 x 19",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 3021
    },
    {
        "question": "332 + 65",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 397
    },
    {
        "question": "175 - 49",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 126
    },
    {
        "question": "252 - 83",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 169
    },
    {
        "question": "212 + 39",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 251
    },
    {
        "question": "258 - 75",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 183
    },
    {
        "question": "97 x 19",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1843
    },
    {
        "question": "22 x 87",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1914
    },
    {
        "question": "162 + 73",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 235
    },
    {
        "question": "190 - 91",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 99
    },
    {
        "question": "262 x 51",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 13362
    },
    {
        "question": "16 + 23",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 39
    },
    {
        "question": "73 + 73",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 146
    },
    {
        "question": "47 + 95",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 142
    },
    {
        "question": "319 + 59",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 378
    },
    {
        "question": "343 x 73",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 25039
    },
    {
        "question": "246 x 33",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 8118
    },
    {
        "question": "308 x 97",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 29876
    },
    {
        "question": "297 - 93",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 204
    },
    {
        "question": "335 - 73",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 262
    },
    {
        "question": "88 x 37",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 3256
    },
    {
        "question": "74 x 33",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 2442
    },
    {
        "question": "244 - 75",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 169
    },
    {
        "question": "133 x 23",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 3059
    },
    {
        "question": "367 + 47",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 414
    },
    {
        "question": "257 - 29",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 228
    },
    {
        "question": "52 x 39",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 2028
    },
    {
        "question": "173 + 93",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 266
    },
    {
        "question": "82 - 3",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 79
    },
    {
        "question": "18 + 39",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 57
    },
    {
        "question": "332 x 13",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 4316
    },
    {
        "question": "13 x 11",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 143
    },
    {
        "question": "309 + 31",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 340
    },
    {
        "question": "201 - 33",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 168
    },
    {
        "question": "1 x 41",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 41
    },
    {
        "question": "12 + 11",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 23
    },
    {
        "question": "177 x 59",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 10443
    },
    {
        "question": "301 x 3",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 903
    },
    {
        "question": "259 - 83",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 176
    },
    {
        "question": "136 - 59",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 77
    },
    {
        "question": "211 - 23",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 188
    },
    {
        "question": "245 + 23",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 268
    },
    {
        "question": "196 x 63",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 12348
    },
    {
        "question": "362 - 79",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 283
    },
    {
        "question": "250 + 17",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 267
    },
    {
        "question": "110 + 37",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 147
    },
    {
        "question": "223 + 33",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 256
    },
    {
        "question": "169 + 27",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 196
    },
    {
        "question": "396 - 79",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 317
    },
    {
        "question": "38 + 23",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 61
    },
    {
        "question": "346 - 41",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 305
    },
    {
        "question": "36 x 97",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 3492
    },
    {
        "question": "140 x 45",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 6300
    },
    {
        "question": "167 - 89",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 78
    },
    {
        "question": "2 - 95",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -93
    },
    {
        "question": "264 + 41",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 305
    },
    {
        "question": "204 + 83",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 287
    },
    {
        "question": "348 - 9",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 339
    },
    {
        "question": "89 + 17",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 106
    },
    {
        "question": "109 x 53",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 5777
    },
    {
        "question": "93 - 1",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 92
    },
    {
        "question": "77 + 91",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 168
    },
    {
        "question": "27 - 69",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -42
    },
    {
        "question": "216 x 97",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 20952
    },
    {
        "question": "16 + 17",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 33
    },
    {
        "question": "241 x 55",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 13255
    },
    {
        "question": "1 x 95",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 95
    },
    {
        "question": "270 - 17",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 253
    },
    {
        "question": "342 + 3",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 345
    },
    {
        "question": "149 - 83",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 66
    },
    {
        "question": "177 - 1",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 176
    },
    {
        "question": "313 + 41",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 354
    },
    {
        "question": "130 - 67",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 63
    },
    {
        "question": "354 x 61",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 21594
    },
    {
        "question": "238 x 45",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 10710
    },
    {
        "question": "109 + 71",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 180
    },
    {
        "question": "304 + 35",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 339
    },
    {
        "question": "364 - 33",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 331
    },
    {
        "question": "170 + 37",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 207
    },
    {
        "question": "35 x 75",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 2625
    },
    {
        "question": "222 + 27",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 249
    },
    {
        "question": "246 + 17",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 263
    },
    {
        "question": "198 + 7",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 205
    },
    {
        "question": "264 + 75",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 339
    },
    {
        "question": "206 - 47",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 159
    },
    {
        "question": "165 x 57",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 9405
    },
    {
        "question": "268 + 95",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 363
    },
    {
        "question": "73 x 1",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 73
    },
    {
        "question": "72 x 99",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 7128
    },
    {
        "question": "91 + 65",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 156
    },
    {
        "question": "371 + 87",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 458
    },
    {
        "question": "118 - 65",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 53
    },
    {
        "question": "344 x 79",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 27176
    },
    {
        "question": "127 x 9",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1143
    },
    {
        "question": "212 + 31",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 243
    },
    {
        "question": "272 - 81",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 191
    },
    {
        "question": "386 - 95",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 291
    },
    {
        "question": "297 - 57",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 240
    },
    {
        "question": "211 + 79",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 290
    },
    {
        "question": "1 x 85",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 85
    },
    {
        "question": "183 - 33",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 150
    },
    {
        "question": "123 - 75",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 48
    },
    {
        "question": "60 - 9",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 51
    },
    {
        "question": "54 + 81",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 135
    },
    {
        "question": "305 - 27",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 278
    },
    {
        "question": "202 + 17",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 219
    },
    {
        "question": "145 - 31",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 114
    },
    {
        "question": "163 - 27",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 136
    },
    {
        "question": "60 x 93",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 5580
    },
    {
        "question": "267 x 67",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 17889
    },
    {
        "question": "361 x 7",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 2527
    },
    {
        "question": "355 - 15",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 340
    },
    {
        "question": "174 - 71",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 103
    },
    {
        "question": "86 + 35",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 121
    },
    {
        "question": "132 + 7",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 139
    },
    {
        "question": "318 x 89",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 28302
    },
    {
        "question": "217 - 85",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 132
    },
    {
        "question": "155 - 13",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 142
    },
    {
        "question": "336 + 17",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 353
    },
    {
        "question": "368 x 83",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 30544
    },
    {
        "question": "321 + 5",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 326
    },
    {
        "question": "106 x 15",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1590
    },
    {
        "question": "227 - 19",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 208
    },
    {
        "question": "108 + 9",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 117
    },
    {
        "question": "263 + 23",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 286
    },
    {
        "question": "265 + 39",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 304
    },
    {
        "question": "204 x 25",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 5100
    },
    {
        "question": "15 + 55",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 70
    },
    {
        "question": "196 x 17",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 3332
    },
    {
        "question": "334 + 95",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 429
    },
    {
        "question": "59 x 27",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1593
    },
    {
        "question": "345 x 53",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 18285
    },
    {
        "question": "180 x 49",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 8820
    },
    {
        "question": "213 x 77",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 16401
    },
    {
        "question": "327 x 61",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 19947
    },
    {
        "question": "112 + 91",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 203
    },
    {
        "question": "291 - 55",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 236
    },
    {
        "question": "60 - 27",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 33
    },
    {
        "question": "293 - 99",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 194
    },
    {
        "question": "285 x 57",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 16245
    },
    {
        "question": "259 x 7",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1813
    },
    {
        "question": "382 - 31",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 351
    },
    {
        "question": "199 - 99",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 100
    },
    {
        "question": "146 + 7",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 153
    },
    {
        "question": "139 + 33",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 172
    },
    {
        "question": "135 + 31",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 166
    },
    {
        "question": "288 - 43",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 245
    },
    {
        "question": "317 - 77",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 240
    },
    {
        "question": "340 - 31",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 309
    },
    {
        "question": "194 x 53",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 10282
    },
    {
        "question": "360 x 99",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 35640
    },
    {
        "question": "227 x 1",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 227
    },
    {
        "question": "381 x 15",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 5715
    },
    {
        "question": "258 + 33",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 291
    },
    {
        "question": "267 + 15",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 282
    },
    {
        "question": "243 - 69",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 174
    },
    {
        "question": "275 - 35",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 240
    },
    {
        "question": "211 x 7",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1477
    },
    {
        "question": "147 - 79",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 68
    },
    {
        "question": "115 x 97",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 11155
    },
    {
        "question": "114 x 33",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 3762
    },
    {
        "question": "347 x 71",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 24637
    },
    {
        "question": "209 + 43",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 252
    },
    {
        "question": "185 - 77",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 108
    },
    {
        "question": "157 - 41",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 116
    },
    {
        "question": "243 x 47",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 11421
    },
    {
        "question": "118 + 25",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 143
    },
    {
        "question": "246 - 99",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 147
    },
    {
        "question": "26 x 47",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1222
    },
    {
        "question": "245 x 45",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 11025
    },
    {
        "question": "394 + 21",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 415
    },
    {
        "question": "176 - 93",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 83
    },
    {
        "question": "150 x 5",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 750
    },
    {
        "question": "164 x 7",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1148
    },
    {
        "question": "203 - 85",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 118
    },
    {
        "question": "397 x 83",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 32951
    },
    {
        "question": "160 - 97",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 63
    },
    {
        "question": "345 x 5",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1725
    },
    {
        "question": "257 - 15",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 242
    },
    {
        "question": "340 x 27",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 9180
    },
    {
        "question": "228 x 81",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 18468
    },
    {
        "question": "378 + 97",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 475
    },
    {
        "question": "149 + 55",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 204
    },
    {
        "question": "372 + 31",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 403
    },
    {
        "question": "306 x 99",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 30294
    },
    {
        "question": "289 x 39",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 11271
    },
    {
        "question": "324 x 59",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 19116
    },
    {
        "question": "8 x 69",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 552
    },
    {
        "question": "47 x 99",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 4653
    },
    {
        "question": "224 - 63",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 161
    },
    {
        "question": "209 - 45",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 164
    },
    {
        "question": "399 x 49",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 19551
    },
    {
        "question": "373 x 11",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 4103
    },
    {
        "question": "203 - 21",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 182
    },
    {
        "question": "150 - 67",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 83
    },
    {
        "question": "348 - 47",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 301
    },
    {
        "question": "79 - 63",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 16
    },
    {
        "question": "364 + 17",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 381
    },
    {
        "question": "32 - 79",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -47
    },
    {
        "question": "151 + 17",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 168
    },
    {
        "question": "205 - 81",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 124
    },
    {
        "question": "344 x 17",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 5848
    },
    {
        "question": "49 - 67",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -18
    },
    {
        "question": "92 - 69",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 23
    },
    {
        "question": "391 x 71",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 27761
    },
    {
        "question": "203 - 97",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 106
    },
    {
        "question": "140 x 5",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 700
    },
    {
        "question": "395 - 73",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 322
    },
    {
        "question": "345 - 29",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 316
    },
    {
        "question": "205 + 75",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 280
    },
    {
        "question": "317 x 43",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 13631
    },
    {
        "question": "104 + 63",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 167
    },
    {
        "question": "279 - 5",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 274
    },
    {
        "question": "282 - 3",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 279
    },
    {
        "question": "160 x 69",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 11040
    },
    {
        "question": "295 + 77",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 372
    },
    {
        "question": "176 + 57",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 233
    },
    {
        "question": "368 x 19",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 6992
    },
    {
        "question": "366 x 45",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 16470
    },
    {
        "question": "318 + 31",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 349
    },
    {
        "question": "345 - 73",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 272
    },
    {
        "question": "361 + 65",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 426
    },
    {
        "question": "318 x 25",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 7950
    },
    {
        "question": "223 + 19",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 242
    },
    {
        "question": "357 x 21",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 7497
    },
    {
        "question": "298 x 23",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 6854
    },
    {
        "question": "100 x 79",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 7900
    },
    {
        "question": "35 + 35",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 70
    },
    {
        "question": "171 x 49",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 8379
    },
    {
        "question": "398 - 35",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 363
    },
    {
        "question": "125 x 41",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 5125
    },
    {
        "question": "115 + 75",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 190
    },
    {
        "question": "118 + 69",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 187
    },
    {
        "question": "394 x 3",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1182
    },
    {
        "question": "15 + 91",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 106
    },
    {
        "question": "285 x 89",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 25365
    },
    {
        "question": "266 + 97",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 363
    },
    {
        "question": "22 + 69",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 91
    },
    {
        "question": "110 x 89",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 9790
    },
    {
        "question": "379 - 73",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 306
    },
    {
        "question": "73 x 69",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 5037
    },
    {
        "question": "222 x 7",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1554
    },
    {
        "question": "255 + 95",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 350
    },
    {
        "question": "174 - 63",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 111
    },
    {
        "question": "122 x 29",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 3538
    },
    {
        "question": "235 + 23",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 258
    },
    {
        "question": "120 + 93",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 213
    },
    {
        "question": "6 + 17",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 23
    },
    {
        "question": "19 - 93",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -74
    },
    {
        "question": "58 + 77",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 135
    },
    {
        "question": "19 - 81",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -62
    },
    {
        "question": "393 x 25",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 9825
    },
    {
        "question": "202 + 3",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 205
    },
    {
        "question": "24 - 41",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -17
    },
    {
        "question": "39 - 49",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -10
    },
    {
        "question": "120 + 53",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 173
    },
    {
        "question": "54 + 3",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 57
    },
    {
        "question": "55 + 43",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 98
    },
    {
        "question": "143 + 65",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 208
    },
    {
        "question": "272 - 29",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 243
    },
    {
        "question": "66 x 27",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1782
    },
    {
        "question": "26 - 79",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -53
    },
    {
        "question": "91 x 83",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 7553
    },
    {
        "question": "169 x 25",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 4225
    },
    {
        "question": "102 - 3",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 99
    },
    {
        "question": "221 - 77",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 144
    },
    {
        "question": "75 x 79",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 5925
    },
    {
        "question": "150 + 67",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 217
    },
    {
        "question": "240 - 43",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 197
    },
    {
        "question": "367 x 31",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 11377
    },
    {
        "question": "312 + 19",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 331
    },
    {
        "question": "155 - 67",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 88
    },
    {
        "question": "278 + 19",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 297
    },
    {
        "question": "354 - 79",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 275
    },
    {
        "question": "300 - 25",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 275
    },
    {
        "question": "11 x 73",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 803
    },
    {
        "question": "124 + 23",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 147
    },
    {
        "question": "128 + 73",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 201
    },
    {
        "question": "287 x 25",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 7175
    },
    {
        "question": "54 x 61",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 3294
    },
    {
        "question": "203 + 67",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 270
    },
    {
        "question": "124 + 75",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 199
    },
    {
        "question": "190 x 75",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 14250
    },
    {
        "question": "192 + 19",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 211
    },
    {
        "question": "289 x 41",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 11849
    },
    {
        "question": "352 x 65",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 22880
    },
    {
        "question": "152 + 79",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 231
    },
    {
        "question": "278 + 75",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 353
    },
    {
        "question": "26 + 39",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 65
    },
    {
        "question": "31 x 97",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 3007
    },
    {
        "question": "278 x 31",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 8618
    },
    {
        "question": "77 - 3",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 74
    },
    {
        "question": "165 x 47",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 7755
    },
    {
        "question": "289 x 27",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 7803
    },
    {
        "question": "250 + 21",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 271
    },
    {
        "question": "61 x 61",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 3721
    },
    {
        "question": "251 + 17",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 268
    },
    {
        "question": "265 + 83",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 348
    },
    {
        "question": "26 x 51",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1326
    },
    {
        "question": "372 + 53",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 425
    },
    {
        "question": "101 + 67",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 168
    },
    {
        "question": "159 x 21",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 3339
    },
    {
        "question": "325 - 25",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 300
    },
    {
        "question": "134 + 61",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 195
    },
    {
        "question": "74 + 37",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 111
    },
    {
        "question": "45 x 37",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1665
    },
    {
        "question": "124 - 57",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 67
    },
    {
        "question": "331 x 63",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 20853
    },
    {
        "question": "319 + 75",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 394
    },
    {
        "question": "366 + 95",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 461
    },
    {
        "question": "37 + 97",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 134
    },
    {
        "question": "248 x 61",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 15128
    },
    {
        "question": "148 - 17",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 131
    },
    {
        "question": "276 x 77",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 21252
    },
    {
        "question": "151 + 23",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 174
    },
    {
        "question": "88 - 1",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 87
    },
    {
        "question": "109 x 79",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 8611
    },
    {
        "question": "159 + 51",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 210
    },
    {
        "question": "97 x 23",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 2231
    },
    {
        "question": "327 + 77",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 404
    },
    {
        "question": "199 - 63",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 136
    },
    {
        "question": "66 + 31",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 97
    },
    {
        "question": "135 + 25",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 160
    },
    {
        "question": "141 x 43",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 6063
    },
    {
        "question": "39 - 33",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 6
    },
    {
        "question": "167 - 73",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 94
    },
    {
        "question": "308 x 53",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 16324
    },
    {
        "question": "95 x 57",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 5415
    },
    {
        "question": "336 + 65",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 401
    },
    {
        "question": "253 + 17",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 270
    },
    {
        "question": "278 x 29",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 8062
    },
    {
        "question": "166 - 91",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 75
    },
    {
        "question": "374 - 19",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 355
    },
    {
        "question": "188 x 67",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 12596
    },
    {
        "question": "392 x 1",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 392
    },
    {
        "question": "130 + 37",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 167
    },
    {
        "question": "376 x 45",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 16920
    },
    {
        "question": "35 x 49",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1715
    },
    {
        "question": "185 x 57",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 10545
    },
    {
        "question": "320 x 47",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 15040
    },
    {
        "question": "154 + 57",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 211
    },
    {
        "question": "234 x 89",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 20826
    },
    {
        "question": "110 + 55",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 165
    },
    {
        "question": "98 - 65",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 33
    },
    {
        "question": "64 - 93",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -29
    },
    {
        "question": "171 x 35",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 5985
    },
    {
        "question": "222 - 73",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 149
    },
    {
        "question": "364 - 85",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 279
    },
    {
        "question": "213 x 49",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 10437
    },
    {
        "question": "272 x 33",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 8976
    },
    {
        "question": "161 + 29",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 190
    },
    {
        "question": "99 - 73",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 26
    },
    {
        "question": "343 x 39",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 13377
    },
    {
        "question": "396 x 85",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 33660
    },
    {
        "question": "64 x 1",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 64
    },
    {
        "question": "226 x 41",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 9266
    },
    {
        "question": "294 x 85",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 24990
    },
    {
        "question": "233 x 15",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 3495
    },
    {
        "question": "107 x 5",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 535
    },
    {
        "question": "92 - 53",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 39
    },
    {
        "question": "5 + 9",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 14
    },
    {
        "question": "71 x 43",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 3053
    },
    {
        "question": "263 x 3",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 789
    },
    {
        "question": "392 - 67",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 325
    },
    {
        "question": "271 + 91",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 362
    },
    {
        "question": "121 + 39",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 160
    },
    {
        "question": "348 + 11",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 359
    },
    {
        "question": "200 - 7",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 193
    },
    {
        "question": "265 - 11",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 254
    },
    {
        "question": "154 - 41",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 113
    },
    {
        "question": "109 - 21",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 88
    },
    {
        "question": "133 x 45",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 5985
    },
    {
        "question": "10 - 55",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -45
    },
    {
        "question": "38 x 1",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 38
    },
    {
        "question": "330 - 15",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 315
    },
    {
        "question": "311 - 85",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 226
    },
    {
        "question": "57 - 77",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -20
    },
    {
        "question": "357 - 71",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 286
    },
    {
        "question": "187 - 21",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 166
    },
    {
        "question": "127 + 59",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 186
    },
    {
        "question": "66 + 69",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 135
    },
    {
        "question": "129 x 9",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1161
    },
    {
        "question": "155 - 19",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 136
    },
    {
        "question": "180 + 25",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 205
    },
    {
        "question": "128 + 65",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 193
    },
    {
        "question": "328 + 53",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 381
    },
    {
        "question": "11 + 19",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 30
    },
    {
        "question": "58 - 29",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 29
    },
    {
        "question": "233 x 29",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 6757
    },
    {
        "question": "391 x 19",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 7429
    },
    {
        "question": "81 + 39",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 120
    },
    {
        "question": "224 x 29",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 6496
    },
    {
        "question": "189 + 37",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 226
    },
    {
        "question": "82 - 73",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 9
    },
    {
        "question": "319 + 15",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 334
    },
    {
        "question": "379 - 33",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 346
    },
    {
        "question": "144 + 57",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 201
    },
    {
        "question": "184 - 93",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 91
    },
    {
        "question": "352 x 83",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 29216
    },
    {
        "question": "301 - 59",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 242
    },
    {
        "question": "24 - 81",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -57
    },
    {
        "question": "290 + 77",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 367
    },
    {
        "question": "94 + 91",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 185
    },
    {
        "question": "42 - 27",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 15
    },
    {
        "question": "328 + 81",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 409
    },
    {
        "question": "190 - 73",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 117
    },
    {
        "question": "320 x 35",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 11200
    },
    {
        "question": "363 x 89",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 32307
    },
    {
        "question": "360 x 17",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 6120
    },
    {
        "question": "283 x 25",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 7075
    },
    {
        "question": "119 - 79",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 40
    },
    {
        "question": "226 + 17",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 243
    },
    {
        "question": "189 x 85",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 16065
    },
    {
        "question": "174 + 5",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 179
    },
    {
        "question": "395 x 81",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 31995
    },
    {
        "question": "59 - 91",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -32
    },
    {
        "question": "134 x 5",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 670
    },
    {
        "question": "294 - 23",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 271
    },
    {
        "question": "292 x 47",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 13724
    },
    {
        "question": "318 + 1",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 319
    },
    {
        "question": "313 x 89",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 27857
    },
    {
        "question": "3 + 1",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 4
    },
    {
        "question": "195 + 7",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 202
    },
    {
        "question": "338 x 27",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 9126
    },
    {
        "question": "24 - 59",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -35
    },
    {
        "question": "365 - 53",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 312
    },
    {
        "question": "66 + 77",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 143
    },
    {
        "question": "281 - 79",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 202
    },
    {
        "question": "62 - 67",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -5
    },
    {
        "question": "88 x 87",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 7656
    },
    {
        "question": "292 - 17",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 275
    },
    {
        "question": "167 + 61",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 228
    },
    {
        "question": "21 + 93",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 114
    },
    {
        "question": "348 + 9",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 357
    },
    {
        "question": "155 x 3",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 465
    },
    {
        "question": "46 x 35",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1610
    },
    {
        "question": "232 x 49",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 11368
    },
    {
        "question": "196 - 57",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 139
    },
    {
        "question": "380 + 33",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 413
    },
    {
        "question": "112 x 9",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1008
    },
    {
        "question": "345 + 3",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 348
    },
    {
        "question": "379 - 91",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 288
    },
    {
        "question": "160 + 87",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 247
    },
    {
        "question": "382 + 47",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 429
    },
    {
        "question": "172 + 57",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 229
    },
    {
        "question": "174 + 29",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 203
    },
    {
        "question": "3 x 31",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 93
    },
    {
        "question": "202 x 37",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 7474
    },
    {
        "question": "366 + 93",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 459
    },
    {
        "question": "247 + 47",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 294
    },
    {
        "question": "10 - 37",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -27
    },
    {
        "question": "122 + 1",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 123
    },
    {
        "question": "248 x 69",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 17112
    },
    {
        "question": "27 - 7",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 20
    },
    {
        "question": "358 + 53",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 411
    },
    {
        "question": "109 - 9",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 100
    },
    {
        "question": "204 - 3",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 201
    },
    {
        "question": "335 + 29",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 364
    },
    {
        "question": "331 + 25",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 356
    },
    {
        "question": "293 x 33",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 9669
    },
    {
        "question": "336 x 95",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 31920
    },
    {
        "question": "250 - 71",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 179
    },
    {
        "question": "183 + 45",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 228
    },
    {
        "question": "236 + 1",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 237
    },
    {
        "question": "212 + 49",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 261
    },
    {
        "question": "392 + 55",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 447
    },
    {
        "question": "172 x 67",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 11524
    },
    {
        "question": "189 + 33",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 222
    },
    {
        "question": "226 + 23",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 249
    },
    {
        "question": "183 + 97",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 280
    },
    {
        "question": "183 x 97",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 17751
    },
    {
        "question": "16 + 69",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 85
    },
    {
        "question": "42 x 27",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1134
    },
    {
        "question": "257 x 13",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 3341
    },
    {
        "question": "244 x 79",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 19276
    },
    {
        "question": "133 - 79",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 54
    },
    {
        "question": "73 - 1",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 72
    },
    {
        "question": "34 x 93",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 3162
    },
    {
        "question": "288 - 59",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 229
    },
    {
        "question": "114 - 43",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 71
    },
    {
        "question": "336 + 35",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 371
    },
    {
        "question": "172 + 71",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 243
    },
    {
        "question": "228 - 91",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 137
    },
    {
        "question": "295 - 19",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 276
    },
    {
        "question": "183 x 55",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 10065
    },
    {
        "question": "172 x 51",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 8772
    },
    {
        "question": "139 x 59",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 8201
    },
    {
        "question": "93 x 25",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 2325
    },
    {
        "question": "357 x 1",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 357
    },
    {
        "question": "326 x 65",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 21190
    },
    {
        "question": "363 + 49",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 412
    },
    {
        "question": "136 - 17",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 119
    },
    {
        "question": "343 + 51",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 394
    },
    {
        "question": "396 + 53",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 449
    },
    {
        "question": "78 - 99",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -21
    },
    {
        "question": "238 x 43",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 10234
    },
    {
        "question": "182 + 59",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 241
    },
    {
        "question": "247 + 21",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 268
    },
    {
        "question": "61 x 29",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1769
    },
    {
        "question": "226 + 99",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 325
    },
    {
        "question": "116 - 25",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 91
    },
    {
        "question": "316 + 93",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 409
    },
    {
        "question": "118 x 89",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 10502
    },
    {
        "question": "197 + 31",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 228
    },
    {
        "question": "374 x 11",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 4114
    },
    {
        "question": "358 x 9",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 3222
    },
    {
        "question": "308 + 31",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 339
    },
    {
        "question": "86 x 65",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 5590
    },
    {
        "question": "301 - 39",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 262
    },
    {
        "question": "74 x 21",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1554
    },
    {
        "question": "43 + 67",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 110
    },
    {
        "question": "60 x 83",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 4980
    },
    {
        "question": "43 + 9",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 52
    },
    {
        "question": "298 + 91",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 389
    },
    {
        "question": "343 x 97",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 33271
    },
    {
        "question": "131 + 95",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 226
    },
    {
        "question": "178 + 33",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 211
    },
    {
        "question": "248 - 85",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 163
    },
    {
        "question": "63 + 95",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 158
    },
    {
        "question": "270 - 5",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 265
    },
    {
        "question": "158 - 21",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 137
    },
    {
        "question": "345 - 19",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 326
    },
    {
        "question": "387 - 51",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 336
    },
    {
        "question": "136 + 67",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 203
    },
    {
        "question": "344 + 69",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 413
    },
    {
        "question": "296 + 61",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 357
    },
    {
        "question": "250 - 27",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 223
    },
    {
        "question": "131 x 45",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 5895
    },
    {
        "question": "157 - 7",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 150
    },
    {
        "question": "213 + 31",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 244
    },
    {
        "question": "65 - 71",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -6
    },
    {
        "question": "191 x 43",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 8213
    },
    {
        "question": "328 + 39",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 367
    },
    {
        "question": "94 - 83",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 11
    },
    {
        "question": "262 - 25",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 237
    },
    {
        "question": "257 - 91",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 166
    },
    {
        "question": "156 + 13",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 169
    },
    {
        "question": "300 + 67",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 367
    },
    {
        "question": "367 x 11",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 4037
    },
    {
        "question": "12 + 11",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 23
    },
    {
        "question": "33 + 95",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 128
    },
    {
        "question": "319 x 77",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 24563
    },
    {
        "question": "356 x 7",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 2492
    },
    {
        "question": "359 + 5",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 364
    },
    {
        "question": "233 - 37",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 196
    },
    {
        "question": "285 - 7",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 278
    },
    {
        "question": "156 x 41",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 6396
    },
    {
        "question": "114 - 1",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 113
    },
    {
        "question": "57 + 53",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 110
    },
    {
        "question": "345 + 57",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 402
    },
    {
        "question": "200 - 33",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 167
    },
    {
        "question": "1 - 21",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -20
    },
    {
        "question": "345 + 55",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 400
    },
    {
        "question": "102 + 31",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 133
    },
    {
        "question": "18 + 33",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 51
    },
    {
        "question": "226 x 17",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 3842
    },
    {
        "question": "84 + 1",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 85
    },
    {
        "question": "392 x 17",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 6664
    },
    {
        "question": "174 + 79",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 253
    },
    {
        "question": "101 - 59",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 42
    },
    {
        "question": "190 - 71",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 119
    },
    {
        "question": "26 x 71",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1846
    },
    {
        "question": "281 + 91",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 372
    },
    {
        "question": "365 + 45",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 410
    },
    {
        "question": "222 - 91",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 131
    },
    {
        "question": "76 + 31",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 107
    },
    {
        "question": "107 + 61",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 168
    },
    {
        "question": "364 x 51",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 18564
    },
    {
        "question": "125 x 11",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1375
    },
    {
        "question": "97 - 73",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 24
    },
    {
        "question": "256 x 47",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 12032
    },
    {
        "question": "295 - 97",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 198
    },
    {
        "question": "175 + 71",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 246
    },
    {
        "question": "284 - 67",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 217
    },
    {
        "question": "397 - 29",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 368
    },
    {
        "question": "211 x 29",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 6119
    },
    {
        "question": "114 x 47",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 5358
    },
    {
        "question": "102 x 83",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 8466
    },
    {
        "question": "37 - 67",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -30
    },
    {
        "question": "211 + 59",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 270
    },
    {
        "question": "138 + 89",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 227
    },
    {
        "question": "305 - 65",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 240
    },
    {
        "question": "186 + 9",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 195
    },
    {
        "question": "186 + 47",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 233
    },
    {
        "question": "38 - 97",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -59
    },
    {
        "question": "329 - 21",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 308
    },
    {
        "question": "100 + 55",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 155
    },
    {
        "question": "148 + 57",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 205
    },
    {
        "question": "294 + 75",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 369
    },
    {
        "question": "167 x 43",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 7181
    },
    {
        "question": "100 + 29",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 129
    },
    {
        "question": "357 + 69",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 426
    },
    {
        "question": "272 x 31",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 8432
    },
    {
        "question": "160 + 71",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 231
    },
    {
        "question": "72 x 91",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 6552
    },
    {
        "question": "395 + 35",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 430
    },
    {
        "question": "342 + 55",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 397
    },
    {
        "question": "270 - 95",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 175
    },
    {
        "question": "215 x 65",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 13975
    },
    {
        "question": "236 + 31",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 267
    },
    {
        "question": "102 - 61",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 41
    },
    {
        "question": "309 + 21",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 330
    },
    {
        "question": "207 - 75",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 132
    },
    {
        "question": "88 - 75",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 13
    },
    {
        "question": "163 - 45",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 118
    },
    {
        "question": "87 x 21",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1827
    },
    {
        "question": "34 x 87",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 2958
    },
    {
        "question": "272 - 63",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 209
    },
    {
        "question": "142 + 33",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 175
    },
    {
        "question": "25 x 43",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1075
    },
    {
        "question": "315 + 93",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 408
    },
    {
        "question": "13 + 95",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 108
    },
    {
        "question": "201 x 61",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 12261
    },
    {
        "question": "83 x 29",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 2407
    },
    {
        "question": "343 x 87",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 29841
    },
    {
        "question": "173 x 73",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 12629
    },
    {
        "question": "277 - 33",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 244
    },
    {
        "question": "48 - 73",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -25
    },
    {
        "question": "95 - 57",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 38
    },
    {
        "question": "48 - 17",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 31
    },
    {
        "question": "126 + 73",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 199
    },
    {
        "question": "230 - 29",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 201
    },
    {
        "question": "254 - 21",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 233
    },
    {
        "question": "92 - 49",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 43
    },
    {
        "question": "387 x 89",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 34443
    },
    {
        "question": "144 x 51",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 7344
    },
    {
        "question": "30 + 73",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 103
    },
    {
        "question": "128 - 93",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 35
    },
    {
        "question": "158 + 11",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 169
    },
    {
        "question": "248 + 95",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 343
    },
    {
        "question": "34 + 47",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 81
    },
    {
        "question": "391 + 55",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 446
    },
    {
        "question": "176 x 37",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 6512
    },
    {
        "question": "386 - 17",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 369
    },
    {
        "question": "365 + 89",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 454
    },
    {
        "question": "174 - 3",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 171
    },
    {
        "question": "83 x 15",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1245
    },
    {
        "question": "74 - 85",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -11
    },
    {
        "question": "104 x 31",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 3224
    },
    {
        "question": "181 - 35",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 146
    },
    {
        "question": "217 x 59",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 12803
    },
    {
        "question": "36 x 83",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 2988
    },
    {
        "question": "72 - 45",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 27
    },
    {
        "question": "290 - 7",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 283
    },
    {
        "question": "217 - 85",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 132
    },
    {
        "question": "35 x 43",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1505
    },
    {
        "question": "143 + 11",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 154
    },
    {
        "question": "254 - 19",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 235
    },
    {
        "question": "75 x 37",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 2775
    },
    {
        "question": "265 - 33",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 232
    },
    {
        "question": "362 x 37",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 13394
    },
    {
        "question": "341 + 57",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 398
    },
    {
        "question": "334 + 95",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 429
    },
    {
        "question": "274 - 9",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 265
    },
    {
        "question": "323 x 73",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 23579
    },
    {
        "question": "113 x 11",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1243
    },
    {
        "question": "50 + 71",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 121
    },
    {
        "question": "280 - 13",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 267
    },
    {
        "question": "125 x 25",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 3125
    },
    {
        "question": "294 + 51",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 345
    },
    {
        "question": "240 x 51",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 12240
    },
    {
        "question": "181 + 45",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 226
    },
    {
        "question": "294 x 55",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 16170
    },
    {
        "question": "8 x 23",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 184
    },
    {
        "question": "321 - 93",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 228
    },
    {
        "question": "378 - 1",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 377
    },
    {
        "question": "259 x 91",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 23569
    },
    {
        "question": "68 + 71",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 139
    },
    {
        "question": "199 + 19",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 218
    },
    {
        "question": "51 + 53",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 104
    },
    {
        "question": "12 - 73",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -61
    },
    {
        "question": "212 - 45",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 167
    },
    {
        "question": "381 x 39",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 14859
    },
    {
        "question": "64 + 21",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 85
    },
    {
        "question": "97 - 49",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 48
    },
    {
        "question": "339 + 15",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 354
    },
    {
        "question": "6 + 55",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 61
    },
    {
        "question": "77 - 97",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -20
    },
    {
        "question": "299 - 55",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 244
    },
    {
        "question": "144 + 73",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 217
    },
    {
        "question": "85 + 83",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 168
    },
    {
        "question": "194 - 27",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 167
    },
    {
        "question": "117 + 85",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 202
    },
    {
        "question": "385 - 91",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 294
    },
    {
        "question": "219 x 89",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 19491
    },
    {
        "question": "210 x 79",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 16590
    },
    {
        "question": "250 x 61",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 15250
    },
    {
        "question": "126 + 57",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 183
    },
    {
        "question": "244 + 27",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 271
    },
    {
        "question": "174 - 43",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 131
    },
    {
        "question": "284 - 73",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 211
    },
    {
        "question": "332 + 31",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 363
    },
    {
        "question": "75 + 11",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 86
    },
    {
        "question": "330 x 45",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 14850
    },
    {
        "question": "397 - 47",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 350
    },
    {
        "question": "184 x 73",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 13432
    },
    {
        "question": "270 + 83",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 353
    },
    {
        "question": "65 x 91",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 5915
    },
    {
        "question": "71 - 83",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -12
    },
    {
        "question": "298 x 91",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 27118
    },
    {
        "question": "108 x 13",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1404
    },
    {
        "question": "133 x 57",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 7581
    },
    {
        "question": "74 x 43",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 3182
    },
    {
        "question": "271 - 63",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 208
    },
    {
        "question": "88 - 25",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 63
    },
    {
        "question": "395 + 65",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 460
    },
    {
        "question": "319 + 3",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 322
    },
    {
        "question": "348 + 15",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 363
    },
    {
        "question": "13 x 39",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 507
    },
    {
        "question": "168 - 33",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 135
    },
    {
        "question": "10 x 95",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 950
    },
    {
        "question": "185 + 37",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 222
    },
    {
        "question": "112 x 75",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 8400
    },
    {
        "question": "3 x 63",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 189
    },
    {
        "question": "333 + 73",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 406
    },
    {
        "question": "103 x 17",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1751
    },
    {
        "question": "14 - 97",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -83
    },
    {
        "question": "315 - 47",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 268
    },
    {
        "question": "372 x 9",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 3348
    },
    {
        "question": "369 x 35",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 12915
    },
    {
        "question": "357 x 81",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 28917
    },
    {
        "question": "191 x 39",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 7449
    },
    {
        "question": "301 - 85",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 216
    },
    {
        "question": "13 x 1",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 13
    },
    {
        "question": "32 + 37",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 69
    },
    {
        "question": "274 x 69",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 18906
    },
    {
        "question": "384 x 59",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 22656
    },
    {
        "question": "237 - 15",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 222
    },
    {
        "question": "227 x 37",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 8399
    },
    {
        "question": "92 + 99",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 191
    },
    {
        "question": "12 x 61",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 732
    },
    {
        "question": "70 x 99",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 6930
    },
    {
        "question": "47 - 89",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -42
    },
    {
        "question": "115 + 91",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 206
    },
    {
        "question": "102 - 19",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 83
    },
    {
        "question": "15 x 97",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1455
    },
    {
        "question": "50 x 25",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1250
    },
    {
        "question": "324 x 21",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 6804
    },
    {
        "question": "160 x 99",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 15840
    },
    {
        "question": "294 - 35",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 259
    },
    {
        "question": "236 x 91",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 21476
    },
    {
        "question": "89 x 59",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 5251
    },
    {
        "question": "13 - 35",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -22
    },
    {
        "question": "41 x 67",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 2747
    },
    {
        "question": "269 + 87",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 356
    },
    {
        "question": "187 + 63",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 250
    },
    {
        "question": "105 x 85",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 8925
    },
    {
        "question": "367 x 17",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 6239
    },
    {
        "question": "176 x 55",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 9680
    },
    {
        "question": "185 + 89",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 274
    },
    {
        "question": "288 x 47",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 13536
    },
    {
        "question": "67 + 63",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 130
    },
    {
        "question": "352 x 47",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 16544
    },
    {
        "question": "161 x 1",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 161
    },
    {
        "question": "30 x 53",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1590
    },
    {
        "question": "244 x 93",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 22692
    },
    {
        "question": "349 + 95",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 444
    },
    {
        "question": "257 + 51",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 308
    },
    {
        "question": "333 + 87",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 420
    },
    {
        "question": "373 x 79",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 29467
    },
    {
        "question": "124 x 87",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 10788
    },
    {
        "question": "393 - 31",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 362
    },
    {
        "question": "248 - 37",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 211
    },
    {
        "question": "127 x 91",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 11557
    },
    {
        "question": "118 - 61",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 57
    },
    {
        "question": "199 - 9",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 190
    },
    {
        "question": "253 - 9",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 244
    },
    {
        "question": "255 - 73",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 182
    },
    {
        "question": "299 + 55",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 354
    },
    {
        "question": "198 + 35",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 233
    },
    {
        "question": "279 x 29",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 8091
    },
    {
        "question": "19 x 63",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1197
    },
    {
        "question": "297 + 37",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 334
    },
    {
        "question": "114 + 37",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 151
    },
    {
        "question": "156 - 23",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 133
    },
    {
        "question": "131 x 87",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 11397
    },
    {
        "question": "87 - 19",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 68
    },
    {
        "question": "1 x 13",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 13
    },
    {
        "question": "372 x 45",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 16740
    },
    {
        "question": "184 + 53",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 237
    },
    {
        "question": "125 - 59",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 66
    },
    {
        "question": "129 - 1",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 128
    },
    {
        "question": "309 + 25",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 334
    },
    {
        "question": "277 - 83",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 194
    },
    {
        "question": "23 x 35",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 805
    },
    {
        "question": "291 - 25",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 266
    },
    {
        "question": "321 x 91",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 29211
    },
    {
        "question": "185 + 91",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 276
    },
    {
        "question": "8 + 75",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 83
    },
    {
        "question": "7 - 99",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -92
    },
    {
        "question": "173 - 75",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 98
    },
    {
        "question": "307 + 49",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 356
    },
    {
        "question": "217 - 7",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 210
    },
    {
        "question": "347 + 85",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 432
    },
    {
        "question": "268 x 13",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 3484
    },
    {
        "question": "387 - 95",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 292
    },
    {
        "question": "379 x 13",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 4927
    },
    {
        "question": "162 - 53",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 109
    },
    {
        "question": "202 + 3",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 205
    },
    {
        "question": "178 + 39",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 217
    },
    {
        "question": "392 + 99",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 491
    },
    {
        "question": "56 - 75",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -19
    },
    {
        "question": "324 + 39",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 363
    },
    {
        "question": "363 - 27",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 336
    },
    {
        "question": "55 - 97",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -42
    },
    {
        "question": "271 x 45",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 12195
    },
    {
        "question": "194 + 79",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 273
    },
    {
        "question": "133 x 53",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 7049
    },
    {
        "question": "301 + 85",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 386
    },
    {
        "question": "398 + 11",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 409
    },
    {
        "question": "331 + 1",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 332
    },
    {
        "question": "268 + 53",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 321
    },
    {
        "question": "254 x 39",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 9906
    },
    {
        "question": "226 x 31",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 7006
    },
    {
        "question": "349 x 9",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 3141
    },
    {
        "question": "30 - 83",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -53
    },
    {
        "question": "139 + 97",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 236
    },
    {
        "question": "115 x 35",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 4025
    },
    {
        "question": "384 - 55",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 329
    },
    {
        "question": "336 x 61",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 20496
    },
    {
        "question": "327 x 99",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 32373
    },
    {
        "question": "241 + 37",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 278
    },
    {
        "question": "360 - 29",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 331
    },
    {
        "question": "271 - 5",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 266
    },
    {
        "question": "253 x 53",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 13409
    },
    {
        "question": "197 x 57",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 11229
    },
    {
        "question": "310 + 73",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 383
    },
    {
        "question": "13 x 21",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 273
    },
    {
        "question": "182 + 97",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 279
    },
    {
        "question": "209 - 45",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 164
    },
    {
        "question": "123 + 55",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 178
    },
    {
        "question": "327 + 49",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 376
    },
    {
        "question": "69 - 31",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 38
    },
    {
        "question": "385 x 61",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 23485
    },
    {
        "question": "168 - 47",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 121
    },
    {
        "question": "374 - 43",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 331
    },
    {
        "question": "317 + 61",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 378
    },
    {
        "question": "203 + 43",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 246
    },
    {
        "question": "314 - 29",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 285
    },
    {
        "question": "36 x 97",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 3492
    },
    {
        "question": "64 - 35",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 29
    },
    {
        "question": "85 + 13",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 98
    },
    {
        "question": "377 x 3",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1131
    },
    {
        "question": "161 x 53",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 8533
    },
    {
        "question": "272 - 23",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 249
    },
    {
        "question": "29 - 5",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 24
    },
    {
        "question": "248 x 89",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 22072
    },
    {
        "question": "365 + 97",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 462
    },
    {
        "question": "68 - 29",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 39
    },
    {
        "question": "8 - 81",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -73
    },
    {
        "question": "341 + 73",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 414
    },
    {
        "question": "22 x 53",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1166
    },
    {
        "question": "305 + 19",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 324
    },
    {
        "question": "1 x 53",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 53
    },
    {
        "question": "335 x 89",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 29815
    },
    {
        "question": "76 - 93",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -17
    },
    {
        "question": "324 + 61",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 385
    },
    {
        "question": "267 + 39",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 306
    },
    {
        "question": "239 x 11",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 2629
    },
    {
        "question": "361 x 13",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 4693
    },
    {
        "question": "378 x 11",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 4158
    },
    {
        "question": "69 + 9",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 78
    },
    {
        "question": "130 + 71",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 201
    },
    {
        "question": "320 + 27",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 347
    },
    {
        "question": "11 x 63",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 693
    },
    {
        "question": "243 - 27",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 216
    },
    {
        "question": "304 + 5",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 309
    },
    {
        "question": "142 + 93",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 235
    },
    {
        "question": "149 - 51",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 98
    },
    {
        "question": "377 - 3",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 374
    },
    {
        "question": "363 + 31",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 394
    },
    {
        "question": "184 - 79",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 105
    },
    {
        "question": "257 - 91",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 166
    },
    {
        "question": "44 - 1",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 43
    },
    {
        "question": "168 x 71",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 11928
    },
    {
        "question": "349 - 51",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 298
    },
    {
        "question": "173 - 17",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 156
    },
    {
        "question": "397 - 83",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 314
    },
    {
        "question": "359 - 43",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 316
    },
    {
        "question": "373 + 43",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 416
    },
    {
        "question": "253 - 95",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 158
    },
    {
        "question": "113 - 39",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 74
    },
    {
        "question": "225 x 61",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 13725
    },
    {
        "question": "144 + 61",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 205
    },
    {
        "question": "111 - 73",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 38
    },
    {
        "question": "375 - 67",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 308
    },
    {
        "question": "127 x 83",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 10541
    },
    {
        "question": "229 + 23",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 252
    },
    {
        "question": "207 x 53",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 10971
    },
    {
        "question": "5 x 25",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 125
    },
    {
        "question": "167 - 49",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 118
    },
    {
        "question": "202 - 89",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 113
    },
    {
        "question": "258 + 15",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 273
    },
    {
        "question": "207 x 95",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 19665
    },
    {
        "question": "32 x 73",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 2336
    },
    {
        "question": "116 x 69",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 8004
    },
    {
        "question": "345 x 57",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 19665
    },
    {
        "question": "158 - 87",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 71
    },
    {
        "question": "214 - 51",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 163
    },
    {
        "question": "349 + 23",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 372
    },
    {
        "question": "192 x 37",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 7104
    },
    {
        "question": "200 - 91",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 109
    },
    {
        "question": "371 - 23",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 348
    },
    {
        "question": "394 x 3",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1182
    },
    {
        "question": "151 x 15",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 2265
    },
    {
        "question": "184 + 5",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 189
    },
    {
        "question": "391 - 7",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 384
    },
    {
        "question": "143 - 33",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 110
    },
    {
        "question": "188 - 7",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 181
    },
    {
        "question": "328 x 29",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 9512
    },
    {
        "question": "13 - 77",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -64
    },
    {
        "question": "393 + 77",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 470
    },
    {
        "question": "309 + 93",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 402
    },
    {
        "question": "270 - 39",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 231
    },
    {
        "question": "203 x 1",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 203
    },
    {
        "question": "186 + 63",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 249
    },
    {
        "question": "82 + 95",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 177
    },
    {
        "question": "394 - 75",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 319
    },
    {
        "question": "48 x 1",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 48
    },
    {
        "question": "254 - 41",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 213
    },
    {
        "question": "322 x 67",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 21574
    },
    {
        "question": "376 - 9",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 367
    },
    {
        "question": "325 + 63",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 388
    },
    {
        "question": "275 + 63",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 338
    },
    {
        "question": "59 + 73",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 132
    },
    {
        "question": "207 x 25",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 5175
    },
    {
        "question": "35 + 15",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 50
    },
    {
        "question": "54 x 15",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 810
    },
    {
        "question": "102 - 35",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 67
    },
    {
        "question": "247 x 69",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 17043
    },
    {
        "question": "298 + 55",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 353
    },
    {
        "question": "208 - 55",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 153
    },
    {
        "question": "67 - 37",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 30
    },
    {
        "question": "179 - 65",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 114
    },
    {
        "question": "121 - 25",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 96
    },
    {
        "question": "145 + 7",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 152
    },
    {
        "question": "266 + 87",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 353
    },
    {
        "question": "128 - 55",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 73
    },
    {
        "question": "391 x 15",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 5865
    },
    {
        "question": "339 x 97",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 32883
    },
    {
        "question": "109 - 55",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 54
    },
    {
        "question": "125 x 3",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 375
    },
    {
        "question": "41 + 5",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 46
    },
    {
        "question": "293 + 27",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 320
    },
    {
        "question": "248 + 57",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 305
    },
    {
        "question": "266 x 47",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 12502
    },
    {
        "question": "15 x 19",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 285
    },
    {
        "question": "268 + 93",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 361
    },
    {
        "question": "146 - 33",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 113
    },
    {
        "question": "239 - 11",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 228
    },
    {
        "question": "6 + 77",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 83
    },
    {
        "question": "148 + 73",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 221
    },
    {
        "question": "260 x 83",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 21580
    },
    {
        "question": "320 + 29",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 349
    },
    {
        "question": "21 - 37",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -16
    },
    {
        "question": "285 - 69",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 216
    },
    {
        "question": "36 + 53",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 89
    },
    {
        "question": "315 + 69",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 384
    },
    {
        "question": "288 - 23",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 265
    },
    {
        "question": "232 x 39",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 9048
    },
    {
        "question": "199 - 35",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 164
    },
    {
        "question": "163 + 53",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 216
    },
    {
        "question": "152 + 65",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 217
    },
    {
        "question": "348 x 19",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 6612
    },
    {
        "question": "223 x 23",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 5129
    },
    {
        "question": "135 x 19",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 2565
    },
    {
        "question": "167 + 89",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 256
    },
    {
        "question": "368 + 81",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 449
    },
    {
        "question": "135 x 59",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 7965
    },
    {
        "question": "180 - 95",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 85
    },
    {
        "question": "162 x 7",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1134
    },
    {
        "question": "3 + 41",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 44
    },
    {
        "question": "325 - 27",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 298
    },
    {
        "question": "324 - 23",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 301
    },
    {
        "question": "313 - 5",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 308
    },
    {
        "question": "249 + 81",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 330
    },
    {
        "question": "101 x 69",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 6969
    },
    {
        "question": "39 x 63",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 2457
    },
    {
        "question": "194 - 9",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 185
    },
    {
        "question": "104 + 93",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 197
    },
    {
        "question": "194 + 49",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 243
    },
    {
        "question": "103 + 91",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 194
    },
    {
        "question": "113 - 69",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 44
    },
    {
        "question": "113 + 27",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 140
    },
    {
        "question": "303 + 11",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 314
    },
    {
        "question": "231 - 19",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 212
    },
    {
        "question": "31 x 83",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 2573
    },
    {
        "question": "51 - 31",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 20
    },
    {
        "question": "363 + 43",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 406
    },
    {
        "question": "267 + 3",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 270
    },
    {
        "question": "389 + 29",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 418
    },
    {
        "question": "100 x 97",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 9700
    },
    {
        "question": "233 - 49",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 184
    },
    {
        "question": "295 x 69",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 20355
    },
    {
        "question": "341 x 41",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 13981
    },
    {
        "question": "383 + 89",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 472
    },
    {
        "question": "388 x 75",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 29100
    },
    {
        "question": "317 - 67",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 250
    },
    {
        "question": "181 - 69",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 112
    },
    {
        "question": "272 x 45",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 12240
    },
    {
        "question": "347 - 67",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 280
    },
    {
        "question": "251 + 37",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 288
    },
    {
        "question": "27 + 75",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 102
    },
    {
        "question": "289 - 67",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 222
    },
    {
        "question": "284 - 61",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 223
    },
    {
        "question": "113 - 43",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 70
    },
    {
        "question": "168 - 65",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 103
    },
    {
        "question": "342 - 41",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 301
    },
    {
        "question": "41 - 85",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -44
    },
    {
        "question": "106 + 91",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 197
    },
    {
        "question": "76 x 31",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 2356
    },
    {
        "question": "227 - 69",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 158
    },
    {
        "question": "334 - 87",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 247
    },
    {
        "question": "235 x 75",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 17625
    },
    {
        "question": "28 x 67",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1876
    },
    {
        "question": "364 + 73",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 437
    },
    {
        "question": "167 + 17",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 184
    },
    {
        "question": "356 x 77",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 27412
    },
    {
        "question": "142 + 5",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 147
    },
    {
        "question": "200 x 83",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 16600
    },
    {
        "question": "233 x 17",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 3961
    },
    {
        "question": "187 - 71",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 116
    },
    {
        "question": "178 + 13",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 191
    },
    {
        "question": "209 x 9",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1881
    },
    {
        "question": "363 x 89",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 32307
    },
    {
        "question": "63 + 41",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 104
    },
    {
        "question": "45 x 87",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 3915
    },
    {
        "question": "288 x 85",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 24480
    },
    {
        "question": "393 + 47",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 440
    },
    {
        "question": "331 - 29",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 302
    },
    {
        "question": "33 x 3",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 99
    },
    {
        "question": "336 + 7",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 343
    },
    {
        "question": "212 + 61",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 273
    },
    {
        "question": "53 x 97",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 5141
    },
    {
        "question": "177 x 37",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 6549
    },
    {
        "question": "224 + 95",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 319
    },
    {
        "question": "12 + 3",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 15
    },
    {
        "question": "145 + 65",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 210
    },
    {
        "question": "188 x 9",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1692
    },
    {
        "question": "38 - 71",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -33
    },
    {
        "question": "84 + 67",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 151
    },
    {
        "question": "305 x 69",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 21045
    },
    {
        "question": "193 x 61",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 11773
    },
    {
        "question": "19 - 7",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 12
    },
    {
        "question": "39 + 5",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 44
    },
    {
        "question": "121 - 89",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 32
    },
    {
        "question": "332 x 13",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 4316
    },
    {
        "question": "335 + 29",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 364
    },
    {
        "question": "354 x 89",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 31506
    },
    {
        "question": "341 x 37",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 12617
    },
    {
        "question": "338 + 17",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 355
    },
    {
        "question": "98 x 23",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 2254
    },
    {
        "question": "259 x 85",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 22015
    },
    {
        "question": "44 x 71",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 3124
    },
    {
        "question": "5 - 47",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -42
    },
    {
        "question": "302 x 37",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 11174
    },
    {
        "question": "21 x 69",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1449
    },
    {
        "question": "349 + 65",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 414
    },
    {
        "question": "202 - 87",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 115
    },
    {
        "question": "377 x 41",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 15457
    },
    {
        "question": "378 x 39",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 14742
    },
    {
        "question": "384 x 57",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 21888
    },
    {
        "question": "137 + 47",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 184
    },
    {
        "question": "203 x 51",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 10353
    },
    {
        "question": "359 x 61",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 21899
    },
    {
        "question": "355 x 23",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 8165
    },
    {
        "question": "74 - 99",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -25
    },
    {
        "question": "3 - 91",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -88
    },
    {
        "question": "360 + 7",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 367
    },
    {
        "question": "308 + 91",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 399
    },
    {
        "question": "307 x 17",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 5219
    },
    {
        "question": "167 + 7",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 174
    },
    {
        "question": "118 - 81",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 37
    },
    {
        "question": "196 + 45",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 241
    },
    {
        "question": "361 + 59",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 420
    },
    {
        "question": "218 - 33",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 185
    },
    {
        "question": "385 - 51",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 334
    },
    {
        "question": "195 x 87",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 16965
    },
    {
        "question": "183 + 17",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 200
    },
    {
        "question": "204 + 17",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 221
    },
    {
        "question": "295 x 91",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 26845
    },
    {
        "question": "370 - 71",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 299
    },
    {
        "question": "252 - 99",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 153
    },
    {
        "question": "391 + 99",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 490
    },
    {
        "question": "116 + 33",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 149
    },
    {
        "question": "241 - 75",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 166
    },
    {
        "question": "241 - 85",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 156
    },
    {
        "question": "183 + 61",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 244
    },
    {
        "question": "311 - 33",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 278
    },
    {
        "question": "13 x 99",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1287
    },
    {
        "question": "133 x 83",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 11039
    },
    {
        "question": "396 + 99",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 495
    },
    {
        "question": "200 x 81",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 16200
    },
    {
        "question": "146 + 29",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 175
    },
    {
        "question": "200 - 11",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 189
    },
    {
        "question": "156 x 17",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 2652
    },
    {
        "question": "271 + 79",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 350
    },
    {
        "question": "98 x 81",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 7938
    },
    {
        "question": "36 + 41",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 77
    },
    {
        "question": "362 x 31",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 11222
    },
    {
        "question": "10 x 27",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 270
    },
    {
        "question": "3 x 71",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 213
    },
    {
        "question": "178 x 93",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 16554
    },
    {
        "question": "379 - 37",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 342
    },
    {
        "question": "191 x 31",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 5921
    },
    {
        "question": "129 + 19",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 148
    },
    {
        "question": "30 x 45",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1350
    },
    {
        "question": "54 - 21",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 33
    },
    {
        "question": "175 x 93",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 16275
    },
    {
        "question": "72 + 79",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 151
    },
    {
        "question": "357 x 59",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 21063
    },
    {
        "question": "125 x 83",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 10375
    },
    {
        "question": "298 x 91",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 27118
    },
    {
        "question": "56 x 11",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 616
    },
    {
        "question": "87 + 29",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 116
    },
    {
        "question": "15 + 47",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 62
    },
    {
        "question": "375 x 5",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1875
    },
    {
        "question": "273 - 3",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 270
    },
    {
        "question": "7 - 11",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -4
    },
    {
        "question": "338 x 37",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 12506
    },
    {
        "question": "10 + 3",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 13
    },
    {
        "question": "325 x 93",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 30225
    },
    {
        "question": "395 - 3",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 392
    },
    {
        "question": "123 x 29",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 3567
    },
    {
        "question": "346 + 81",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 427
    },
    {
        "question": "66 x 33",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 2178
    },
    {
        "question": "277 + 45",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 322
    },
    {
        "question": "131 + 7",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 138
    },
    {
        "question": "204 - 17",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 187
    },
    {
        "question": "108 + 49",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 157
    },
    {
        "question": "167 + 87",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 254
    },
    {
        "question": "361 + 9",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 370
    },
    {
        "question": "294 x 77",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 22638
    },
    {
        "question": "32 - 19",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 13
    },
    {
        "question": "296 + 43",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 339
    },
    {
        "question": "2 x 59",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 118
    },
    {
        "question": "83 x 65",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 5395
    },
    {
        "question": "357 x 97",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 34629
    },
    {
        "question": "337 x 57",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 19209
    },
    {
        "question": "375 + 37",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 412
    },
    {
        "question": "65 - 1",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 64
    },
    {
        "question": "118 - 51",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 67
    },
    {
        "question": "41 x 69",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 2829
    },
    {
        "question": "190 - 23",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 167
    },
    {
        "question": "174 + 47",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 221
    },
    {
        "question": "157 x 71",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 11147
    },
    {
        "question": "351 x 1",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 351
    },
    {
        "question": "199 x 65",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 12935
    },
    {
        "question": "338 - 59",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 279
    },
    {
        "question": "250 - 13",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 237
    },
    {
        "question": "40 - 69",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -29
    },
    {
        "question": "99 + 87",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 186
    },
    {
        "question": "146 x 3",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 438
    },
    {
        "question": "263 + 79",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 342
    },
    {
        "question": "217 - 91",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 126
    },
    {
        "question": "266 x 31",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 8246
    },
    {
        "question": "33 x 31",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1023
    },
    {
        "question": "77 + 3",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 80
    },
    {
        "question": "156 + 99",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 255
    },
    {
        "question": "221 + 19",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 240
    },
    {
        "question": "355 + 81",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 436
    },
    {
        "question": "72 - 23",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 49
    },
    {
        "question": "273 x 29",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 7917
    },
    {
        "question": "366 x 21",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 7686
    },
    {
        "question": "310 + 65",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 375
    },
    {
        "question": "141 x 43",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 6063
    },
    {
        "question": "213 x 13",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 2769
    },
    {
        "question": "206 x 95",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 19570
    },
    {
        "question": "277 - 61",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 216
    },
    {
        "question": "264 + 61",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 325
    },
    {
        "question": "288 - 3",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 285
    },
    {
        "question": "174 x 43",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 7482
    },
    {
        "question": "244 - 87",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 157
    },
    {
        "question": "203 x 9",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1827
    },
    {
        "question": "361 + 85",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 446
    },
    {
        "question": "177 x 27",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 4779
    },
    {
        "question": "344 x 67",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 23048
    },
    {
        "question": "197 + 29",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 226
    },
    {
        "question": "115 x 59",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 6785
    },
    {
        "question": "309 x 23",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 7107
    },
    {
        "question": "258 x 71",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 18318
    },
    {
        "question": "243 x 1",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 243
    },
    {
        "question": "286 - 11",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 275
    },
    {
        "question": "34 - 59",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -25
    },
    {
        "question": "62 - 3",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 59
    },
    {
        "question": "125 - 1",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 124
    },
    {
        "question": "167 x 67",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 11189
    },
    {
        "question": "343 x 81",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 27783
    },
    {
        "question": "343 + 43",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 386
    },
    {
        "question": "345 x 95",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 32775
    },
    {
        "question": "259 - 91",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 168
    },
    {
        "question": "295 + 31",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 326
    },
    {
        "question": "73 x 79",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 5767
    },
    {
        "question": "18 x 19",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 342
    },
    {
        "question": "21 + 77",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 98
    },
    {
        "question": "387 - 91",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 296
    },
    {
        "question": "34 x 59",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 2006
    },
    {
        "question": "17 - 29",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -12
    },
    {
        "question": "315 x 25",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 7875
    },
    {
        "question": "189 - 25",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 164
    },
    {
        "question": "395 - 31",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 364
    },
    {
        "question": "379 x 25",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 9475
    },
    {
        "question": "126 + 29",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 155
    },
    {
        "question": "304 x 81",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 24624
    },
    {
        "question": "64 - 75",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -11
    },
    {
        "question": "8 - 41",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -33
    },
    {
        "question": "365 - 77",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 288
    },
    {
        "question": "56 x 87",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 4872
    },
    {
        "question": "337 x 79",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 26623
    },
    {
        "question": "287 x 85",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 24395
    },
    {
        "question": "257 - 69",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 188
    },
    {
        "question": "321 x 41",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 13161
    },
    {
        "question": "246 + 13",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 259
    },
    {
        "question": "75 - 79",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -4
    },
    {
        "question": "164 + 83",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 247
    },
    {
        "question": "330 x 49",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 16170
    },
    {
        "question": "148 - 35",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 113
    },
    {
        "question": "183 x 65",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 11895
    },
    {
        "question": "383 x 75",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 28725
    },
    {
        "question": "171 x 47",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 8037
    },
    {
        "question": "207 x 1",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 207
    },
    {
        "question": "165 x 73",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 12045
    },
    {
        "question": "24 x 37",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 888
    },
    {
        "question": "332 - 45",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 287
    },
    {
        "question": "365 + 81",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 446
    },
    {
        "question": "109 - 9",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 100
    },
    {
        "question": "67 x 1",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 67
    },
    {
        "question": "172 x 97",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 16684
    },
    {
        "question": "89 + 23",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 112
    },
    {
        "question": "85 - 7",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 78
    },
    {
        "question": "334 + 57",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 391
    },
    {
        "question": "132 - 9",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 123
    },
    {
        "question": "267 x 71",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 18957
    },
    {
        "question": "104 + 35",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 139
    },
    {
        "question": "122 x 71",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 8662
    },
    {
        "question": "47 x 79",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 3713
    },
    {
        "question": "105 + 13",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 118
    },
    {
        "question": "357 + 93",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 450
    },
    {
        "question": "191 x 1",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 191
    },
    {
        "question": "142 + 1",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 143
    },
    {
        "question": "392 + 31",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 423
    },
    {
        "question": "11 - 69",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -58
    },
    {
        "question": "61 - 1",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 60
    },
    {
        "question": "240 - 85",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 155
    },
    {
        "question": "358 - 41",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 317
    },
    {
        "question": "381 - 27",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 354
    },
    {
        "question": "260 + 47",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 307
    },
    {
        "question": "196 x 27",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 5292
    },
    {
        "question": "328 x 77",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 25256
    },
    {
        "question": "280 - 69",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 211
    },
    {
        "question": "392 x 83",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 32536
    },
    {
        "question": "143 - 39",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 104
    },
    {
        "question": "254 x 85",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 21590
    },
    {
        "question": "304 + 75",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 379
    },
    {
        "question": "369 + 17",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 386
    },
    {
        "question": "110 - 73",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 37
    },
    {
        "question": "305 - 35",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 270
    },
    {
        "question": "290 - 77",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 213
    },
    {
        "question": "357 x 35",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 12495
    },
    {
        "question": "334 - 45",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 289
    },
    {
        "question": "144 - 95",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 49
    },
    {
        "question": "122 + 97",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 219
    },
    {
        "question": "14 - 7",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 7
    },
    {
        "question": "164 x 63",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 10332
    },
    {
        "question": "268 + 35",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 303
    },
    {
        "question": "307 + 97",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 404
    },
    {
        "question": "53 + 95",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 148
    },
    {
        "question": "389 x 7",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 2723
    },
    {
        "question": "228 x 73",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 16644
    },
    {
        "question": "358 - 75",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 283
    },
    {
        "question": "346 x 33",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 11418
    },
    {
        "question": "68 - 17",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 51
    },
    {
        "question": "165 - 11",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 154
    },
    {
        "question": "59 x 43",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 2537
    },
    {
        "question": "350 - 19",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 331
    },
    {
        "question": "348 - 13",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 335
    },
    {
        "question": "101 + 73",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 174
    },
    {
        "question": "337 x 33",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 11121
    },
    {
        "question": "337 - 11",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 326
    },
    {
        "question": "279 x 41",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 11439
    },
    {
        "question": "275 + 93",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 368
    },
    {
        "question": "366 - 71",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 295
    },
    {
        "question": "79 + 41",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 120
    },
    {
        "question": "203 - 69",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 134
    },
    {
        "question": "372 + 85",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 457
    },
    {
        "question": "212 - 37",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 175
    },
    {
        "question": "5 x 87",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 435
    },
    {
        "question": "304 x 77",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 23408
    },
    {
        "question": "236 x 77",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 18172
    },
    {
        "question": "146 + 45",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 191
    },
    {
        "question": "84 + 35",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 119
    },
    {
        "question": "382 + 7",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 389
    },
    {
        "question": "258 + 89",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 347
    },
    {
        "question": "101 - 11",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 90
    },
    {
        "question": "131 x 13",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1703
    },
    {
        "question": "222 + 35",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 257
    },
    {
        "question": "313 x 81",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 25353
    },
    {
        "question": "300 - 61",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 239
    },
    {
        "question": "292 x 75",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 21900
    },
    {
        "question": "117 x 75",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 8775
    },
    {
        "question": "210 - 61",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 149
    },
    {
        "question": "271 - 51",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 220
    },
    {
        "question": "360 x 63",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 22680
    },
    {
        "question": "103 x 51",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 5253
    },
    {
        "question": "48 x 41",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1968
    },
    {
        "question": "118 + 91",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 209
    },
    {
        "question": "51 + 1",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 52
    },
    {
        "question": "1 - 49",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -48
    },
    {
        "question": "89 x 75",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 6675
    },
    {
        "question": "134 - 63",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 71
    },
    {
        "question": "61 x 19",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1159
    },
    {
        "question": "326 + 51",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 377
    },
    {
        "question": "158 x 79",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 12482
    },
    {
        "question": "260 + 23",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 283
    },
    {
        "question": "326 - 39",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 287
    },
    {
        "question": "112 - 7",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 105
    },
    {
        "question": "222 - 45",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 177
    },
    {
        "question": "389 + 75",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 464
    },
    {
        "question": "231 + 93",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 324
    },
    {
        "question": "196 - 11",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 185
    },
    {
        "question": "41 + 95",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 136
    },
    {
        "question": "18 + 67",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 85
    },
    {
        "question": "38 + 47",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 85
    },
    {
        "question": "45 + 41",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 86
    },
    {
        "question": "354 + 83",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 437
    },
    {
        "question": "121 - 33",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 88
    },
    {
        "question": "268 - 69",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 199
    },
    {
        "question": "128 - 67",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 61
    },
    {
        "question": "49 x 81",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 3969
    },
    {
        "question": "18 x 81",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1458
    },
    {
        "question": "64 x 45",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 2880
    },
    {
        "question": "149 - 69",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 80
    },
    {
        "question": "146 x 87",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 12702
    },
    {
        "question": "174 - 21",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 153
    },
    {
        "question": "397 - 67",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 330
    },
    {
        "question": "3 - 45",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -42
    },
    {
        "question": "96 + 27",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 123
    },
    {
        "question": "70 x 27",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1890
    },
    {
        "question": "286 - 99",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 187
    },
    {
        "question": "180 - 13",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 167
    },
    {
        "question": "102 x 89",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 9078
    },
    {
        "question": "74 - 89",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -15
    },
    {
        "question": "358 + 97",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 455
    },
    {
        "question": "75 + 3",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 78
    },
    {
        "question": "277 + 49",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 326
    },
    {
        "question": "91 - 13",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 78
    },
    {
        "question": "12 + 85",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 97
    },
    {
        "question": "113 - 17",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 96
    },
    {
        "question": "149 - 33",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 116
    },
    {
        "question": "392 x 81",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 31752
    },
    {
        "question": "287 x 25",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 7175
    },
    {
        "question": "99 x 25",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 2475
    },
    {
        "question": "262 x 57",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 14934
    },
    {
        "question": "293 x 89",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 26077
    },
    {
        "question": "300 + 7",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 307
    },
    {
        "question": "53 + 89",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 142
    },
    {
        "question": "165 + 25",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 190
    },
    {
        "question": "136 + 61",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 197
    },
    {
        "question": "4 + 45",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 49
    },
    {
        "question": "7 x 85",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 595
    },
    {
        "question": "344 + 79",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 423
    },
    {
        "question": "215 - 73",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 142
    },
    {
        "question": "141 + 85",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 226
    },
    {
        "question": "205 x 19",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 3895
    },
    {
        "question": "309 x 91",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 28119
    },
    {
        "question": "321 + 25",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 346
    },
    {
        "question": "185 x 7",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1295
    },
    {
        "question": "97 x 1",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 97
    },
    {
        "question": "368 x 9",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 3312
    },
    {
        "question": "361 - 7",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 354
    },
    {
        "question": "255 x 83",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 21165
    },
    {
        "question": "177 + 29",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 206
    },
    {
        "question": "4 x 29",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 116
    },
    {
        "question": "128 + 89",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 217
    },
    {
        "question": "355 - 97",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 258
    },
    {
        "question": "112 + 53",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 165
    },
    {
        "question": "132 x 93",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 12276
    },
    {
        "question": "333 + 29",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 362
    },
    {
        "question": "84 - 95",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -11
    },
    {
        "question": "211 + 9",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 220
    },
    {
        "question": "363 x 25",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 9075
    },
    {
        "question": "139 + 53",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 192
    },
    {
        "question": "226 + 55",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 281
    },
    {
        "question": "60 - 77",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -17
    },
    {
        "question": "316 + 95",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 411
    },
    {
        "question": "78 + 81",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 159
    },
    {
        "question": "4 + 51",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 55
    },
    {
        "question": "298 x 45",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 13410
    },
    {
        "question": "345 + 9",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 354
    },
    {
        "question": "355 + 9",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 364
    },
    {
        "question": "188 + 73",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 261
    },
    {
        "question": "26 - 49",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -23
    },
    {
        "question": "312 x 61",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 19032
    },
    {
        "question": "85 + 59",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 144
    },
    {
        "question": "183 + 65",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 248
    },
    {
        "question": "373 - 53",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 320
    },
    {
        "question": "222 + 5",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 227
    },
    {
        "question": "190 x 21",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 3990
    },
    {
        "question": "128 + 57",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 185
    },
    {
        "question": "158 + 89",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 247
    },
    {
        "question": "140 + 49",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 189
    },
    {
        "question": "181 - 45",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 136
    },
    {
        "question": "165 + 73",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 238
    },
    {
        "question": "49 x 59",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 2891
    },
    {
        "question": "122 + 91",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 213
    },
    {
        "question": "392 x 19",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 7448
    },
    {
        "question": "356 + 77",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 433
    },
    {
        "question": "167 + 1",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 168
    },
    {
        "question": "77 + 77",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 154
    },
    {
        "question": "295 - 21",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 274
    },
    {
        "question": "87 x 69",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 6003
    },
    {
        "question": "185 - 3",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 182
    },
    {
        "question": "335 - 31",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 304
    },
    {
        "question": "295 - 83",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 212
    },
    {
        "question": "267 + 37",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 304
    },
    {
        "question": "178 - 43",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 135
    },
    {
        "question": "261 + 73",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 334
    },
    {
        "question": "369 + 79",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 448
    },
    {
        "question": "281 + 41",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 322
    },
    {
        "question": "186 x 53",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 9858
    },
    {
        "question": "83 x 53",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 4399
    },
    {
        "question": "112 - 77",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 35
    },
    {
        "question": "183 - 21",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 162
    },
    {
        "question": "187 + 79",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 266
    },
    {
        "question": "197 x 31",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 6107
    },
    {
        "question": "96 - 1",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 95
    },
    {
        "question": "261 + 3",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 264
    },
    {
        "question": "323 - 41",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 282
    },
    {
        "question": "2 - 75",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -73
    },
    {
        "question": "66 - 23",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 43
    },
    {
        "question": "242 + 77",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 319
    },
    {
        "question": "21 - 99",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -78
    },
    {
        "question": "247 x 97",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 23959
    },
    {
        "question": "384 + 53",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 437
    },
    {
        "question": "332 - 85",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 247
    },
    {
        "question": "274 x 19",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 5206
    },
    {
        "question": "190 x 37",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 7030
    },
    {
        "question": "143 + 77",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 220
    },
    {
        "question": "54 + 37",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 91
    },
    {
        "question": "248 x 31",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 7688
    },
    {
        "question": "103 + 55",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 158
    },
    {
        "question": "62 + 1",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 63
    },
    {
        "question": "143 - 73",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 70
    },
    {
        "question": "106 - 29",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 77
    },
    {
        "question": "289 - 9",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 280
    },
    {
        "question": "109 x 71",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 7739
    },
    {
        "question": "29 + 13",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 42
    },
    {
        "question": "90 - 59",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 31
    },
    {
        "question": "198 + 99",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 297
    },
    {
        "question": "98 x 33",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 3234
    },
    {
        "question": "286 + 63",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 349
    },
    {
        "question": "199 x 93",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 18507
    },
    {
        "question": "153 x 41",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 6273
    },
    {
        "question": "358 + 19",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 377
    },
    {
        "question": "204 + 67",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 271
    },
    {
        "question": "347 + 69",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 416
    },
    {
        "question": "280 + 15",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 295
    },
    {
        "question": "69 + 67",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 136
    },
    {
        "question": "165 + 45",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 210
    },
    {
        "question": "33 + 59",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 92
    },
    {
        "question": "397 x 35",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 13895
    },
    {
        "question": "144 x 27",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 3888
    },
    {
        "question": "74 + 1",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 75
    },
    {
        "question": "269 - 97",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 172
    },
    {
        "question": "217 x 17",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 3689
    },
    {
        "question": "340 - 47",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 293
    },
    {
        "question": "107 - 37",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 70
    },
    {
        "question": "361 - 47",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 314
    },
    {
        "question": "321 + 17",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 338
    },
    {
        "question": "103 + 63",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 166
    },
    {
        "question": "377 x 41",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 15457
    },
    {
        "question": "300 + 23",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 323
    },
    {
        "question": "121 x 69",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 8349
    },
    {
        "question": "27 + 49",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 76
    },
    {
        "question": "43 - 9",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 34
    },
    {
        "question": "248 x 59",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 14632
    },
    {
        "question": "38 x 41",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1558
    },
    {
        "question": "306 x 81",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 24786
    },
    {
        "question": "362 - 75",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 287
    },
    {
        "question": "335 x 39",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 13065
    },
    {
        "question": "344 x 57",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 19608
    },
    {
        "question": "3 - 13",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -10
    },
    {
        "question": "235 - 89",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 146
    },
    {
        "question": "33 + 29",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 62
    },
    {
        "question": "61 - 85",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -24
    },
    {
        "question": "76 + 57",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 133
    },
    {
        "question": "107 x 11",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1177
    },
    {
        "question": "322 - 91",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 231
    },
    {
        "question": "281 - 25",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 256
    },
    {
        "question": "224 + 11",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 235
    },
    {
        "question": "56 - 67",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -11
    },
    {
        "question": "164 x 23",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 3772
    },
    {
        "question": "13 - 53",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -40
    },
    {
        "question": "73 x 29",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 2117
    },
    {
        "question": "84 x 21",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1764
    },
    {
        "question": "396 x 13",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 5148
    },
    {
        "question": "238 + 39",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 277
    },
    {
        "question": "38 + 17",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 55
    },
    {
        "question": "246 - 49",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 197
    },
    {
        "question": "237 + 61",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 298
    },
    {
        "question": "152 + 75",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 227
    },
    {
        "question": "48 + 79",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 127
    },
    {
        "question": "209 - 19",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 190
    },
    {
        "question": "142 + 35",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 177
    },
    {
        "question": "241 x 43",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 10363
    },
    {
        "question": "138 x 67",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 9246
    },
    {
        "question": "380 - 47",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 333
    },
    {
        "question": "376 x 93",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 34968
    },
    {
        "question": "193 + 87",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 280
    },
    {
        "question": "99 - 95",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 4
    },
    {
        "question": "88 + 91",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 179
    },
    {
        "question": "399 + 13",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 412
    },
    {
        "question": "162 - 53",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 109
    },
    {
        "question": "227 x 69",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 15663
    },
    {
        "question": "178 + 67",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 245
    },
    {
        "question": "136 + 87",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 223
    },
    {
        "question": "218 x 45",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 9810
    },
    {
        "question": "107 x 25",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 2675
    },
    {
        "question": "39 + 75",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 114
    },
    {
        "question": "378 - 93",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 285
    },
    {
        "question": "50 + 89",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 139
    },
    {
        "question": "6 + 71",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 77
    },
    {
        "question": "368 + 27",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 395
    },
    {
        "question": "103 x 85",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 8755
    },
    {
        "question": "388 + 69",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 457
    },
    {
        "question": "47 - 79",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -32
    },
    {
        "question": "82 + 67",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 149
    },
    {
        "question": "53 + 91",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 144
    },
    {
        "question": "92 x 65",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 5980
    },
    {
        "question": "259 + 93",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 352
    },
    {
        "question": "232 - 69",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 163
    },
    {
        "question": "224 - 49",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 175
    },
    {
        "question": "52 - 91",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -39
    },
    {
        "question": "60 + 99",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 159
    },
    {
        "question": "192 - 71",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 121
    },
    {
        "question": "286 - 57",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 229
    },
    {
        "question": "63 x 47",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 2961
    },
    {
        "question": "113 x 17",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1921
    },
    {
        "question": "4 - 33",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -29
    },
    {
        "question": "11 + 37",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 48
    },
    {
        "question": "127 x 41",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 5207
    },
    {
        "question": "285 + 31",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 316
    },
    {
        "question": "113 - 43",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 70
    },
    {
        "question": "252 + 3",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 255
    },
    {
        "question": "343 + 31",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 374
    },
    {
        "question": "244 - 97",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 147
    },
    {
        "question": "359 + 29",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 388
    },
    {
        "question": "339 + 15",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 354
    },
    {
        "question": "75 x 81",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 6075
    },
    {
        "question": "180 x 87",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 15660
    },
    {
        "question": "21 - 35",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -14
    },
    {
        "question": "75 + 83",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 158
    },
    {
        "question": "232 x 73",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 16936
    },
    {
        "question": "23 + 3",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 26
    },
    {
        "question": "52 x 21",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1092
    },
    {
        "question": "36 + 43",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 79
    },
    {
        "question": "304 - 45",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 259
    },
    {
        "question": "17 + 85",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 102
    },
    {
        "question": "108 - 7",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 101
    },
    {
        "question": "39 + 67",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 106
    },
    {
        "question": "170 + 45",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 215
    },
    {
        "question": "12 x 29",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 348
    },
    {
        "question": "326 - 53",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 273
    },
    {
        "question": "13 + 5",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 18
    },
    {
        "question": "267 + 67",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 334
    },
    {
        "question": "201 - 57",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 144
    },
    {
        "question": "325 - 47",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 278
    },
    {
        "question": "206 + 13",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 219
    },
    {
        "question": "313 - 17",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 296
    },
    {
        "question": "291 x 19",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 5529
    },
    {
        "question": "299 + 19",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 318
    },
    {
        "question": "216 x 95",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 20520
    },
    {
        "question": "221 - 45",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 176
    },
    {
        "question": "176 + 41",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 217
    },
    {
        "question": "277 - 1",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 276
    },
    {
        "question": "107 - 11",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 96
    },
    {
        "question": "376 + 33",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 409
    },
    {
        "question": "200 - 7",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 193
    },
    {
        "question": "325 x 69",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 22425
    },
    {
        "question": "151 - 23",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 128
    },
    {
        "question": "371 - 23",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 348
    },
    {
        "question": "5 - 45",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -40
    },
    {
        "question": "234 + 69",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 303
    },
    {
        "question": "340 x 5",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1700
    },
    {
        "question": "390 x 95",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 37050
    },
    {
        "question": "126 + 65",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 191
    },
    {
        "question": "112 + 57",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 169
    },
    {
        "question": "104 - 37",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 67
    },
    {
        "question": "398 + 57",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 455
    },
    {
        "question": "138 + 69",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 207
    },
    {
        "question": "214 + 67",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 281
    },
    {
        "question": "174 - 85",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 89
    },
    {
        "question": "220 + 83",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 303
    },
    {
        "question": "332 + 85",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 417
    },
    {
        "question": "293 x 91",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 26663
    },
    {
        "question": "217 + 11",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 228
    },
    {
        "question": "131 - 63",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 68
    },
    {
        "question": "372 - 91",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 281
    },
    {
        "question": "184 + 91",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 275
    },
    {
        "question": "260 - 51",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 209
    },
    {
        "question": "299 + 17",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 316
    },
    {
        "question": "43 + 31",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 74
    },
    {
        "question": "267 + 79",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 346
    },
    {
        "question": "87 - 7",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 80
    },
    {
        "question": "123 - 47",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 76
    },
    {
        "question": "284 + 47",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 331
    },
    {
        "question": "5 - 63",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -58
    },
    {
        "question": "294 + 25",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 319
    },
    {
        "question": "303 - 21",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 282
    },
    {
        "question": "303 - 35",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 268
    },
    {
        "question": "392 - 99",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 293
    },
    {
        "question": "111 x 37",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 4107
    },
    {
        "question": "322 + 85",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 407
    },
    {
        "question": "307 x 29",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 8903
    },
    {
        "question": "144 x 57",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 8208
    },
    {
        "question": "317 x 65",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 20605
    },
    {
        "question": "395 x 31",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 12245
    },
    {
        "question": "274 x 43",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 11782
    },
    {
        "question": "321 - 59",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 262
    },
    {
        "question": "47 - 49",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -2
    },
    {
        "question": "222 + 91",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 313
    },
    {
        "question": "389 - 21",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 368
    },
    {
        "question": "398 - 55",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 343
    },
    {
        "question": "82 x 87",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 7134
    },
    {
        "question": "383 - 3",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 380
    },
    {
        "question": "393 x 57",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 22401
    },
    {
        "question": "191 + 21",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 212
    },
    {
        "question": "300 x 59",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 17700
    },
    {
        "question": "77 + 63",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 140
    },
    {
        "question": "195 x 45",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 8775
    },
    {
        "question": "19 + 73",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 92
    },
    {
        "question": "309 - 51",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 258
    },
    {
        "question": "215 + 81",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 296
    },
    {
        "question": "41 + 7",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 48
    },
    {
        "question": "266 + 31",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 297
    },
    {
        "question": "106 + 37",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 143
    },
    {
        "question": "240 + 73",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 313
    },
    {
        "question": "173 + 21",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 194
    },
    {
        "question": "158 x 83",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 13114
    },
    {
        "question": "52 x 7",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 364
    },
    {
        "question": "345 x 79",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 27255
    },
    {
        "question": "190 - 41",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 149
    },
    {
        "question": "393 - 21",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 372
    },
    {
        "question": "310 x 55",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 17050
    },
    {
        "question": "21 - 47",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -26
    },
    {
        "question": "176 x 9",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1584
    },
    {
        "question": "194 + 99",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 293
    },
    {
        "question": "234 - 49",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 185
    },
    {
        "question": "59 + 63",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 122
    },
    {
        "question": "312 x 45",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 14040
    },
    {
        "question": "198 + 35",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 233
    },
    {
        "question": "347 - 3",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 344
    },
    {
        "question": "188 - 83",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 105
    },
    {
        "question": "250 x 63",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 15750
    },
    {
        "question": "387 x 61",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 23607
    },
    {
        "question": "274 x 89",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 24386
    },
    {
        "question": "242 + 71",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 313
    },
    {
        "question": "18 + 91",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 109
    },
    {
        "question": "35 - 67",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -32
    },
    {
        "question": "105 + 13",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 118
    },
    {
        "question": "104 - 3",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 101
    },
    {
        "question": "177 x 11",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1947
    },
    {
        "question": "390 - 79",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 311
    },
    {
        "question": "140 x 95",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 13300
    },
    {
        "question": "251 - 79",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 172
    },
    {
        "question": "309 + 11",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 320
    },
    {
        "question": "382 - 89",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 293
    },
    {
        "question": "192 + 19",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 211
    },
    {
        "question": "359 + 11",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 370
    },
    {
        "question": "212 + 23",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 235
    },
    {
        "question": "368 + 11",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 379
    },
    {
        "question": "159 + 49",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 208
    },
    {
        "question": "358 - 47",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 311
    },
    {
        "question": "333 - 43",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 290
    },
    {
        "question": "126 + 69",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 195
    },
    {
        "question": "243 - 9",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 234
    },
    {
        "question": "141 - 83",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 58
    },
    {
        "question": "311 - 83",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 228
    },
    {
        "question": "306 x 53",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 16218
    },
    {
        "question": "100 - 37",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 63
    },
    {
        "question": "72 + 75",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 147
    },
    {
        "question": "367 x 57",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 20919
    },
    {
        "question": "397 + 11",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 408
    },
    {
        "question": "324 - 5",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 319
    },
    {
        "question": "348 + 81",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 429
    },
    {
        "question": "350 + 67",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 417
    },
    {
        "question": "361 - 45",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 316
    },
    {
        "question": "388 x 3",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1164
    },
    {
        "question": "39 x 89",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 3471
    },
    {
        "question": "324 + 29",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 353
    },
    {
        "question": "199 - 51",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 148
    },
    {
        "question": "394 + 23",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 417
    },
    {
        "question": "26 - 39",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -13
    },
    {
        "question": "127 x 11",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1397
    },
    {
        "question": "249 + 31",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 280
    },
    {
        "question": "211 + 55",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 266
    },
    {
        "question": "243 x 51",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 12393
    },
    {
        "question": "350 - 75",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 275
    },
    {
        "question": "149 - 33",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 116
    },
    {
        "question": "271 x 17",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 4607
    },
    {
        "question": "190 + 15",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 205
    },
    {
        "question": "143 - 15",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 128
    },
    {
        "question": "10 x 71",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 710
    },
    {
        "question": "51 + 15",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 66
    },
    {
        "question": "189 x 1",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 189
    },
    {
        "question": "179 - 67",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 112
    },
    {
        "question": "179 x 91",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 16289
    },
    {
        "question": "164 x 75",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 12300
    },
    {
        "question": "154 + 25",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 179
    },
    {
        "question": "229 - 63",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 166
    },
    {
        "question": "60 - 85",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -25
    },
    {
        "question": "139 x 69",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 9591
    },
    {
        "question": "281 x 35",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 9835
    },
    {
        "question": "355 x 93",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 33015
    },
    {
        "question": "393 + 29",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 422
    },
    {
        "question": "260 + 9",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 269
    },
    {
        "question": "149 - 73",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 76
    },
    {
        "question": "82 - 97",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -15
    },
    {
        "question": "114 - 75",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 39
    },
    {
        "question": "10 - 75",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -65
    },
    {
        "question": "71 + 99",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 170
    },
    {
        "question": "347 + 75",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 422
    },
    {
        "question": "283 x 45",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 12735
    },
    {
        "question": "393 x 77",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 30261
    },
    {
        "question": "148 + 65",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 213
    },
    {
        "question": "90 - 7",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 83
    },
    {
        "question": "317 - 69",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 248
    },
    {
        "question": "106 x 89",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 9434
    },
    {
        "question": "260 x 85",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 22100
    },
    {
        "question": "388 x 99",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 38412
    },
    {
        "question": "304 + 3",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 307
    },
    {
        "question": "25 x 83",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 2075
    },
    {
        "question": "25 - 85",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -60
    },
    {
        "question": "181 + 61",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 242
    },
    {
        "question": "344 x 1",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 344
    },
    {
        "question": "41 - 95",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -54
    },
    {
        "question": "218 + 59",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 277
    },
    {
        "question": "261 - 83",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 178
    },
    {
        "question": "367 + 97",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 464
    },
    {
        "question": "399 x 35",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 13965
    },
    {
        "question": "383 - 39",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 344
    },
    {
        "question": "95 x 49",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 4655
    },
    {
        "question": "36 - 55",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -19
    },
    {
        "question": "239 x 61",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 14579
    },
    {
        "question": "73 x 9",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 657
    },
    {
        "question": "277 + 71",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 348
    },
    {
        "question": "295 x 19",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 5605
    },
    {
        "question": "372 + 91",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 463
    },
    {
        "question": "359 - 75",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 284
    },
    {
        "question": "146 x 11",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1606
    },
    {
        "question": "214 x 69",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 14766
    },
    {
        "question": "238 - 65",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 173
    },
    {
        "question": "126 x 51",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 6426
    },
    {
        "question": "392 + 69",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 461
    },
    {
        "question": "272 x 43",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 11696
    },
    {
        "question": "380 + 83",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 463
    },
    {
        "question": "167 - 63",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 104
    },
    {
        "question": "393 - 91",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 302
    },
    {
        "question": "107 x 23",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 2461
    },
    {
        "question": "135 x 25",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 3375
    },
    {
        "question": "10 + 75",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 85
    },
    {
        "question": "258 - 21",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 237
    },
    {
        "question": "311 - 21",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 290
    },
    {
        "question": "372 + 51",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 423
    },
    {
        "question": "233 x 93",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 21669
    },
    {
        "question": "62 + 7",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 69
    },
    {
        "question": "46 - 87",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -41
    },
    {
        "question": "173 + 63",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 236
    },
    {
        "question": "316 x 87",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 27492
    },
    {
        "question": "232 x 55",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 12760
    },
    {
        "question": "122 - 89",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 33
    },
    {
        "question": "78 - 1",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 77
    },
    {
        "question": "219 + 53",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 272
    },
    {
        "question": "225 x 81",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 18225
    },
    {
        "question": "106 x 37",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 3922
    },
    {
        "question": "53 + 17",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 70
    },
    {
        "question": "358 + 23",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 381
    },
    {
        "question": "317 + 77",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 394
    },
    {
        "question": "136 - 11",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 125
    },
    {
        "question": "225 - 49",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 176
    },
    {
        "question": "101 x 83",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 8383
    },
    {
        "question": "390 - 55",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 335
    },
    {
        "question": "133 x 47",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 6251
    },
    {
        "question": "191 + 65",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 256
    },
    {
        "question": "21 + 41",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 62
    },
    {
        "question": "34 - 63",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -29
    },
    {
        "question": "261 + 37",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 298
    },
    {
        "question": "358 + 7",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 365
    },
    {
        "question": "130 + 99",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 229
    },
    {
        "question": "225 - 3",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 222
    },
    {
        "question": "116 - 65",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 51
    },
    {
        "question": "211 + 93",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 304
    },
    {
        "question": "268 x 69",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 18492
    },
    {
        "question": "66 x 17",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1122
    },
    {
        "question": "395 + 87",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 482
    },
    {
        "question": "352 - 25",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 327
    },
    {
        "question": "371 x 15",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 5565
    },
    {
        "question": "82 + 67",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 149
    },
    {
        "question": "260 + 93",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 353
    },
    {
        "question": "110 x 81",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 8910
    },
    {
        "question": "121 - 75",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 46
    },
    {
        "question": "174 x 1",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 174
    },
    {
        "question": "107 - 3",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 104
    },
    {
        "question": "85 + 25",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 110
    },
    {
        "question": "294 - 7",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 287
    },
    {
        "question": "118 + 5",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 123
    },
    {
        "question": "138 + 21",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 159
    },
    {
        "question": "339 - 65",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 274
    },
    {
        "question": "351 x 75",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 26325
    },
    {
        "question": "243 + 65",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 308
    },
    {
        "question": "27 - 87",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -60
    },
    {
        "question": "39 x 47",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1833
    },
    {
        "question": "322 + 43",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 365
    },
    {
        "question": "66 x 55",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 3630
    },
    {
        "question": "152 x 43",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 6536
    },
    {
        "question": "159 - 5",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 154
    },
    {
        "question": "274 - 1",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 273
    },
    {
        "question": "160 x 23",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 3680
    },
    {
        "question": "13 - 23",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -10
    },
    {
        "question": "236 - 47",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 189
    },
    {
        "question": "30 x 67",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 2010
    },
    {
        "question": "96 x 49",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 4704
    },
    {
        "question": "239 - 67",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 172
    },
    {
        "question": "21 + 61",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 82
    },
    {
        "question": "108 x 29",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 3132
    },
    {
        "question": "196 + 55",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 251
    },
    {
        "question": "191 + 23",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 214
    },
    {
        "question": "193 - 69",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 124
    },
    {
        "question": "239 + 89",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 328
    },
    {
        "question": "86 x 53",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 4558
    },
    {
        "question": "62 - 27",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 35
    },
    {
        "question": "300 + 41",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 341
    },
    {
        "question": "359 x 47",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 16873
    },
    {
        "question": "10 + 77",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 87
    },
    {
        "question": "41 + 3",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 44
    },
    {
        "question": "359 + 69",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 428
    },
    {
        "question": "241 + 87",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 328
    },
    {
        "question": "313 x 25",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 7825
    },
    {
        "question": "24 + 87",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 111
    },
    {
        "question": "52 + 57",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 109
    },
    {
        "question": "11 x 75",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 825
    },
    {
        "question": "148 - 57",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 91
    },
    {
        "question": "101 x 55",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 5555
    },
    {
        "question": "347 - 47",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 300
    },
    {
        "question": "343 - 81",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 262
    },
    {
        "question": "236 + 5",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 241
    },
    {
        "question": "318 + 57",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 375
    },
    {
        "question": "70 - 9",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 61
    },
    {
        "question": "276 + 53",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 329
    },
    {
        "question": "148 x 49",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 7252
    },
    {
        "question": "34 - 97",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -63
    },
    {
        "question": "84 x 21",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1764
    },
    {
        "question": "279 - 29",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 250
    },
    {
        "question": "93 x 33",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 3069
    },
    {
        "question": "396 x 65",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 25740
    },
    {
        "question": "314 + 69",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 383
    },
    {
        "question": "299 - 5",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 294
    },
    {
        "question": "281 - 67",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 214
    },
    {
        "question": "324 x 39",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 12636
    },
    {
        "question": "168 - 41",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 127
    },
    {
        "question": "231 + 79",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 310
    },
    {
        "question": "309 + 61",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 370
    },
    {
        "question": "172 - 5",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 167
    },
    {
        "question": "75 - 25",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 50
    },
    {
        "question": "320 - 87",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 233
    },
    {
        "question": "357 - 35",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 322
    },
    {
        "question": "355 + 89",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 444
    },
    {
        "question": "254 + 1",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 255
    },
    {
        "question": "178 - 67",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 111
    },
    {
        "question": "128 x 99",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 12672
    },
    {
        "question": "385 - 25",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 360
    },
    {
        "question": "75 x 71",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 5325
    },
    {
        "question": "188 - 33",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 155
    },
    {
        "question": "328 x 43",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 14104
    },
    {
        "question": "232 - 1",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 231
    },
    {
        "question": "212 - 9",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 203
    },
    {
        "question": "276 x 61",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 16836
    },
    {
        "question": "360 - 31",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 329
    },
    {
        "question": "218 x 71",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 15478
    },
    {
        "question": "387 + 39",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 426
    },
    {
        "question": "284 + 29",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 313
    },
    {
        "question": "117 + 13",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 130
    },
    {
        "question": "357 x 71",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 25347
    },
    {
        "question": "51 + 33",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 84
    },
    {
        "question": "176 - 57",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 119
    },
    {
        "question": "89 - 47",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 42
    },
    {
        "question": "377 - 25",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 352
    },
    {
        "question": "267 x 37",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 9879
    },
    {
        "question": "387 x 97",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 37539
    },
    {
        "question": "188 - 93",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 95
    },
    {
        "question": "371 x 97",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 35987
    },
    {
        "question": "229 - 99",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 130
    },
    {
        "question": "254 x 57",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 14478
    },
    {
        "question": "1 x 29",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 29
    },
    {
        "question": "169 x 79",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 13351
    },
    {
        "question": "146 + 63",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 209
    },
    {
        "question": "364 + 85",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 449
    },
    {
        "question": "149 x 97",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 14453
    },
    {
        "question": "391 - 17",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 374
    },
    {
        "question": "231 - 97",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 134
    },
    {
        "question": "194 + 45",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 239
    },
    {
        "question": "18 - 13",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 5
    },
    {
        "question": "25 + 97",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 122
    },
    {
        "question": "181 x 83",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 15023
    },
    {
        "question": "304 - 11",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 293
    },
    {
        "question": "278 + 83",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 361
    },
    {
        "question": "319 x 33",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 10527
    },
    {
        "question": "260 x 47",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 12220
    },
    {
        "question": "321 x 81",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 26001
    },
    {
        "question": "385 x 51",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 19635
    },
    {
        "question": "195 - 17",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 178
    },
    {
        "question": "104 + 21",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 125
    },
    {
        "question": "112 - 37",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 75
    },
    {
        "question": "360 - 29",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 331
    },
    {
        "question": "161 x 51",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 8211
    },
    {
        "question": "353 + 23",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 376
    },
    {
        "question": "133 x 71",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 9443
    },
    {
        "question": "384 - 35",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 349
    },
    {
        "question": "257 x 35",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 8995
    },
    {
        "question": "22 + 3",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 25
    },
    {
        "question": "12 x 23",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 276
    },
    {
        "question": "321 + 47",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 368
    },
    {
        "question": "259 x 1",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 259
    },
    {
        "question": "293 + 3",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 296
    },
    {
        "question": "46 - 55",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -9
    },
    {
        "question": "147 + 69",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 216
    },
    {
        "question": "252 - 11",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 241
    },
    {
        "question": "236 x 85",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 20060
    },
    {
        "question": "286 x 79",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 22594
    },
    {
        "question": "130 - 33",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 97
    },
    {
        "question": "38 x 57",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 2166
    },
    {
        "question": "254 + 33",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 287
    },
    {
        "question": "80 x 83",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 6640
    },
    {
        "question": "325 - 75",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 250
    },
    {
        "question": "246 - 33",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 213
    },
    {
        "question": "145 + 89",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 234
    },
    {
        "question": "301 + 55",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 356
    },
    {
        "question": "245 x 75",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 18375
    },
    {
        "question": "333 x 21",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 6993
    },
    {
        "question": "85 - 89",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -4
    },
    {
        "question": "300 x 69",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 20700
    },
    {
        "question": "17 - 61",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -44
    },
    {
        "question": "11 x 89",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 979
    },
    {
        "question": "81 - 1",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 80
    },
    {
        "question": "293 + 81",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 374
    },
    {
        "question": "180 - 11",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 169
    },
    {
        "question": "283 - 85",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 198
    },
    {
        "question": "356 x 49",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 17444
    },
    {
        "question": "206 - 19",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 187
    },
    {
        "question": "211 x 47",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 9917
    },
    {
        "question": "364 - 23",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 341
    },
    {
        "question": "362 x 87",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 31494
    },
    {
        "question": "27 - 5",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 22
    },
    {
        "question": "394 + 97",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 491
    },
    {
        "question": "182 - 69",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 113
    },
    {
        "question": "99 - 17",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 82
    },
    {
        "question": "186 + 17",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 203
    },
    {
        "question": "162 x 97",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 15714
    },
    {
        "question": "280 - 51",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 229
    },
    {
        "question": "18 + 3",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 21
    },
    {
        "question": "225 x 25",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 5625
    },
    {
        "question": "190 x 63",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 11970
    },
    {
        "question": "165 + 41",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 206
    },
    {
        "question": "39 + 85",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 124
    },
    {
        "question": "97 x 55",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 5335
    },
    {
        "question": "376 - 73",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 303
    },
    {
        "question": "168 x 11",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1848
    },
    {
        "question": "221 - 39",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 182
    },
    {
        "question": "195 + 9",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 204
    },
    {
        "question": "62 - 67",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -5
    },
    {
        "question": "134 - 19",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 115
    },
    {
        "question": "68 - 53",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 15
    },
    {
        "question": "239 + 57",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 296
    },
    {
        "question": "233 - 59",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 174
    },
    {
        "question": "359 - 89",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 270
    },
    {
        "question": "354 x 67",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 23718
    },
    {
        "question": "213 - 83",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 130
    },
    {
        "question": "90 x 23",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 2070
    },
    {
        "question": "258 + 65",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 323
    },
    {
        "question": "299 - 45",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 254
    },
    {
        "question": "191 x 29",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 5539
    },
    {
        "question": "5 x 49",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 245
    },
    {
        "question": "334 x 81",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 27054
    },
    {
        "question": "90 + 67",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 157
    },
    {
        "question": "119 + 13",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 132
    },
    {
        "question": "21 x 77",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1617
    },
    {
        "question": "352 x 3",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1056
    },
    {
        "question": "351 - 55",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 296
    },
    {
        "question": "289 x 73",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 21097
    },
    {
        "question": "252 - 39",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 213
    },
    {
        "question": "341 - 11",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 330
    },
    {
        "question": "184 + 97",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 281
    },
    {
        "question": "237 - 47",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 190
    },
    {
        "question": "179 - 99",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 80
    },
    {
        "question": "219 + 63",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 282
    },
    {
        "question": "207 + 21",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 228
    },
    {
        "question": "340 - 99",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 241
    },
    {
        "question": "115 x 63",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 7245
    },
    {
        "question": "194 + 89",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 283
    },
    {
        "question": "80 + 91",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 171
    },
    {
        "question": "381 - 31",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 350
    },
    {
        "question": "211 - 47",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 164
    },
    {
        "question": "187 - 73",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 114
    },
    {
        "question": "249 + 51",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 300
    },
    {
        "question": "318 + 19",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 337
    },
    {
        "question": "269 - 33",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 236
    },
    {
        "question": "2 - 43",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -41
    },
    {
        "question": "349 x 97",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 33853
    },
    {
        "question": "396 x 87",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 34452
    },
    {
        "question": "115 + 71",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 186
    },
    {
        "question": "78 x 15",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1170
    },
    {
        "question": "253 x 71",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 17963
    },
    {
        "question": "114 x 7",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 798
    },
    {
        "question": "144 x 75",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 10800
    },
    {
        "question": "381 - 69",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 312
    },
    {
        "question": "368 x 57",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 20976
    },
    {
        "question": "363 + 21",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 384
    },
    {
        "question": "385 x 13",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 5005
    },
    {
        "question": "160 + 17",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 177
    },
    {
        "question": "367 + 5",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 372
    },
    {
        "question": "347 + 11",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 358
    },
    {
        "question": "115 x 85",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 9775
    },
    {
        "question": "235 x 75",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 17625
    },
    {
        "question": "98 x 77",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 7546
    },
    {
        "question": "391 - 85",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 306
    },
    {
        "question": "108 x 53",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 5724
    },
    {
        "question": "156 - 93",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 63
    },
    {
        "question": "219 x 93",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 20367
    },
    {
        "question": "391 + 33",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 424
    },
    {
        "question": "399 x 27",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 10773
    },
    {
        "question": "145 - 65",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 80
    },
    {
        "question": "48 - 95",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -47
    },
    {
        "question": "308 + 47",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 355
    },
    {
        "question": "78 + 31",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 109
    },
    {
        "question": "386 - 99",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 287
    },
    {
        "question": "126 + 55",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 181
    },
    {
        "question": "339 - 21",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 318
    },
    {
        "question": "220 x 5",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1100
    },
    {
        "question": "79 x 93",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 7347
    },
    {
        "question": "38 x 77",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 2926
    },
    {
        "question": "132 + 65",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 197
    },
    {
        "question": "390 + 59",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 449
    },
    {
        "question": "311 + 59",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 370
    },
    {
        "question": "71 - 43",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 28
    },
    {
        "question": "369 - 89",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 280
    },
    {
        "question": "142 + 39",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 181
    },
    {
        "question": "378 - 25",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 353
    },
    {
        "question": "5 - 93",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -88
    },
    {
        "question": "396 - 29",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 367
    },
    {
        "question": "102 - 79",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 23
    },
    {
        "question": "251 x 77",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 19327
    },
    {
        "question": "247 x 7",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1729
    },
    {
        "question": "217 + 43",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 260
    },
    {
        "question": "150 + 21",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 171
    },
    {
        "question": "104 + 9",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 113
    },
    {
        "question": "108 - 45",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 63
    },
    {
        "question": "214 x 89",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 19046
    },
    {
        "question": "56 - 1",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 55
    },
    {
        "question": "373 x 79",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 29467
    },
    {
        "question": "63 x 51",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 3213
    },
    {
        "question": "248 x 99",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 24552
    },
    {
        "question": "150 - 45",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 105
    },
    {
        "question": "331 - 93",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 238
    },
    {
        "question": "47 - 65",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -18
    },
    {
        "question": "241 - 99",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 142
    },
    {
        "question": "360 - 61",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 299
    },
    {
        "question": "85 - 11",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 74
    },
    {
        "question": "70 - 5",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 65
    },
    {
        "question": "247 x 71",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 17537
    },
    {
        "question": "221 x 3",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 663
    },
    {
        "question": "372 + 93",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 465
    },
    {
        "question": "203 - 75",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 128
    },
    {
        "question": "297 - 49",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 248
    },
    {
        "question": "31 - 51",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -20
    },
    {
        "question": "224 - 5",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 219
    },
    {
        "question": "321 + 69",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 390
    },
    {
        "question": "351 x 45",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 15795
    },
    {
        "question": "89 - 37",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 52
    },
    {
        "question": "274 - 11",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 263
    },
    {
        "question": "386 x 69",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 26634
    },
    {
        "question": "246 + 81",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 327
    },
    {
        "question": "199 + 21",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 220
    },
    {
        "question": "93 x 75",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 6975
    },
    {
        "question": "19 + 7",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 26
    },
    {
        "question": "366 - 7",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 359
    },
    {
        "question": "287 - 93",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 194
    },
    {
        "question": "176 - 57",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 119
    },
    {
        "question": "223 x 55",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 12265
    },
    {
        "question": "309 - 81",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 228
    },
    {
        "question": "384 - 1",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 383
    },
    {
        "question": "80 - 37",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 43
    },
    {
        "question": "19 + 23",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 42
    },
    {
        "question": "158 - 61",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 97
    },
    {
        "question": "55 - 19",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 36
    },
    {
        "question": "181 + 79",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 260
    },
    {
        "question": "94 x 93",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 8742
    },
    {
        "question": "310 - 27",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 283
    },
    {
        "question": "360 x 57",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 20520
    },
    {
        "question": "69 - 57",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 12
    },
    {
        "question": "95 x 99",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 9405
    },
    {
        "question": "360 - 51",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 309
    },
    {
        "question": "324 - 83",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 241
    },
    {
        "question": "40 x 71",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 2840
    },
    {
        "question": "35 + 51",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 86
    },
    {
        "question": "297 + 7",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 304
    },
    {
        "question": "233 + 61",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 294
    },
    {
        "question": "110 - 31",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 79
    },
    {
        "question": "142 x 57",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 8094
    },
    {
        "question": "86 - 65",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 21
    },
    {
        "question": "326 x 7",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 2282
    },
    {
        "question": "370 + 31",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 401
    },
    {
        "question": "328 x 77",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 25256
    },
    {
        "question": "369 - 91",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 278
    },
    {
        "question": "348 - 15",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 333
    },
    {
        "question": "4 - 39",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -35
    },
    {
        "question": "300 + 61",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 361
    },
    {
        "question": "282 - 23",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 259
    },
    {
        "question": "118 x 75",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 8850
    },
    {
        "question": "229 - 11",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 218
    },
    {
        "question": "131 - 67",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 64
    },
    {
        "question": "230 + 91",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 321
    },
    {
        "question": "165 + 99",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 264
    },
    {
        "question": "392 - 35",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 357
    },
    {
        "question": "8 + 47",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 55
    },
    {
        "question": "379 - 63",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 316
    },
    {
        "question": "128 x 5",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 640
    },
    {
        "question": "43 - 65",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -22
    },
    {
        "question": "331 x 67",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 22177
    },
    {
        "question": "69 + 61",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 130
    },
    {
        "question": "280 x 83",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 23240
    },
    {
        "question": "67 - 99",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -32
    },
    {
        "question": "314 x 93",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 29202
    },
    {
        "question": "284 + 21",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 305
    },
    {
        "question": "236 - 51",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 185
    },
    {
        "question": "270 - 81",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 189
    },
    {
        "question": "69 + 61",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 130
    },
    {
        "question": "292 x 29",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 8468
    },
    {
        "question": "284 - 93",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 191
    },
    {
        "question": "180 x 13",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 2340
    },
    {
        "question": "347 + 27",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 374
    },
    {
        "question": "28 x 43",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1204
    },
    {
        "question": "336 x 77",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 25872
    },
    {
        "question": "182 x 59",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 10738
    },
    {
        "question": "47 x 89",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 4183
    },
    {
        "question": "348 - 29",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 319
    },
    {
        "question": "282 x 75",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 21150
    },
    {
        "question": "150 x 81",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 12150
    },
    {
        "question": "250 - 69",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 181
    },
    {
        "question": "180 x 7",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1260
    },
    {
        "question": "252 - 69",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 183
    },
    {
        "question": "231 + 83",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 314
    },
    {
        "question": "231 + 69",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 300
    },
    {
        "question": "267 - 25",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 242
    },
    {
        "question": "77 - 29",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 48
    },
    {
        "question": "46 - 3",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 43
    },
    {
        "question": "142 x 23",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 3266
    },
    {
        "question": "56 + 89",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 145
    },
    {
        "question": "12 + 89",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 101
    },
    {
        "question": "389 x 99",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 38511
    },
    {
        "question": "67 x 27",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1809
    },
    {
        "question": "171 + 55",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 226
    },
    {
        "question": "367 x 41",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 15047
    },
    {
        "question": "22 x 11",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 242
    },
    {
        "question": "29 + 77",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 106
    },
    {
        "question": "53 + 81",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 134
    },
    {
        "question": "161 - 71",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 90
    },
    {
        "question": "350 x 33",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 11550
    },
    {
        "question": "89 - 11",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 78
    },
    {
        "question": "184 + 59",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 243
    },
    {
        "question": "102 x 9",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 918
    },
    {
        "question": "357 x 39",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 13923
    },
    {
        "question": "241 + 91",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 332
    },
    {
        "question": "21 - 43",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -22
    },
    {
        "question": "164 + 55",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 219
    },
    {
        "question": "17 x 75",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1275
    },
    {
        "question": "193 - 47",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 146
    },
    {
        "question": "248 - 77",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 171
    },
    {
        "question": "181 x 81",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 14661
    },
    {
        "question": "239 x 91",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 21749
    },
    {
        "question": "137 x 13",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1781
    },
    {
        "question": "296 + 57",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 353
    },
    {
        "question": "114 x 13",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1482
    },
    {
        "question": "94 - 49",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 45
    },
    {
        "question": "172 x 31",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 5332
    },
    {
        "question": "362 + 17",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 379
    },
    {
        "question": "32 x 79",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 2528
    },
    {
        "question": "192 - 3",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 189
    },
    {
        "question": "398 + 83",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 481
    },
    {
        "question": "355 - 23",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 332
    },
    {
        "question": "394 + 67",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 461
    },
    {
        "question": "83 x 55",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 4565
    },
    {
        "question": "258 x 19",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 4902
    },
    {
        "question": "321 - 5",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 316
    },
    {
        "question": "265 x 55",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 14575
    },
    {
        "question": "178 - 41",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 137
    },
    {
        "question": "358 + 11",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 369
    },
    {
        "question": "360 + 73",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 433
    },
    {
        "question": "107 x 99",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 10593
    },
    {
        "question": "77 - 5",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 72
    },
    {
        "question": "278 + 33",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 311
    },
    {
        "question": "181 - 11",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 170
    },
    {
        "question": "102 + 41",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 143
    },
    {
        "question": "219 - 75",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 144
    },
    {
        "question": "55 - 73",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -18
    },
    {
        "question": "74 x 69",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 5106
    },
    {
        "question": "318 x 97",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 30846
    },
    {
        "question": "16 - 57",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -41
    },
    {
        "question": "170 - 47",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 123
    },
    {
        "question": "364 x 9",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 3276
    },
    {
        "question": "291 x 73",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 21243
    },
    {
        "question": "228 + 63",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 291
    },
    {
        "question": "367 + 61",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 428
    },
    {
        "question": "1 + 41",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 42
    },
    {
        "question": "16 - 59",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -43
    },
    {
        "question": "31 - 13",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 18
    },
    {
        "question": "355 - 81",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 274
    },
    {
        "question": "358 + 3",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 361
    },
    {
        "question": "178 + 13",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 191
    },
    {
        "question": "391 - 37",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 354
    },
    {
        "question": "69 - 79",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -10
    },
    {
        "question": "151 - 37",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 114
    },
    {
        "question": "48 + 9",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 57
    },
    {
        "question": "214 + 5",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 219
    },
    {
        "question": "7 x 41",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 287
    },
    {
        "question": "49 + 75",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 124
    },
    {
        "question": "393 + 47",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 440
    },
    {
        "question": "104 + 41",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 145
    },
    {
        "question": "377 x 63",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 23751
    },
    {
        "question": "60 - 27",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 33
    },
    {
        "question": "285 + 61",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 346
    },
    {
        "question": "6 + 21",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 27
    },
    {
        "question": "122 x 55",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 6710
    },
    {
        "question": "391 x 29",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 11339
    },
    {
        "question": "134 x 85",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 11390
    },
    {
        "question": "188 x 65",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 12220
    },
    {
        "question": "213 + 93",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 306
    },
    {
        "question": "113 x 41",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 4633
    },
    {
        "question": "90 + 3",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 93
    },
    {
        "question": "212 - 45",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 167
    },
    {
        "question": "360 + 55",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 415
    },
    {
        "question": "67 x 99",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 6633
    },
    {
        "question": "22 + 17",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 39
    },
    {
        "question": "192 - 57",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 135
    },
    {
        "question": "305 + 25",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 330
    },
    {
        "question": "265 x 97",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 25705
    },
    {
        "question": "99 + 31",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 130
    },
    {
        "question": "264 - 53",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 211
    },
    {
        "question": "352 + 43",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 395
    },
    {
        "question": "356 x 69",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 24564
    },
    {
        "question": "97 + 29",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 126
    },
    {
        "question": "366 + 95",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 461
    },
    {
        "question": "275 - 85",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 190
    },
    {
        "question": "383 x 1",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 383
    },
    {
        "question": "55 + 43",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 98
    },
    {
        "question": "147 - 99",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 48
    },
    {
        "question": "232 - 33",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 199
    },
    {
        "question": "94 + 47",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 141
    },
    {
        "question": "249 x 77",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 19173
    },
    {
        "question": "195 + 9",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 204
    },
    {
        "question": "245 - 37",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 208
    },
    {
        "question": "351 x 95",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 33345
    },
    {
        "question": "247 x 27",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 6669
    },
    {
        "question": "294 x 37",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 10878
    },
    {
        "question": "1 x 61",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 61
    },
    {
        "question": "37 + 91",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 128
    },
    {
        "question": "59 - 7",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 52
    },
    {
        "question": "154 - 31",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 123
    },
    {
        "question": "89 + 55",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 144
    },
    {
        "question": "7 x 67",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 469
    },
    {
        "question": "229 x 11",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 2519
    },
    {
        "question": "221 x 41",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 9061
    },
    {
        "question": "385 + 13",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 398
    },
    {
        "question": "338 - 89",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 249
    },
    {
        "question": "6 x 49",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 294
    },
    {
        "question": "87 - 71",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 16
    },
    {
        "question": "96 - 23",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 73
    },
    {
        "question": "339 - 35",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 304
    },
    {
        "question": "236 x 49",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 11564
    },
    {
        "question": "381 + 57",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 438
    },
    {
        "question": "90 + 15",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 105
    },
    {
        "question": "6 + 29",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 35
    },
    {
        "question": "105 x 9",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 945
    },
    {
        "question": "57 x 19",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1083
    },
    {
        "question": "305 x 65",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 19825
    },
    {
        "question": "69 x 81",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 5589
    },
    {
        "question": "173 + 37",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 210
    },
    {
        "question": "50 - 85",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -35
    },
    {
        "question": "261 x 63",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 16443
    },
    {
        "question": "201 x 83",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 16683
    },
    {
        "question": "15 + 55",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 70
    },
    {
        "question": "223 - 1",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 222
    },
    {
        "question": "135 - 1",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 134
    },
    {
        "question": "171 x 51",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 8721
    },
    {
        "question": "136 - 29",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 107
    },
    {
        "question": "69 - 9",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 60
    },
    {
        "question": "207 + 17",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 224
    },
    {
        "question": "393 x 23",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 9039
    },
    {
        "question": "277 x 45",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 12465
    },
    {
        "question": "75 + 23",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 98
    },
    {
        "question": "275 x 65",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 17875
    },
    {
        "question": "110 x 63",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 6930
    },
    {
        "question": "387 + 97",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 484
    },
    {
        "question": "37 + 55",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 92
    },
    {
        "question": "81 + 79",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 160
    },
    {
        "question": "136 - 61",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 75
    },
    {
        "question": "385 - 67",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 318
    },
    {
        "question": "58 x 33",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1914
    },
    {
        "question": "239 x 17",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 4063
    },
    {
        "question": "252 x 81",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 20412
    },
    {
        "question": "109 - 23",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 86
    },
    {
        "question": "57 x 61",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 3477
    },
    {
        "question": "258 + 3",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 261
    },
    {
        "question": "233 + 33",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 266
    },
    {
        "question": "61 + 71",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 132
    },
    {
        "question": "57 - 13",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 44
    },
    {
        "question": "284 - 17",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 267
    },
    {
        "question": "198 + 7",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 205
    },
    {
        "question": "114 x 23",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 2622
    },
    {
        "question": "329 - 25",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 304
    },
    {
        "question": "155 + 97",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 252
    },
    {
        "question": "91 + 77",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 168
    },
    {
        "question": "116 - 73",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 43
    },
    {
        "question": "378 x 11",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 4158
    },
    {
        "question": "86 x 37",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 3182
    },
    {
        "question": "45 + 7",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 52
    },
    {
        "question": "198 - 11",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 187
    },
    {
        "question": "229 x 45",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 10305
    },
    {
        "question": "63 x 61",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 3843
    },
    {
        "question": "359 x 71",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 25489
    },
    {
        "question": "113 - 47",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 66
    },
    {
        "question": "145 - 61",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 84
    },
    {
        "question": "276 + 31",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 307
    },
    {
        "question": "122 - 15",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 107
    },
    {
        "question": "219 + 47",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 266
    },
    {
        "question": "193 + 29",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 222
    },
    {
        "question": "173 - 63",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 110
    },
    {
        "question": "224 - 15",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 209
    },
    {
        "question": "343 x 93",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 31899
    },
    {
        "question": "101 - 89",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 12
    },
    {
        "question": "95 - 27",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 68
    },
    {
        "question": "178 + 25",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 203
    },
    {
        "question": "25 - 45",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -20
    },
    {
        "question": "144 - 51",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 93
    },
    {
        "question": "91 + 51",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 142
    },
    {
        "question": "154 x 23",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 3542
    },
    {
        "question": "207 + 17",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 224
    },
    {
        "question": "325 - 1",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 324
    },
    {
        "question": "282 x 57",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 16074
    },
    {
        "question": "102 - 17",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 85
    },
    {
        "question": "193 + 47",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 240
    },
    {
        "question": "370 x 59",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 21830
    },
    {
        "question": "369 + 93",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 462
    },
    {
        "question": "336 + 83",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 419
    },
    {
        "question": "130 x 45",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 5850
    },
    {
        "question": "128 - 55",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 73
    },
    {
        "question": "118 x 61",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 7198
    },
    {
        "question": "365 - 45",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 320
    },
    {
        "question": "359 - 95",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 264
    },
    {
        "question": "123 - 63",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 60
    },
    {
        "question": "126 + 7",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 133
    },
    {
        "question": "385 + 53",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 438
    },
    {
        "question": "66 + 37",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 103
    },
    {
        "question": "342 x 77",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 26334
    },
    {
        "question": "372 - 21",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 351
    },
    {
        "question": "133 - 25",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 108
    },
    {
        "question": "74 + 29",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 103
    },
    {
        "question": "359 + 97",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 456
    },
    {
        "question": "199 x 5",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 995
    },
    {
        "question": "286 - 81",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 205
    },
    {
        "question": "236 + 23",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 259
    },
    {
        "question": "373 - 73",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 300
    },
    {
        "question": "389 - 41",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 348
    },
    {
        "question": "243 x 49",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 11907
    },
    {
        "question": "224 + 5",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 229
    },
    {
        "question": "149 x 17",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 2533
    },
    {
        "question": "139 + 99",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 238
    },
    {
        "question": "145 x 69",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 10005
    },
    {
        "question": "173 x 15",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 2595
    },
    {
        "question": "379 + 43",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 422
    },
    {
        "question": "116 x 13",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1508
    },
    {
        "question": "382 - 69",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 313
    },
    {
        "question": "56 x 5",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 280
    },
    {
        "question": "131 x 1",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 131
    },
    {
        "question": "24 x 31",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 744
    },
    {
        "question": "199 x 31",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 6169
    },
    {
        "question": "278 + 75",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 353
    },
    {
        "question": "288 + 19",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 307
    },
    {
        "question": "54 + 53",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 107
    },
    {
        "question": "167 - 27",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 140
    },
    {
        "question": "183 x 71",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 12993
    },
    {
        "question": "49 + 99",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 148
    },
    {
        "question": "282 x 37",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 10434
    },
    {
        "question": "119 + 57",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 176
    },
    {
        "question": "54 - 1",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 53
    },
    {
        "question": "81 + 81",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 162
    },
    {
        "question": "138 - 43",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 95
    },
    {
        "question": "133 x 79",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 10507
    },
    {
        "question": "189 - 23",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 166
    },
    {
        "question": "185 - 39",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 146
    },
    {
        "question": "282 x 89",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 25098
    },
    {
        "question": "163 x 9",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1467
    },
    {
        "question": "75 - 19",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 56
    },
    {
        "question": "371 - 29",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 342
    },
    {
        "question": "86 + 21",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 107
    },
    {
        "question": "381 - 5",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 376
    },
    {
        "question": "69 + 47",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 116
    },
    {
        "question": "362 + 43",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 405
    },
    {
        "question": "271 + 65",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 336
    },
    {
        "question": "349 x 93",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 32457
    },
    {
        "question": "269 x 43",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 11567
    },
    {
        "question": "102 - 55",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 47
    },
    {
        "question": "15 x 67",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1005
    },
    {
        "question": "209 + 7",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 216
    },
    {
        "question": "399 + 39",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 438
    },
    {
        "question": "50 + 29",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 79
    },
    {
        "question": "371 - 47",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 324
    },
    {
        "question": "172 + 11",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 183
    },
    {
        "question": "378 - 91",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 287
    },
    {
        "question": "145 - 35",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 110
    },
    {
        "question": "123 + 35",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 158
    },
    {
        "question": "169 - 73",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 96
    },
    {
        "question": "131 + 3",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 134
    },
    {
        "question": "313 + 29",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 342
    },
    {
        "question": "105 - 91",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 14
    },
    {
        "question": "256 + 9",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 265
    },
    {
        "question": "205 x 55",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 11275
    },
    {
        "question": "144 - 5",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 139
    },
    {
        "question": "104 x 17",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1768
    },
    {
        "question": "321 x 21",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 6741
    },
    {
        "question": "156 + 83",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 239
    },
    {
        "question": "325 x 21",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 6825
    },
    {
        "question": "317 + 25",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 342
    },
    {
        "question": "329 x 11",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 3619
    },
    {
        "question": "46 - 67",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -21
    },
    {
        "question": "297 x 51",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 15147
    },
    {
        "question": "142 x 3",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 426
    },
    {
        "question": "380 - 41",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 339
    },
    {
        "question": "306 - 11",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 295
    },
    {
        "question": "122 - 41",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 81
    },
    {
        "question": "270 - 27",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 243
    },
    {
        "question": "128 + 37",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 165
    },
    {
        "question": "228 - 43",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 185
    },
    {
        "question": "290 - 99",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 191
    },
    {
        "question": "55 + 37",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 92
    },
    {
        "question": "249 x 77",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 19173
    },
    {
        "question": "77 x 29",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 2233
    },
    {
        "question": "379 + 13",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 392
    },
    {
        "question": "329 - 17",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 312
    },
    {
        "question": "105 + 15",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 120
    },
    {
        "question": "122 - 67",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 55
    },
    {
        "question": "348 - 49",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 299
    },
    {
        "question": "185 - 13",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 172
    },
    {
        "question": "162 + 33",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 195
    },
    {
        "question": "275 x 63",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 17325
    },
    {
        "question": "10 - 93",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -83
    },
    {
        "question": "150 - 81",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 69
    },
    {
        "question": "343 + 59",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 402
    },
    {
        "question": "318 - 67",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 251
    },
    {
        "question": "2 x 73",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 146
    },
    {
        "question": "206 + 25",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 231
    },
    {
        "question": "274 - 13",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 261
    },
    {
        "question": "251 x 83",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 20833
    },
    {
        "question": "376 + 95",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 471
    },
    {
        "question": "88 + 35",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 123
    },
    {
        "question": "203 + 71",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 274
    },
    {
        "question": "192 x 87",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 16704
    },
    {
        "question": "141 - 1",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 140
    },
    {
        "question": "219 - 93",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 126
    },
    {
        "question": "76 x 77",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 5852
    },
    {
        "question": "65 x 87",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 5655
    },
    {
        "question": "172 + 1",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 173
    },
    {
        "question": "61 x 99",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 6039
    },
    {
        "question": "130 - 95",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 35
    },
    {
        "question": "149 - 89",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 60
    },
    {
        "question": "278 x 41",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 11398
    },
    {
        "question": "307 - 67",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 240
    },
    {
        "question": "303 - 25",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 278
    },
    {
        "question": "298 x 9",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 2682
    },
    {
        "question": "36 + 41",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 77
    },
    {
        "question": "324 x 31",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 10044
    },
    {
        "question": "73 + 17",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 90
    },
    {
        "question": "152 + 99",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 251
    },
    {
        "question": "73 + 41",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 114
    },
    {
        "question": "350 x 35",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 12250
    },
    {
        "question": "107 x 89",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 9523
    },
    {
        "question": "6 + 41",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 47
    },
    {
        "question": "74 x 39",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 2886
    },
    {
        "question": "322 x 49",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 15778
    },
    {
        "question": "7 x 37",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 259
    },
    {
        "question": "254 + 57",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 311
    },
    {
        "question": "318 + 7",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 325
    },
    {
        "question": "247 x 81",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 20007
    },
    {
        "question": "174 - 49",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 125
    },
    {
        "question": "262 + 37",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 299
    },
    {
        "question": "234 - 31",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 203
    },
    {
        "question": "376 - 49",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 327
    },
    {
        "question": "279 x 15",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 4185
    },
    {
        "question": "5 - 65",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -60
    },
    {
        "question": "376 x 77",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 28952
    },
    {
        "question": "71 - 87",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -16
    },
    {
        "question": "48 - 71",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -23
    },
    {
        "question": "234 - 69",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 165
    },
    {
        "question": "53 x 75",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 3975
    },
    {
        "question": "349 x 65",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 22685
    },
    {
        "question": "316 x 79",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 24964
    },
    {
        "question": "270 - 73",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 197
    },
    {
        "question": "203 x 97",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 19691
    },
    {
        "question": "177 + 57",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 234
    },
    {
        "question": "295 - 91",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 204
    },
    {
        "question": "139 + 89",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 228
    },
    {
        "question": "140 + 19",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 159
    },
    {
        "question": "388 - 1",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 387
    },
    {
        "question": "363 - 95",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 268
    },
    {
        "question": "128 + 81",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 209
    },
    {
        "question": "104 x 25",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 2600
    },
    {
        "question": "243 x 1",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 243
    },
    {
        "question": "105 x 45",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 4725
    },
    {
        "question": "181 x 97",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 17557
    },
    {
        "question": "332 + 1",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 333
    },
    {
        "question": "252 x 57",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 14364
    },
    {
        "question": "96 - 57",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 39
    },
    {
        "question": "160 + 41",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 201
    },
    {
        "question": "9 - 65",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -56
    },
    {
        "question": "15 x 23",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 345
    },
    {
        "question": "148 + 87",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 235
    },
    {
        "question": "32 - 7",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 25
    },
    {
        "question": "337 + 83",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 420
    },
    {
        "question": "375 - 51",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 324
    },
    {
        "question": "154 x 3",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 462
    },
    {
        "question": "63 + 81",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 144
    },
    {
        "question": "264 x 37",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 9768
    },
    {
        "question": "306 x 77",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 23562
    },
    {
        "question": "324 x 87",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 28188
    },
    {
        "question": "252 - 79",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 173
    },
    {
        "question": "87 x 67",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 5829
    },
    {
        "question": "291 - 13",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 278
    },
    {
        "question": "145 - 37",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 108
    },
    {
        "question": "268 + 7",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 275
    },
    {
        "question": "350 + 55",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 405
    },
    {
        "question": "9 + 5",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 14
    },
    {
        "question": "32 + 89",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 121
    },
    {
        "question": "242 x 81",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 19602
    },
    {
        "question": "242 - 29",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 213
    },
    {
        "question": "261 x 19",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 4959
    },
    {
        "question": "46 + 57",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 103
    },
    {
        "question": "37 + 31",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 68
    },
    {
        "question": "301 x 73",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 21973
    },
    {
        "question": "215 + 67",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 282
    },
    {
        "question": "196 x 93",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 18228
    },
    {
        "question": "286 + 79",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 365
    },
    {
        "question": "345 x 17",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 5865
    },
    {
        "question": "321 + 15",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 336
    },
    {
        "question": "154 x 71",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 10934
    },
    {
        "question": "285 x 43",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 12255
    },
    {
        "question": "24 + 11",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 35
    },
    {
        "question": "118 + 17",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 135
    },
    {
        "question": "224 x 85",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 19040
    },
    {
        "question": "101 x 33",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 3333
    },
    {
        "question": "163 - 83",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 80
    },
    {
        "question": "5 - 89",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -84
    },
    {
        "question": "111 - 25",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 86
    },
    {
        "question": "334 x 73",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 24382
    },
    {
        "question": "112 x 19",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 2128
    },
    {
        "question": "231 + 19",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 250
    },
    {
        "question": "322 x 29",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 9338
    },
    {
        "question": "72 - 57",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 15
    },
    {
        "question": "151 - 3",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 148
    },
    {
        "question": "390 + 23",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 413
    },
    {
        "question": "154 - 45",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 109
    },
    {
        "question": "92 - 91",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 1
    },
    {
        "question": "42 x 95",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 3990
    },
    {
        "question": "181 x 85",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 15385
    },
    {
        "question": "218 - 83",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 135
    },
    {
        "question": "152 x 39",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 5928
    },
    {
        "question": "18 x 33",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 594
    },
    {
        "question": "105 x 85",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 8925
    },
    {
        "question": "255 + 83",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 338
    },
    {
        "question": "262 - 21",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 241
    },
    {
        "question": "396 x 83",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 32868
    },
    {
        "question": "114 + 77",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 191
    },
    {
        "question": "6 - 33",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -27
    },
    {
        "question": "6 + 95",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 101
    },
    {
        "question": "88 - 37",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 51
    },
    {
        "question": "49 x 7",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 343
    },
    {
        "question": "67 - 97",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -30
    },
    {
        "question": "365 - 33",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 332
    },
    {
        "question": "350 - 89",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 261
    },
    {
        "question": "227 + 29",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 256
    },
    {
        "question": "33 x 27",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 891
    },
    {
        "question": "108 x 23",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 2484
    },
    {
        "question": "51 - 29",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 22
    },
    {
        "question": "181 + 25",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 206
    },
    {
        "question": "305 x 75",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 22875
    },
    {
        "question": "40 - 79",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -39
    },
    {
        "question": "226 x 47",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 10622
    },
    {
        "question": "395 + 53",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 448
    },
    {
        "question": "153 - 61",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 92
    },
    {
        "question": "203 x 59",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 11977
    },
    {
        "question": "274 - 77",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 197
    },
    {
        "question": "4 - 41",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -37
    },
    {
        "question": "166 x 37",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 6142
    },
    {
        "question": "273 x 1",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 273
    },
    {
        "question": "1 x 21",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 21
    },
    {
        "question": "160 - 45",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 115
    },
    {
        "question": "239 - 63",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 176
    },
    {
        "question": "53 - 55",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -2
    },
    {
        "question": "228 - 29",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 199
    },
    {
        "question": "355 + 9",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 364
    },
    {
        "question": "138 - 85",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 53
    },
    {
        "question": "72 x 5",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 360
    },
    {
        "question": "174 + 13",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 187
    },
    {
        "question": "81 x 77",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 6237
    },
    {
        "question": "2 + 97",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 99
    },
    {
        "question": "294 + 67",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 361
    },
    {
        "question": "241 - 17",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 224
    },
    {
        "question": "98 - 75",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 23
    },
    {
        "question": "315 x 73",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 22995
    },
    {
        "question": "128 x 13",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1664
    },
    {
        "question": "230 + 55",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 285
    },
    {
        "question": "24 + 17",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 41
    },
    {
        "question": "108 - 57",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 51
    },
    {
        "question": "242 - 23",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 219
    },
    {
        "question": "125 x 11",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1375
    },
    {
        "question": "175 x 59",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 10325
    },
    {
        "question": "168 + 89",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 257
    },
    {
        "question": "27 - 55",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -28
    },
    {
        "question": "355 + 17",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 372
    },
    {
        "question": "357 + 91",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 448
    },
    {
        "question": "294 + 35",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 329
    },
    {
        "question": "166 - 97",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 69
    },
    {
        "question": "202 + 27",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 229
    },
    {
        "question": "139 x 45",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 6255
    },
    {
        "question": "168 x 1",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 168
    },
    {
        "question": "102 + 39",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 141
    },
    {
        "question": "140 x 91",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 12740
    },
    {
        "question": "58 + 31",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 89
    },
    {
        "question": "299 - 37",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 262
    },
    {
        "question": "190 - 25",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 165
    },
    {
        "question": "267 x 85",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 22695
    },
    {
        "question": "144 - 9",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 135
    },
    {
        "question": "166 x 39",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 6474
    },
    {
        "question": "84 + 41",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 125
    },
    {
        "question": "146 + 79",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 225
    },
    {
        "question": "353 + 15",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 368
    },
    {
        "question": "73 + 81",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 154
    },
    {
        "question": "300 - 57",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 243
    },
    {
        "question": "1 + 99",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 100
    },
    {
        "question": "272 x 57",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 15504
    },
    {
        "question": "206 - 11",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 195
    },
    {
        "question": "206 x 61",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 12566
    },
    {
        "question": "245 x 53",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 12985
    },
    {
        "question": "301 x 27",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 8127
    },
    {
        "question": "362 + 39",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 401
    },
    {
        "question": "197 - 65",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 132
    },
    {
        "question": "71 x 93",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 6603
    },
    {
        "question": "180 - 99",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 81
    },
    {
        "question": "392 - 9",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 383
    },
    {
        "question": "255 - 73",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 182
    },
    {
        "question": "242 + 27",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 269
    },
    {
        "question": "306 - 63",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 243
    },
    {
        "question": "299 x 65",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 19435
    },
    {
        "question": "78 x 63",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 4914
    },
    {
        "question": "117 + 41",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 158
    },
    {
        "question": "135 x 59",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 7965
    },
    {
        "question": "21 - 73",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -52
    },
    {
        "question": "331 x 7",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 2317
    },
    {
        "question": "220 + 35",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 255
    },
    {
        "question": "197 + 17",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 214
    },
    {
        "question": "204 + 57",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 261
    },
    {
        "question": "164 x 67",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 10988
    },
    {
        "question": "198 - 33",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 165
    },
    {
        "question": "22 x 93",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 2046
    },
    {
        "question": "88 - 97",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -9
    },
    {
        "question": "96 x 43",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 4128
    },
    {
        "question": "30 x 77",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 2310
    },
    {
        "question": "46 - 31",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 15
    },
    {
        "question": "381 + 75",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 456
    },
    {
        "question": "43 + 97",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 140
    },
    {
        "question": "95 - 25",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 70
    },
    {
        "question": "357 - 45",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 312
    },
    {
        "question": "334 + 29",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 363
    },
    {
        "question": "86 x 15",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1290
    },
    {
        "question": "344 - 93",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 251
    },
    {
        "question": "101 - 75",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 26
    },
    {
        "question": "74 - 61",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 13
    },
    {
        "question": "19 x 77",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1463
    },
    {
        "question": "9 x 67",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 603
    },
    {
        "question": "378 + 5",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 383
    },
    {
        "question": "337 + 71",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 408
    },
    {
        "question": "310 + 17",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 327
    },
    {
        "question": "279 x 21",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 5859
    },
    {
        "question": "83 - 13",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 70
    },
    {
        "question": "362 x 53",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 19186
    },
    {
        "question": "114 x 91",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 10374
    },
    {
        "question": "370 - 31",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 339
    },
    {
        "question": "201 - 89",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 112
    },
    {
        "question": "285 x 17",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 4845
    },
    {
        "question": "114 - 29",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 85
    },
    {
        "question": "126 x 71",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 8946
    },
    {
        "question": "204 - 57",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 147
    },
    {
        "question": "50 + 65",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 115
    },
    {
        "question": "32 - 73",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -41
    },
    {
        "question": "126 + 93",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 219
    },
    {
        "question": "347 + 53",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 400
    },
    {
        "question": "76 x 79",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 6004
    },
    {
        "question": "111 + 99",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 210
    },
    {
        "question": "342 - 97",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 245
    },
    {
        "question": "188 x 31",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 5828
    },
    {
        "question": "297 - 21",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 276
    },
    {
        "question": "11 x 19",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 209
    },
    {
        "question": "121 + 53",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 174
    },
    {
        "question": "44 + 69",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 113
    },
    {
        "question": "26 - 47",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -21
    },
    {
        "question": "36 - 85",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -49
    },
    {
        "question": "160 x 13",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 2080
    },
    {
        "question": "350 + 9",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 359
    },
    {
        "question": "78 + 29",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 107
    },
    {
        "question": "121 + 5",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 126
    },
    {
        "question": "129 x 13",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1677
    },
    {
        "question": "355 + 31",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 386
    },
    {
        "question": "338 + 61",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 399
    },
    {
        "question": "68 + 3",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 71
    },
    {
        "question": "327 x 43",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 14061
    },
    {
        "question": "172 x 87",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 14964
    },
    {
        "question": "374 + 19",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 393
    },
    {
        "question": "339 + 81",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 420
    },
    {
        "question": "380 - 53",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 327
    },
    {
        "question": "65 - 81",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -16
    },
    {
        "question": "280 + 1",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 281
    },
    {
        "question": "372 x 79",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 29388
    },
    {
        "question": "214 + 35",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 249
    },
    {
        "question": "340 + 91",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 431
    },
    {
        "question": "245 + 51",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 296
    },
    {
        "question": "386 - 1",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 385
    },
    {
        "question": "172 x 35",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 6020
    },
    {
        "question": "21 - 67",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -46
    },
    {
        "question": "95 x 3",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 285
    },
    {
        "question": "393 - 55",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 338
    },
    {
        "question": "65 - 45",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 20
    },
    {
        "question": "226 + 81",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 307
    },
    {
        "question": "88 - 3",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 85
    },
    {
        "question": "93 + 71",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 164
    },
    {
        "question": "278 + 33",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 311
    },
    {
        "question": "308 x 97",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 29876
    },
    {
        "question": "353 x 91",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 32123
    },
    {
        "question": "278 + 35",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 313
    },
    {
        "question": "103 + 85",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 188
    },
    {
        "question": "162 x 99",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 16038
    },
    {
        "question": "195 + 55",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 250
    },
    {
        "question": "10 - 47",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -37
    },
    {
        "question": "308 + 91",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 399
    },
    {
        "question": "11 - 75",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -64
    },
    {
        "question": "119 - 23",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 96
    },
    {
        "question": "82 + 5",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 87
    },
    {
        "question": "9 x 39",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 351
    },
    {
        "question": "238 + 63",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 301
    },
    {
        "question": "132 x 45",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 5940
    },
    {
        "question": "277 + 23",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 300
    },
    {
        "question": "220 + 79",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 299
    },
    {
        "question": "163 x 43",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 7009
    },
    {
        "question": "27 + 21",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 48
    },
    {
        "question": "225 - 13",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 212
    },
    {
        "question": "64 + 65",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 129
    },
    {
        "question": "203 - 93",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 110
    },
    {
        "question": "87 - 15",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 72
    },
    {
        "question": "120 x 29",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 3480
    },
    {
        "question": "307 - 93",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 214
    },
    {
        "question": "63 x 35",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 2205
    },
    {
        "question": "251 - 43",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 208
    },
    {
        "question": "143 - 17",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 126
    },
    {
        "question": "25 + 41",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 66
    },
    {
        "question": "177 - 49",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 128
    },
    {
        "question": "160 - 47",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 113
    },
    {
        "question": "58 x 69",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 4002
    },
    {
        "question": "250 - 93",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 157
    },
    {
        "question": "214 + 37",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 251
    },
    {
        "question": "36 - 67",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -31
    },
    {
        "question": "79 x 61",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 4819
    },
    {
        "question": "372 x 43",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 15996
    },
    {
        "question": "313 x 3",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 939
    },
    {
        "question": "249 x 33",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 8217
    },
    {
        "question": "399 + 35",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 434
    },
    {
        "question": "345 + 25",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 370
    },
    {
        "question": "356 x 77",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 27412
    },
    {
        "question": "52 x 3",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 156
    },
    {
        "question": "32 x 11",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 352
    },
    {
        "question": "110 x 31",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 3410
    },
    {
        "question": "343 - 77",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 266
    },
    {
        "question": "185 - 41",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 144
    },
    {
        "question": "350 + 67",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 417
    },
    {
        "question": "72 + 81",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 153
    },
    {
        "question": "156 x 13",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 2028
    },
    {
        "question": "21 + 9",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 30
    },
    {
        "question": "351 x 45",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 15795
    },
    {
        "question": "197 x 83",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 16351
    },
    {
        "question": "337 - 79",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 258
    },
    {
        "question": "359 - 51",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 308
    },
    {
        "question": "379 - 75",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 304
    },
    {
        "question": "396 x 99",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 39204
    },
    {
        "question": "300 x 13",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 3900
    },
    {
        "question": "254 x 83",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 21082
    },
    {
        "question": "19 - 75",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -56
    },
    {
        "question": "112 - 5",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 107
    },
    {
        "question": "282 + 51",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 333
    },
    {
        "question": "85 x 9",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 765
    },
    {
        "question": "294 x 33",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 9702
    },
    {
        "question": "330 + 79",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 409
    },
    {
        "question": "55 x 59",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 3245
    },
    {
        "question": "254 - 55",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 199
    },
    {
        "question": "398 + 51",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 449
    },
    {
        "question": "226 - 43",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 183
    },
    {
        "question": "174 x 93",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 16182
    },
    {
        "question": "249 x 3",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 747
    },
    {
        "question": "97 x 61",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 5917
    },
    {
        "question": "29 - 5",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 24
    },
    {
        "question": "74 - 5",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 69
    },
    {
        "question": "42 + 41",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 83
    },
    {
        "question": "376 x 87",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 32712
    },
    {
        "question": "152 + 53",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 205
    },
    {
        "question": "325 + 43",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 368
    },
    {
        "question": "111 + 17",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 128
    },
    {
        "question": "373 - 27",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 346
    },
    {
        "question": "161 x 15",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 2415
    },
    {
        "question": "347 + 27",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 374
    },
    {
        "question": "365 - 19",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 346
    },
    {
        "question": "276 + 91",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 367
    },
    {
        "question": "260 - 43",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 217
    },
    {
        "question": "135 + 73",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 208
    },
    {
        "question": "30 - 87",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -57
    },
    {
        "question": "277 x 21",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 5817
    },
    {
        "question": "182 x 9",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1638
    },
    {
        "question": "242 + 13",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 255
    },
    {
        "question": "322 - 69",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 253
    },
    {
        "question": "228 - 57",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 171
    },
    {
        "question": "266 x 17",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 4522
    },
    {
        "question": "286 x 23",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 6578
    },
    {
        "question": "316 + 3",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 319
    },
    {
        "question": "338 - 37",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 301
    },
    {
        "question": "29 + 79",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 108
    },
    {
        "question": "169 - 33",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 136
    },
    {
        "question": "135 + 7",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 142
    },
    {
        "question": "271 + 71",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 342
    },
    {
        "question": "213 + 29",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 242
    },
    {
        "question": "240 x 57",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 13680
    },
    {
        "question": "110 + 5",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 115
    },
    {
        "question": "18 - 35",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -17
    },
    {
        "question": "213 x 31",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 6603
    },
    {
        "question": "234 + 63",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 297
    },
    {
        "question": "276 x 79",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 21804
    },
    {
        "question": "15 x 45",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 675
    },
    {
        "question": "176 x 29",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 5104
    },
    {
        "question": "23 x 67",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1541
    },
    {
        "question": "116 - 55",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 61
    },
    {
        "question": "83 + 15",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 98
    },
    {
        "question": "345 - 45",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 300
    },
    {
        "question": "146 + 99",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 245
    },
    {
        "question": "269 x 79",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 21251
    },
    {
        "question": "240 x 9",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 2160
    },
    {
        "question": "367 x 91",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 33397
    },
    {
        "question": "167 + 21",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 188
    },
    {
        "question": "316 + 97",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 413
    },
    {
        "question": "231 x 3",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 693
    },
    {
        "question": "296 x 75",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 22200
    },
    {
        "question": "18 + 99",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 117
    },
    {
        "question": "175 x 13",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 2275
    },
    {
        "question": "212 - 89",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 123
    },
    {
        "question": "330 x 77",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 25410
    },
    {
        "question": "80 + 11",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 91
    },
    {
        "question": "374 + 13",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 387
    },
    {
        "question": "161 - 19",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 142
    },
    {
        "question": "5 + 45",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 50
    },
    {
        "question": "95 - 65",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 30
    },
    {
        "question": "227 + 47",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 274
    },
    {
        "question": "129 + 39",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 168
    },
    {
        "question": "171 x 93",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 15903
    },
    {
        "question": "339 x 27",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 9153
    },
    {
        "question": "101 - 71",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 30
    },
    {
        "question": "206 + 97",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 303
    },
    {
        "question": "231 + 39",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 270
    },
    {
        "question": "217 + 59",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 276
    },
    {
        "question": "324 + 53",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 377
    },
    {
        "question": "225 x 25",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 5625
    },
    {
        "question": "366 - 81",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 285
    },
    {
        "question": "357 + 25",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 382
    },
    {
        "question": "315 x 27",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 8505
    },
    {
        "question": "274 + 21",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 295
    },
    {
        "question": "299 x 81",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 24219
    },
    {
        "question": "6 - 47",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -41
    },
    {
        "question": "8 x 11",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 88
    },
    {
        "question": "372 + 31",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 403
    },
    {
        "question": "202 x 19",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 3838
    },
    {
        "question": "320 + 35",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 355
    },
    {
        "question": "71 x 97",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 6887
    },
    {
        "question": "106 x 33",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 3498
    },
    {
        "question": "236 + 9",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 245
    },
    {
        "question": "219 + 99",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 318
    },
    {
        "question": "173 - 9",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 164
    },
    {
        "question": "376 + 33",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 409
    },
    {
        "question": "229 + 65",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 294
    },
    {
        "question": "102 + 19",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 121
    },
    {
        "question": "213 + 45",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 258
    },
    {
        "question": "195 - 97",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 98
    },
    {
        "question": "261 - 13",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 248
    },
    {
        "question": "306 - 29",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 277
    },
    {
        "question": "138 - 73",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 65
    },
    {
        "question": "68 - 91",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -23
    },
    {
        "question": "37 - 1",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 36
    },
    {
        "question": "40 + 43",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 83
    },
    {
        "question": "66 - 61",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 5
    },
    {
        "question": "124 - 9",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 115
    },
    {
        "question": "216 x 65",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 14040
    },
    {
        "question": "36 + 65",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 101
    },
    {
        "question": "170 x 91",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 15470
    },
    {
        "question": "262 + 87",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 349
    },
    {
        "question": "139 x 95",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 13205
    },
    {
        "question": "124 - 65",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 59
    },
    {
        "question": "311 + 13",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 324
    },
    {
        "question": "291 - 49",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 242
    },
    {
        "question": "199 x 87",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 17313
    },
    {
        "question": "228 + 13",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 241
    },
    {
        "question": "160 - 91",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 69
    },
    {
        "question": "63 + 47",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 110
    },
    {
        "question": "121 x 33",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 3993
    },
    {
        "question": "264 x 49",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 12936
    },
    {
        "question": "365 - 85",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 280
    },
    {
        "question": "383 x 33",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 12639
    },
    {
        "question": "392 + 51",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 443
    },
    {
        "question": "98 + 79",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 177
    },
    {
        "question": "271 x 53",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 14363
    },
    {
        "question": "257 - 43",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 214
    },
    {
        "question": "328 x 33",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 10824
    },
    {
        "question": "74 x 49",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 3626
    },
    {
        "question": "372 + 17",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 389
    },
    {
        "question": "80 x 3",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 240
    },
    {
        "question": "380 + 35",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 415
    },
    {
        "question": "380 - 61",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 319
    },
    {
        "question": "66 + 95",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 161
    },
    {
        "question": "228 - 1",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 227
    },
    {
        "question": "18 - 65",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -47
    },
    {
        "question": "321 - 51",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 270
    },
    {
        "question": "252 - 5",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 247
    },
    {
        "question": "283 - 41",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 242
    },
    {
        "question": "381 x 47",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 17907
    },
    {
        "question": "198 x 79",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 15642
    },
    {
        "question": "96 x 57",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 5472
    },
    {
        "question": "11 x 31",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 341
    },
    {
        "question": "287 + 45",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 332
    },
    {
        "question": "46 - 93",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -47
    },
    {
        "question": "274 + 99",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 373
    },
    {
        "question": "347 - 65",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 282
    },
    {
        "question": "295 x 55",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 16225
    },
    {
        "question": "186 x 93",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 17298
    },
    {
        "question": "299 x 81",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 24219
    },
    {
        "question": "343 - 27",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 316
    },
    {
        "question": "65 + 89",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 154
    },
    {
        "question": "305 - 5",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 300
    },
    {
        "question": "40 + 27",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 67
    },
    {
        "question": "37 + 53",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 90
    },
    {
        "question": "79 - 77",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "140 x 3",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 420
    },
    {
        "question": "298 + 11",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 309
    },
    {
        "question": "65 + 73",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 138
    },
    {
        "question": "270 - 99",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 171
    },
    {
        "question": "199 x 91",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 18109
    },
    {
        "question": "230 + 27",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 257
    },
    {
        "question": "264 + 67",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 331
    },
    {
        "question": "205 + 97",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 302
    },
    {
        "question": "207 x 85",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 17595
    },
    {
        "question": "165 - 11",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 154
    },
    {
        "question": "377 + 23",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 400
    },
    {
        "question": "299 - 71",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 228
    },
    {
        "question": "220 x 39",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 8580
    },
    {
        "question": "148 x 71",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 10508
    },
    {
        "question": "95 - 29",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 66
    },
    {
        "question": "155 x 21",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 3255
    },
    {
        "question": "275 x 57",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 15675
    },
    {
        "question": "101 + 77",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 178
    },
    {
        "question": "321 - 65",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 256
    },
    {
        "question": "56 - 89",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -33
    },
    {
        "question": "191 x 27",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 5157
    },
    {
        "question": "71 - 99",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -28
    },
    {
        "question": "19 x 37",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 703
    },
    {
        "question": "54 x 37",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1998
    },
    {
        "question": "42 x 85",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 3570
    },
    {
        "question": "391 x 25",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 9775
    },
    {
        "question": "21 - 35",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -14
    },
    {
        "question": "332 + 59",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 391
    },
    {
        "question": "109 - 19",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 90
    },
    {
        "question": "88 + 85",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 173
    },
    {
        "question": "309 - 41",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 268
    },
    {
        "question": "196 + 69",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 265
    },
    {
        "question": "148 x 3",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 444
    },
    {
        "question": "369 + 79",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 448
    },
    {
        "question": "114 - 95",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 19
    },
    {
        "question": "30 - 31",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -1
    },
    {
        "question": "97 + 25",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 122
    },
    {
        "question": "378 x 53",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 20034
    },
    {
        "question": "159 - 73",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 86
    },
    {
        "question": "260 x 61",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 15860
    },
    {
        "question": "48 + 43",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 91
    },
    {
        "question": "263 + 53",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 316
    },
    {
        "question": "238 + 65",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 303
    },
    {
        "question": "365 + 73",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 438
    },
    {
        "question": "199 + 35",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 234
    },
    {
        "question": "317 x 45",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 14265
    },
    {
        "question": "24 x 71",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1704
    },
    {
        "question": "373 + 53",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 426
    },
    {
        "question": "147 x 19",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 2793
    },
    {
        "question": "224 - 1",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 223
    },
    {
        "question": "97 x 99",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 9603
    },
    {
        "question": "38 x 99",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 3762
    },
    {
        "question": "231 - 1",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 230
    },
    {
        "question": "290 + 63",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 353
    },
    {
        "question": "93 x 1",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 93
    },
    {
        "question": "115 x 95",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 10925
    },
    {
        "question": "136 - 47",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 89
    },
    {
        "question": "127 - 57",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 70
    },
    {
        "question": "395 + 77",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 472
    },
    {
        "question": "298 + 11",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 309
    },
    {
        "question": "306 x 77",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 23562
    },
    {
        "question": "283 - 49",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 234
    },
    {
        "question": "301 - 9",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 292
    },
    {
        "question": "127 + 67",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 194
    },
    {
        "question": "37 + 57",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 94
    },
    {
        "question": "20 - 25",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -5
    },
    {
        "question": "361 + 47",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 408
    },
    {
        "question": "305 + 57",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 362
    },
    {
        "question": "326 + 99",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 425
    },
    {
        "question": "64 + 55",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 119
    },
    {
        "question": "203 x 61",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 12383
    },
    {
        "question": "131 - 69",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 62
    },
    {
        "question": "364 x 85",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 30940
    },
    {
        "question": "55 x 25",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1375
    },
    {
        "question": "131 - 63",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 68
    },
    {
        "question": "333 + 83",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 416
    },
    {
        "question": "347 - 73",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 274
    },
    {
        "question": "363 x 69",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 25047
    },
    {
        "question": "279 + 63",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 342
    },
    {
        "question": "80 + 97",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 177
    },
    {
        "question": "397 + 13",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 410
    },
    {
        "question": "95 x 5",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 475
    },
    {
        "question": "23 x 43",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 989
    },
    {
        "question": "370 + 19",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 389
    },
    {
        "question": "372 x 21",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 7812
    },
    {
        "question": "13 x 71",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 923
    },
    {
        "question": "183 - 53",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 130
    },
    {
        "question": "245 + 37",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 282
    },
    {
        "question": "110 x 45",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 4950
    },
    {
        "question": "92 + 69",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 161
    },
    {
        "question": "200 x 91",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 18200
    },
    {
        "question": "372 x 85",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 31620
    },
    {
        "question": "26 + 65",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 91
    },
    {
        "question": "312 + 85",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 397
    },
    {
        "question": "248 + 33",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 281
    },
    {
        "question": "298 + 89",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 387
    },
    {
        "question": "47 + 95",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 142
    },
    {
        "question": "216 x 85",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 18360
    },
    {
        "question": "324 - 5",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 319
    },
    {
        "question": "291 + 85",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 376
    },
    {
        "question": "390 - 65",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 325
    },
    {
        "question": "345 - 11",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 334
    },
    {
        "question": "33 x 31",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1023
    },
    {
        "question": "124 + 95",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 219
    },
    {
        "question": "21 - 83",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -62
    },
    {
        "question": "320 - 77",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 243
    },
    {
        "question": "95 - 47",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 48
    },
    {
        "question": "290 - 97",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 193
    },
    {
        "question": "377 - 73",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 304
    },
    {
        "question": "93 - 13",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 80
    },
    {
        "question": "231 x 29",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 6699
    },
    {
        "question": "336 - 65",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 271
    },
    {
        "question": "85 x 65",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 5525
    },
    {
        "question": "75 x 1",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 75
    },
    {
        "question": "223 x 59",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 13157
    },
    {
        "question": "319 - 3",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 316
    },
    {
        "question": "128 - 15",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 113
    },
    {
        "question": "171 + 41",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 212
    },
    {
        "question": "394 - 49",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 345
    },
    {
        "question": "387 x 27",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 10449
    },
    {
        "question": "209 - 39",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 170
    },
    {
        "question": "103 + 61",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 164
    },
    {
        "question": "48 + 23",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 71
    },
    {
        "question": "321 + 57",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 378
    },
    {
        "question": "95 + 33",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 128
    },
    {
        "question": "322 x 45",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 14490
    },
    {
        "question": "163 - 9",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 154
    },
    {
        "question": "357 x 33",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 11781
    },
    {
        "question": "226 + 51",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 277
    },
    {
        "question": "186 x 3",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 558
    },
    {
        "question": "205 - 15",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 190
    },
    {
        "question": "14 + 11",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 25
    },
    {
        "question": "7 - 87",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -80
    },
    {
        "question": "186 - 59",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 127
    },
    {
        "question": "204 + 9",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 213
    },
    {
        "question": "86 + 5",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 91
    },
    {
        "question": "336 x 11",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 3696
    },
    {
        "question": "262 x 83",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 21746
    },
    {
        "question": "156 - 61",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 95
    },
    {
        "question": "399 x 69",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 27531
    },
    {
        "question": "340 + 39",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 379
    },
    {
        "question": "95 x 81",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 7695
    },
    {
        "question": "89 x 1",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 89
    },
    {
        "question": "362 x 47",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 17014
    },
    {
        "question": "31 + 87",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 118
    },
    {
        "question": "87 + 41",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 128
    },
    {
        "question": "238 + 59",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 297
    },
    {
        "question": "200 + 3",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 203
    },
    {
        "question": "333 - 83",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 250
    },
    {
        "question": "26 + 67",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 93
    },
    {
        "question": "336 x 43",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 14448
    },
    {
        "question": "221 - 73",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 148
    },
    {
        "question": "264 - 7",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 257
    },
    {
        "question": "300 - 47",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 253
    },
    {
        "question": "208 + 51",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 259
    },
    {
        "question": "292 x 21",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 6132
    },
    {
        "question": "150 + 83",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 233
    },
    {
        "question": "373 - 79",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 294
    },
    {
        "question": "325 x 5",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1625
    },
    {
        "question": "244 x 15",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 3660
    },
    {
        "question": "229 + 83",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 312
    },
    {
        "question": "139 + 17",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 156
    },
    {
        "question": "153 - 29",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 124
    },
    {
        "question": "107 - 93",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 14
    },
    {
        "question": "217 + 75",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 292
    },
    {
        "question": "320 x 5",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1600
    },
    {
        "question": "323 - 81",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 242
    },
    {
        "question": "294 x 71",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 20874
    },
    {
        "question": "287 + 49",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 336
    },
    {
        "question": "105 + 87",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 192
    },
    {
        "question": "284 x 61",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 17324
    },
    {
        "question": "266 + 75",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 341
    },
    {
        "question": "53 x 71",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 3763
    },
    {
        "question": "209 + 93",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 302
    },
    {
        "question": "57 + 35",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 92
    },
    {
        "question": "101 - 5",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 96
    },
    {
        "question": "130 - 41",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 89
    },
    {
        "question": "204 - 37",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 167
    },
    {
        "question": "17 x 17",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 289
    },
    {
        "question": "267 + 23",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 290
    },
    {
        "question": "65 x 77",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 5005
    },
    {
        "question": "93 - 3",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 90
    },
    {
        "question": "237 x 31",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 7347
    },
    {
        "question": "160 x 15",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 2400
    },
    {
        "question": "5 - 3",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 2
    },
    {
        "question": "19 - 5",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 14
    },
    {
        "question": "179 + 99",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 278
    },
    {
        "question": "15 + 81",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 96
    },
    {
        "question": "126 x 33",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 4158
    },
    {
        "question": "352 - 57",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 295
    },
    {
        "question": "22 x 3",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 66
    },
    {
        "question": "358 - 25",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 333
    },
    {
        "question": "8 - 77",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -69
    },
    {
        "question": "260 + 7",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 267
    },
    {
        "question": "188 x 99",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 18612
    },
    {
        "question": "45 + 43",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 88
    },
    {
        "question": "242 - 85",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 157
    },
    {
        "question": "191 - 19",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 172
    },
    {
        "question": "279 + 37",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 316
    },
    {
        "question": "54 x 55",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 2970
    },
    {
        "question": "310 + 7",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 317
    },
    {
        "question": "310 - 73",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 237
    },
    {
        "question": "69 - 79",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -10
    },
    {
        "question": "69 x 41",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 2829
    },
    {
        "question": "90 - 35",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 55
    },
    {
        "question": "54 + 93",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 147
    },
    {
        "question": "265 + 87",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 352
    },
    {
        "question": "342 - 33",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 309
    },
    {
        "question": "379 - 47",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 332
    },
    {
        "question": "331 x 5",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1655
    },
    {
        "question": "329 - 79",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 250
    },
    {
        "question": "167 x 49",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 8183
    },
    {
        "question": "229 x 21",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 4809
    },
    {
        "question": "62 - 65",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -3
    },
    {
        "question": "91 x 31",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 2821
    },
    {
        "question": "269 x 73",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 19637
    },
    {
        "question": "238 + 79",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 317
    },
    {
        "question": "58 + 61",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 119
    },
    {
        "question": "115 + 89",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 204
    },
    {
        "question": "53 - 79",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -26
    },
    {
        "question": "76 x 79",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 6004
    },
    {
        "question": "63 - 1",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 62
    },
    {
        "question": "266 x 71",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 18886
    },
    {
        "question": "364 x 29",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 10556
    },
    {
        "question": "268 - 59",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 209
    },
    {
        "question": "303 x 1",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 303
    },
    {
        "question": "19 x 89",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1691
    },
    {
        "question": "185 - 79",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 106
    },
    {
        "question": "146 x 21",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 3066
    },
    {
        "question": "283 - 95",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 188
    },
    {
        "question": "254 + 69",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 323
    },
    {
        "question": "318 + 85",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 403
    },
    {
        "question": "255 + 91",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 346
    },
    {
        "question": "273 x 65",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 17745
    },
    {
        "question": "270 + 73",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 343
    },
    {
        "question": "142 x 13",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1846
    },
    {
        "question": "371 + 15",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 386
    },
    {
        "question": "14 + 9",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 23
    },
    {
        "question": "16 + 35",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 51
    },
    {
        "question": "29 + 9",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 38
    },
    {
        "question": "250 + 73",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 323
    },
    {
        "question": "385 + 23",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 408
    },
    {
        "question": "188 x 83",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 15604
    },
    {
        "question": "137 + 23",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 160
    },
    {
        "question": "75 x 63",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 4725
    },
    {
        "question": "307 x 83",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 25481
    },
    {
        "question": "88 x 5",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 440
    },
    {
        "question": "128 x 17",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 2176
    },
    {
        "question": "52 + 43",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 95
    },
    {
        "question": "381 + 19",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 400
    },
    {
        "question": "393 - 53",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 340
    },
    {
        "question": "134 x 49",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 6566
    },
    {
        "question": "60 x 65",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 3900
    },
    {
        "question": "114 + 95",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 209
    },
    {
        "question": "363 x 23",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 8349
    },
    {
        "question": "104 - 83",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 21
    },
    {
        "question": "97 x 53",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 5141
    },
    {
        "question": "187 - 81",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 106
    },
    {
        "question": "386 + 37",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 423
    },
    {
        "question": "12 x 25",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 300
    },
    {
        "question": "54 + 23",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 77
    },
    {
        "question": "30 - 57",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -27
    },
    {
        "question": "295 + 41",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 336
    },
    {
        "question": "196 x 29",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 5684
    },
    {
        "question": "271 - 53",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 218
    },
    {
        "question": "68 + 45",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 113
    },
    {
        "question": "85 x 91",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 7735
    },
    {
        "question": "158 - 41",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 117
    },
    {
        "question": "143 - 67",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 76
    },
    {
        "question": "240 x 97",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 23280
    },
    {
        "question": "203 - 91",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 112
    },
    {
        "question": "368 + 55",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 423
    },
    {
        "question": "252 x 7",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1764
    },
    {
        "question": "302 + 25",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 327
    },
    {
        "question": "284 x 37",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 10508
    },
    {
        "question": "18 + 63",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 81
    },
    {
        "question": "66 x 29",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 1914
    },
    {
        "question": "18 x 43",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 774
    },
    {
        "question": "182 + 75",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 257
    },
    {
        "question": "176 + 57",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 233
    },
    {
        "question": "3 x 85",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 255
    },
    {
        "question": "162 - 65",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": 97
    },
    {
        "question": "272 + 61",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 333
    },
    {
        "question": "58 x 59",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 3422
    },
    {
        "question": "257 + 45",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 302
    },
    {
        "question": "42 - 93",
        "level": "EASY",
        "answer": -51
    },
    {
        "question": "387 x 17",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 6579
    },
    {
        "question": "388 x 63",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 24444
    },
    {
        "question": "218 + 25",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 243
    },
    {
        "question": "254 x 49",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 12446
    },
    {
        "question": "397 x 25",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 9925
    },
    {
        "question": "319 x 51",
        "level": "HARD",
        "answer": 16269
    },
    {
        "question": "359 - 55",
        "level": "MEDIUM",
        "answer": 304
    }
]